{"author_id": "20jdn2f6l8qd73yj6y2kppbc798xstql", "truth": 0, "tweets": ["READ &gt;&gt; The Best of New Zealand: A Photo Essay #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Things to do in San Miguel de Allende: Travel Guide and 3 Day Itinerary #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 10 Things to do in Florida (besides hanging out with Mickey) #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 15+ Best Things to do in Oaxaca, Mexico #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Adventuring at Home: 27 Travelers Prove it’s Possible #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Travel MORE in 2017:  Last Minute Accommodation Options + Ideas #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 5 Places I’ve Never Been (And Why I Want To Go) #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Cafe du Monde – A Sugary Treat in the French Quarter #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; London (For a Hot Second) #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Reaching New Heights in Napa: Hot Air Ballooning over the Valley #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Scuba Diving for the First Time: My Experience in Santorini #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 15+ Best Things to Do in Athens, Greece #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Experiencing Yosemite National Park in One Day Flat #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Discovering BANANA KETCHUP in St. Lucia: The Secret Taste of the Caribbean #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; HONDURAS: Best Things to See and Do #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; City Views from a Seattle Seaplane [Photos] #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Where to Stay in Dublin, Ireland: Best Places to Stay #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Ten Things to do in Sri Lanka, On the Cheap! #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 3 Days in Taipei: The Perfect Taipei Itinerary #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; The 25 Best Long Weekend Trips from San Francisco #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Best Things to do in Hoi An in 3 Days: A Hoi An Itinerary Guide #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; The New York Botanical Gardens: Up Close and Personal #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Nine (Super-Awesome) Things to do in Nashville, TN #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 365 Days Later… And I’ve Been Married a Whole Year! #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 15+ Things to do in Havana, Cuba #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Where to Stay in Santorini: Top Luxury, Boutique, and Budget Hotels #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Airplane Entertainment: How to Keep Yourself Sane on Long Flights #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; First Views of the Negev: A Photo Essay #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 3 Days in Mexico City: The Perfect Mexico City Itinerary #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; A Two Week Vietnam Itinerary: A Complete First-Timer’s Guide #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 10 Things To Do in Malaysia: SE Asia’s Most Overlooked Country #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 22 Ways to Cut Costs on Your (Once-in-a-lifetime) Trip to Tahiti #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Blogging from A-Z April Challenge: One Week ‘Til Go Time #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Masada: The Hike Down on the Never Ending Snake Path #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Top Summer Festivals in Europe // MUSIC, DANCING, and FOOD #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 15 Best Things to do in Seville, Spain #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; The Ultimate California Coast Road Trip Itinerary #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; How I Made $70k+ Blogging in 2018 While Holding a Full Time Job #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Y is for YOLO and all those crazy stupid things I want to do #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 23 Reasons Why You Should Love San Pedro, Belize #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; An Epic Canadian Rockies Itinerary: From Calgary to Jasper and Beyond #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 2 Days in Bangkok, Thailand: A (Super) Comprehensive Bangkok Itinerary #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; The 15 Best Things to Do in Ljubljana Slovenia #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 18 Summer Essentials for Any Warm-Weather Trip #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 15+ Best Things to Do in Miami #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 15+ Best Things to do in Prague, Czech Republic #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Feelin’ a little artsy in the Mission #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Get Free Travel by Managing Points and Miles with AwardWallet #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Where to Go in March 2020: Travel Destination Inspiration #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 3 Days in Barcelona: A Barcelona Itinerary for the First Time Visitor #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Utah National Parks Road Trip: A Spectacular One Week in Utah Itinerary #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Day Trips from Reykjavik: Iceland Day Trips You Can’t Miss #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 35+ Winter Weekend Getaways in the USA [Snowy and Warm Included!] #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 10 Days in Bali: The Perfect 10 Day Bali Itinerary For Your First Visit #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 48 Hours in Atlanta, GA #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Best Day Trips from Naples, Italy #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Majestic Monument Valley: A Tour Through The Navajo Tribal Park #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; X is for X-TREME hikes: The Toughest, Roughest, Muddiest in the World #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Things to do in Chicago: What to See, Do, Eat, + Enjoy #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Visiting the San Blas Islands in Panama: An Idyllic Island Escape #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Part-Time Traveler Talk with Aaron Cruz #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Things to Do in Crater Lake National Park: A Perfect Two Day Stay #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; An Interview with a Flight Attendant #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 48 Hours in Naples, Italy #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; GALAPAGOS ISLANDS: Best Things to See and Do #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Parasailing in Punta Cana: A Birds Eye View #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; The Hotels of Las Vegas #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 125+ Things to do in San Francisco:  The Ultimate San Francisco Bucket List #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 15 Best Things to do in Cape Town #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 10 Things to do in Budapest, Hungary #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; San Francisco to Seattle Road Trip: A Trip to The Pacific Northwest + MORE #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 35+ Places to Visit in Tokyo // Tokyo Bucket List Inspiration #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 7 Gorgeous Greek Beaches You Can’t Miss #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; How (and why) You Should Splurge on First Class Airfare (again, again, and again) #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; The View from the Window Seat #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 48 Hours in Curacao // What to See, Do, and Eat! #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Stay Connected While Traveling with Vision Global Wifi #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Israel is Incredible: A Journey through Instagram #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Top 4 Ways to Enjoy your Las Vegas Experience in Style! #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; How To Spend A Long Weekend in the Poconos, PA #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; A Taste of Barbados: The Best of the Best #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 15+ Best Things to Do in Paris #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; B is for BEACHES: My Favorite of the Caribbean #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Butts, Balloons, and Beer: The Señor Frogs Experience #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; 17 Things to Do in Toronto in Winter: Full Guide to the City #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; K is for KAUAI and Other Possible Travel Plans for 2013 #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Part-Time Traveler Talk with Megan Hettwer #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; R is for RUM CAKE: The Key to A Happy Crowd #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; How to Have The Best Road Trip EVER #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; O is for OLD SAN JUAN [puerto rico]: A Colorful Photo Essay #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Why I Want to Move to Carmel by the Sea, California #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Best Day Trips from Amsterdam: Where to Go to Get Outta the City #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Cruising: Yay or Nay? The Positives and the Negatives #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Seven of Seattle’s Top Tourist Attractions #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; big changes on the blog! #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Best Day Trips From Sofia, Bulgaria #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; For the Wine Lovers: Hotel Vintage Seattle #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; And the Oscar goes to… #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Monterey and the 17 Mile Drive #URL#", "READ &gt;&gt; Highlights from our Cross Country Road Trip (NYC to SF) #URL#"], "ents": [[["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["The Best of New Zealand", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["San Miguel de Allende: Travel Guide", "GPE"], ["3", "CARDINAL"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["10", "CARDINAL"], ["Florida", "GPE"], ["Mickey", "PERSON"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["15", "CARDINAL"], ["Oaxaca", "GPE"], ["Mexico", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Adventuring", "GPE"], ["27", "CARDINAL"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["2017", "DATE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["5", "CARDINAL"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Cafe du Monde", "FAC"], ["A Sugary Treat", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["French", "NORP"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["London", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["New Heights", "GPE"], ["Napa", "GPE"], ["Valley", "LOC"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Scuba Diving", "PERSON"], ["First", "ORDINAL"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["15", "CARDINAL"], ["Athens", "GPE"], ["Greece", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Yosemite National Park", "FAC"], ["One", "CARDINAL"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Discovering BANANA KETCHUP", "ORG"], ["St. Lucia", "GPE"], ["Caribbean", "LOC"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["City Views", "ORG"], ["Seattle Seaplane", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Stay", "ORG"], ["Dublin", "GPE"], ["Ireland", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Ten", "CARDINAL"], ["Sri Lanka", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["3 Days", "DATE"], ["Taipei", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["25", "CARDINAL"], ["San Francisco", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Hoi An in", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["3 Days", "DATE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["The New York Botanical Gardens", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Nine", "CARDINAL"], ["Nashville", "GPE"], ["TN", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["365 Days Later", "DATE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["15", "CARDINAL"], ["Havana", "GPE"], ["Cuba", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Santorini", "NORP"], ["Boutique", "GPE"], ["Budget Hotels", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Airplane Entertainment", "ORG"], ["Yourself Sane on Long Flights", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["First Views of the Negev:", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["3 Days", "DATE"], ["Mexico City", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Two Week", "DATE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["10", "CARDINAL"], ["Things To Do", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Malaysia", "GPE"], ["Asia", "LOC"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["22", "CARDINAL"], ["Tahiti", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["April", "DATE"], ["One Week", "DATE"], ["Til Go Time", "PERSON"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Masada", "GPE"], ["the Never Ending Snake Path", "EVENT"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Summer", "DATE"], ["Europe", "LOC"], ["DANCING", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["15", "CARDINAL"], ["Seville", "GPE"], ["Spain", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["The Ultimate California Coast Road Trip Itinerary", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["70k+", "MONEY"], ["2018", "DATE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["YOLO", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["23", "CARDINAL"], ["San Pedro", "GPE"], ["Belize", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Calgary", "GPE"], ["Jasper", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["2 Days", "DATE"], ["Bangkok", "GPE"], ["Thailand", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["The 15", "PRODUCT"], ["Ljubljana Slovenia", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["18 Summer", "DATE"], ["Essentials for Any Warm-Weather Trip", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["15", "CARDINAL"], ["Miami", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["15", "CARDINAL"], ["Prague", "GPE"], ["Czech Republic", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Feelin", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Miles", "PERSON"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["March 2020", "DATE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["3 Days", "DATE"], ["Barcelona", "GPE"], ["First", "ORDINAL"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Utah", "GPE"], ["Parks Road Trip", "FAC"], ["One Week", "DATE"], ["Utah", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Day Trips", "FAC"], ["Reykjavik", "GPE"], ["Iceland Day Trips You Can’t", "EVENT"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["35+ Winter Weekend Getaways", "DATE"], ["USA", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["10 Days", "DATE"], ["First", "ORDINAL"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["48 Hours", "TIME"], ["Atlanta", "GPE"], ["GA", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Best Day Trips", "EVENT"], ["Naples", "GPE"], ["Italy", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Majestic Monument Valley", "LOC"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Muddiest", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Chicago", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["the San Blas Islands", "GPE"], ["Panama", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Traveler Talk", "PERSON"], ["Aaron Cruz", "PERSON"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Crater Lake National Park", "LOC"], ["Two Day", "DATE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["48 Hours", "TIME"], ["Naples", "GPE"], ["Italy", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["GALAPAGOS ISLANDS", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Punta Cana", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["The Hotels of Las Vegas", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["125", "CARDINAL"], ["San Francisco", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["15", "CARDINAL"], ["Cape Town", "LOC"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["10", "CARDINAL"], ["Budapest", "GPE"], ["Hungary", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["San Francisco", "GPE"], ["Seattle", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["35", "CARDINAL"], ["Tokyo", "GPE"], ["Tokyo", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["7", "CARDINAL"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["First", "ORDINAL"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["The View from the Window Seat", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["48 Hours", "TIME"], ["Curacao", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Stay Connected While Traveling with Vision Global Wifi", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Israel", "GPE"], ["Instagram", "NORP"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["4", "CARDINAL"], ["Las Vegas", "GPE"], ["Style", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["How To Spend A Long Weekend in the Poconos", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["15", "CARDINAL"], ["Paris", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["BEACHES", "LOC"], ["Caribbean", "LOC"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Butts", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["17", "CARDINAL"], ["Toronto", "GPE"], ["Winter", "DATE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["K", "ORG"], ["KAUAI", "PERSON"], ["2013", "DATE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Traveler Talk", "PERSON"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["OLD SAN JUAN", "ORG"], ["rico", "LAW"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Carmel", "GPE"], ["Sea", "GPE"], ["California", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Best Day Trips", "EVENT"], ["Amsterdam", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Yay", "PERSON"], ["Nay", "PERSON"], ["Positives", "NORP"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Seven", "CARDINAL"], ["Seattle", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Best Day Trips", "EVENT"], ["Sofia", "GPE"], ["Bulgaria", "GPE"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Oscar", "PERSON"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["Monterey", "ORG"], ["17", "CARDINAL"]], [["READ &gt;&gt", "ORG"], ["SF", "GPE"]]], "POS_tags": [[{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "X", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "NUM", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "SCONJ", "VERB", "ADP", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADJ", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SYM", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PROPN", "PRON", "VERB", "ADV", "AUX", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "CCONJ", "AUX"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "ADJ", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADV", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PRON", "VERB", "AUX", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "SYM", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PRON", "ADJ", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PUNCT", "DET", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "SYM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "SYM", "NUM", "VERB", "ADP", "NUM", "SCONJ", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADP", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "DET", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "PART", "AUX"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "AUX", "ADJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PRON", "VERB", "PART", "VERB"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "PUNCT", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "PART", "VERB", "PUNCT", "AUX", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "CCONJ", "AUX"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "SYM", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "PART", "VERB"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADV", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADV", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "PART", "VERB", "PUNCT", "AUX", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "VERB", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADJ", "SCONJ", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PART", "AUX", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PART", "AUX", "PROPN", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "DET", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "DET", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}]], "clean": ["read the good of new zealand a photo essay", "read thing to do in san miguel de allende travel guide and day itinerary", "read thing to do in florida besides hang out with mickey", "read good thing to do in oaxaca mexico", "read adventure at home traveler prove -pron- possible", "read travel more in last minute accommodation options idea", "read places -pron- never be and why -pron- want to go", "read cafe du monde a sugary treat in the french quarter", "read london for a hot second", "read reach new heights in napa hot air ballooning over the valley", "read scuba diving for the first time -pron- experience in santorini", "read good thing to do in athens greece", "read experience yosemite national park in one day flat", "read discover banana ketchup in lucia the secret taste of the caribbean", "read honduras good thing to see and do", "read city view from a seattle seaplane photo", "read where to stay in dublin ireland good places to stay", "read ten thing to do in sri lanka on the cheap", "read day in taipei the perfect taipei itinerary", "read the best long weekend trips from san francisco", "read good thing to do in hoi an in day a hoi an itinerary guide", "read the new york botanical gardens up close and personal", "read nine super awesome thing to do in nashville tn", "read day later and -pron- be marry a whole year", "read thing to do in havana cuba", "read where to stay in santorini top luxury boutique and budget hotels", "read airplane entertainment how to keep -pron- sane on long flight", "read first view of the negev a photo essay", "read days in mexico city the perfect mexico city itinerary", "read a two week vietnam itinerary a complete first timer guide", "read thing to do in malaysia se asia most overlooked country", "read way to cut cost on -pron- once in a lifetime trip to tahiti", "read blogge from a z april challenge one week til go time", "read masada the hike down on the never ending snake path", "read top summer festivals in europe music dancing and food", "read good thing to do in seville spain", "read the ultimate california coast road trip itinerary", "read how -pron- make blogge in while hold a full time job", "read y be for yolo and all those crazy stupid thing -pron- want to do", "read reason why -pron- should love san pedro belize", "read an epic canadian rockies itinerary from calgary to jasper and beyond", "read day in bangkok thailand a super comprehensive bangkok itinerary", "read the good thing to do in ljubljana slovenia", "read summer essentials for any warm weather trip", "read good thing to do in miami", "read good thing to do in prague czech republic", "read feelin a little artsy in the mission", "read get free travel by manage point and miles with awardwallet", "read where to go in march travel destination inspiration", "read day in barcelona a barcelona itinerary for the first time visitor", "read utah national parks road trip a spectacular one week in utah itinerary", "read day trips from reykjavik iceland day trips -pron- can miss", "read winter weekend getaways in the usa snowy and warm include", "read day in bali the perfect day bali itinerary for -pron- first visit", "read hour in atlanta ga", "read good day trips from naples italy", "read majestic monument valley a tour through the navajo tribal park", "read x be for x treme hike the toughest roughest muddiest in the world", "read thing to do in chicago what to see do eat enjoy", "read visit the san blas islands in panama an idyllic island escape", "read part time traveler talk with aaron cruz", "read thing to do in crater lake national park a perfect two day stay", "read an interview with a flight attendant", "read hour in naples italy", "read galapagos island good thing to see and do", "read parasaile in punta cana a birds eye view", "read the hotels of las vegas", "read thing to do in san francisco the ultimate san francisco bucket list", "read good thing to do in cape town", "read thing to do in budapest hungary", "read san francisco to seattle road trip a trip to the pacific northwest more", "read places to visit in tokyo tokyo bucket list inspiration", "read gorgeous greek beach -pron- can miss", "read how and why -pron- should splurge on first class airfare again again and again", "read the view from the window seat", "read hour in curacao what to see do and eat", "read stay connected while travel with vision global wifi", "read israel be incredible a journey through instagram", "read top way to enjoy -pron- las vegas experience in style", "read how to spend a long weekend in the poconos pa", "read a taste of barbados the good of the good", "read good thing to do in paris", "read b be for beaches -pron- favorite of the caribbean", "read butts balloons and beer the señor frog experience", "read thing to do in toronto in winter full guide to the city", "read k be for kauai and other possible travel plan for", "read part time traveler talk with megan hettwer", "read r be for rum cake the key to a happy crowd", "read how to have the best road trip ever", "read o be for old san juan puerto rico a colorful photo essay", "read why -pron- want to move to carmel by the sea california", "read good day trips from amsterdam where to go to get outta the city", "read cruising yay or nay the positive and the negatives", "read seven of seattle top tourist attractions", "read big change on the blog", "read good day trips from sofia bulgaria", "read for the wine lovers hotel vintage seattle", "read and the oscar go to", "read monterey and the mile drive", "read highlight from -pron- cross country road trip nyc to sf"]}