{"py/object": "data.Author", "author_id": "9ybweq2c9bw3whelacik3uxbnba9yj1i", "truth": 0, "tweets": ["A winter's tale for Alaska's Shakespeare fans #URL# #URL#", "A look at the films vying for best picture at the Academy Awards 2019 #URL# #URL#", "George Galloway radio show breached Ofcom rules #URL# #URL#", "SAG awards 2019: Black Panther wins top prize at SAG awards #URL# #URL#", "Parents' anger over Fortnite Live Norwich festival #URL# #URL#", "Forbes 30 Under 30: Letitia Wright and Tom Holland among UK names #URL# #URL#", "From Gormley to Rodin: The famous artworks hidden in plain sight #URL# #URL#", "Ozzy Osbourne cancels tour dates to recover from pneumonia #URL# #URL#", "Karl Lagerfeld: The life of a design icon in pictures #URL# #URL#", "Giving a voice to my friend’s songs #URL# #URL#", "Johnny Depp sues ex-wife Amber Heard over article #URL# #URL#", "National Gallery: NG27 group win workers' rights #URL# #URL#", "The soldier with a secret talent - ballet #URL# #URL#", "Banksy tribute to Bataclan terror victims stolen in Paris #URL# #URL#", "In pictures: Baftas 2019 red carpet glamour #URL# #URL#", "Michael Jackson accuser: 'Michael chose me' #URL# #URL#", "Pretty Woman musical is coming to London in 2020, Bryan Adams says #URL# #URL#", "Rajar figures: Greg James boosts Radio 1 breakfast audience by 230,000 #URL# #URL#", "Dick Miller, Gremlins and Terminator actor, dies aged 90 #URL# #URL#", "Ryan Adams: FBI investigates sexually-explicit texts #URL# #URL#", "Ryan Adams: Fans demand money back ahead of UK tour #URL# #URL#", "Oscars 2019: Nominated short tells of black teen who 'made friends with monsters' #URL# #URL#", "Hamilton leads with five wins at What's On Stage Awards #URL# #URL#", "Jeremy Hardy's comedy highlights #URL# #URL#", "Burberry sorry for 'suicide' hoodie with noose around neck #URL# #URL#", "John Malkovich: Weinstein play may 'upset' people #URL# #URL#", "What's happened since the #HASHTAG# controversy of 2015 #URL# #URL#", "BBC Licence fee set to rise by £4 in April #URL# #URL#", "Bafta Film Awards 2019: Highlights from the ceremony #URL# #URL#", "21 Savage: Rapper released on bond ahead of US deportation hearing #URL# #URL#", "A tale of two Merlins: Sir Patrick's wizard transformation #URL# #URL#", "Juliette Binoche says Harvey Weinstein has 'had enough' #URL# #URL#", "Paul McCartney awarded gold Blue Peter badge #URL# #URL#", "Oscars 2019 ceremony to go without host after row #URL# #URL#", "R Kelly: Singer charged with sexual abuse in Chicago #URL# #URL#", "Oscars 2019: All awards will be shown live after backlash #URL# #URL#", "Joe Sugg on Strictly gives YouTubers hope for TV success #URL# #URL#", "André Previn dies at the age of 89 #URL# #URL#", "Amy Shark: Stowaways found on singer's bus near UK border #URL# #URL#", "#HASHTAG# Oscars: Why aren't there more female directors? #URL# #URL#", "Rosamund Pike on playing the 'fierce' war reporter killed by the Syrian regime #URL# #URL#", "Oscars 2019: Spike Lee says Green Book 'not my cup of tea' #URL# #URL#", "Oscars 2019: What this short speech winner did with his jet ski #URL# #URL#", "Tessa Thompson and Brie Larson join calls for more women film directors #URL# #URL#", "Mr Greedy 'almost as hard to read' as Steinbeck classics #URL# #URL#", "Oscars 2019: Green Book best picture win proves divisive #URL# #URL#", "Trevor Noah sorry for India-Pakistan comments #URL# #URL#", "Glenn Close's Spirit Awards doggy date #URL# #URL#", "Jackson family say Michael's 'naivety was his downfall' #URL# #URL#", "Growing up with grime in Blackpool #URL# #URL#", "Selma Blair opens up about MS: 'People with disabilities are invisible' #URL# #URL#", "Desert Island Discs 'greatest radio show of all time' #URL# #URL#", "Bafta win for vegan farmer who gave away herd #URL# #URL#", "UK needs black culture museum, says architect Sir David Adjaye #URL# #URL#", "Oscars 2019: James Bulger film to remain in Oscars #URL# #URL#", "Maroon 5's Super Bowl show fails to catch fire #URL# #URL#", "Richard Hawley to co-write musical set in flats #URL# #URL#", "Baftas 2019: Stars descend on London for ceremony #URL# #URL#", "Only Fools and Horses: From Peckham to the West End #URL# #URL#", "US RnB singer-songwriter James Ingram dies aged 66 #URL# #URL#", "Man Booker loses £1.6m hedge fund sponsor amid talk of tension #URL# #URL#", "BBC and ITV set to launch Netflix rival #URL# #URL#", "Facebook and Google news should be regulated, report says #URL# #URL#", "Independent Spirit Awards: Beale Street wins big ahead of Oscars #URL# #URL#", "The other 'Oscars' – in Oscar week #URL# #URL#", "Superhero spin-offs and sequels dominate UK cinema top 10 #URL# #URL#", "Fleabag is back - and she's found religion #URL# #URL#", "Oscar-nominated film Capernaum, shows real people in Beirut #URL# #URL#", "Ryan Adams accused of sexual misconduct by several women #URL# #URL#", "Graham Norton and Alan Carr to judge RuPaul's Drag Race #URL# #URL#", "Hollywood hitmaker's fight for an Oscar #URL# #URL#", "TNT Boys: The teen tribute act captivating the Philippines #URL# #URL#", "George Orwell gets food essay apology from British Council after 70 years #URL# #URL#", "Love Sonia: Why Freida Pinto made a film about sex slaves #URL# #URL#", "Lily James in All About Eve: No more Goody One-Shoe #URL# #URL#", "Jamie Lee Curtis: Oscars changes are 'missteps, not chaos' #URL# #URL#", "Oscars 2019: Olivia Colman and Green Book spring surprise wins #URL# #URL#", "Why Vanessa Redgrave's new play is a family affair #URL# #URL#", "Lunar New Year: Meet 'the last' lion dance costume maker #URL# #URL#", "Children to study Doctor Who theme tune in BBC Ten Pieces #URL# #URL#", "Attacked Empire actor Jussie Smollett 'has tasted brutality of hatred' #URL# #URL#", "Fyre Festival: My front-row seat for the chaos in the Exumas #URL# #URL#", "PledgeMusic: The day the music died? #URL# #URL#", "'Why I broke silence surrounding my sister's suicide' #URL# #URL#", "Super Bowl half-time show controversy explained #URL# #URL#", "How Nina Nesbitt fought the pop machine and found herself #URL# #URL#", "Gruffalo artist Axel Scheffler's Zog transformed for the stage #URL# #URL#", "Fespaco nominee Mohamed Boureima : 'I can't handle watching my own films' #URL# #URL#", "How we made the effects on Solo: A Star Wars Story #URL# #URL#", "Ariana Grande hits back after Pride backlash #URL# #URL#", "John Humphrys to leave Today later in 2019 #URL# #URL#", "Oscars 2019: Roma's success shows there's more to movies than Hollywood #URL# #URL#", "Boy George: The things I've learned #URL# #URL#", "Long-nosed lover Cyrano returns to woo Paris in hit play Edmond #URL# #URL#", "Julie Adams: Creature from the Black Lagoon star dies #URL# #URL#", "Yalitza Aparicio: Oscars 'an opportunity to break through stereotypes' #URL# #URL#", "Spike Lee on Liam Neeson racism row: 'It's bad all around' #URL# #URL#", "How Sesame Street charmed US then the world #URL# #URL#", "Venezuela crisis: Univision team 'briefly detained' after Maduro interview #URL# #URL#", "RT #USER#: Manila tries to fix its notorious traffic — bad news for jeepneys and trolley boys #URL# #URL#…"], "ents": [[{"py/tuple": ["winter", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Alaska", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Shakespeare", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["the Academy Awards 2019", "FAC"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["George Galloway", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Ofcom", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["2019", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Black Panther", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["SAG", "ORG"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["30", "CARDINAL"]}, {"py/tuple": ["30", "CARDINAL"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Letitia Wright", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Tom Holland", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["UK", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Gormley", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Rodin", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Ozzy Osbourne", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Karl Lagerfeld", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Johnny Depp", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Amber Heard", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["National Gallery: NG27", "ORG"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Banksy", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Bataclan", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Paris", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Baftas 2019", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Michael Jackson", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Michael", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Pretty Woman", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["London", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["2020", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Bryan Adams", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Greg James", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Radio 1", "LAW"]}, {"py/tuple": ["230,000", "CARDINAL"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Dick Miller", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Gremlins", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Terminator", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["90", "CARDINAL"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Ryan Adams", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["FBI", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Ryan Adams", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["UK", "GPE"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Hamilton", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["five", "CARDINAL"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Jeremy Hardy's", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Burberry", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["John Malkovich", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Weinstein", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["2015", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["BBC Licence", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["4", "MONEY"]}, {"py/tuple": ["April", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Bafta", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Awards 2019", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["21", "CARDINAL"]}, {"py/tuple": ["US", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["two", "CARDINAL"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Merlins", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Patrick", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Juliette Binoche", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Harvey Weinstein", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Paul McCartney", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Blue Peter", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["2019", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Chicago", "GPE"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Joe Sugg", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["André Previn", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["the age of 89", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Amy Shark", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["UK", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Oscars", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Syrian", "NORP"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Oscars 2019", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Spike Lee", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Green Book '", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Tessa Thompson", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Brie Larson", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Greedy", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Steinbeck", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Green Book", "WORK_OF_ART"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Trevor Noah", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["India", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Pakistan", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Glenn Close's", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Jackson", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Michael", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Blackpool", "GPE"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Desert Island Discs '", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Bafta", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["UK", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["David Adjaye", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Oscars 2019", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["James Bulger", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Oscars", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Maroon 5's", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Super Bowl", "EVENT"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Richard Hawley", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["2019", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["London", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Fools", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Horses", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Peckham", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["the West End", "LOC"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["US RnB", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["James Ingram", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["66", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Man Booker", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["£1.6m", "MONEY"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["BBC", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["ITV", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Netflix", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Google", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Beale Street", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Oscars", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Oscars", "WORK_OF_ART"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Oscar week", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["UK", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["10", "CARDINAL"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Capernaum", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Beirut", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Ryan Adams", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Graham Norton", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Alan Carr", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["RuPaul", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Hollywood", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Oscar", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["TNT", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Philippines", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["George Orwell", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["British Council", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["70 years", "DATE"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Lily James", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Goody", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Jamie Lee Curtis", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Oscars 2019", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Olivia Colman", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Green Book spring surprise", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Vanessa Redgrave's", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Lunar New Year", "EVENT"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Jussie Smollett", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Fyre Festival", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["The day", "DATE"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Super Bowl", "EVENT"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Nina Nesbitt", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Axel Scheffler's", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Zog", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Fespaco", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Mohamed Boureima", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Ariana Grande", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["John Humphrys", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Today", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["2019", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Oscars 2019", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Roma", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Hollywood", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Boy George", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Cyrano", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Paris", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Edmond", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Julie Adams", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Black Lagoon", "FAC"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Yalitza Aparicio", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Spike Lee", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Liam Neeson", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Sesame Street", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["US", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Venezuela", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Univision", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Maduro", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Manila", "GPE"]}]], "POS_tags": [[{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NUM", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "PRON", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "PROPN", "ADJ", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADJ", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADV", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADV", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PRON", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PART", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "PRON", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "AUX", "VERB", "SCONJ", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "SYM", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "PUNCT", "AUX", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "AUX", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADV", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["SPACE", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "AUX", "PART", "ADV", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "INTJ", "ADP", "VERB", "DET", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PART", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PRON", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADV", "ADJ", "PART", "VERB", "PUNCT", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADJ", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADJ", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "AUX", "DET", "NOUN", "PART", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "ADP", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NUM", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "SYM", "NUM", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "AUX", "VERB", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADV", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADJ", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "ADV", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PRON", "AUX", "VERB", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "AUX", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PART", "VERB", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "NOUN", "AUX", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "PRON", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "AUX", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "PRON", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADP", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "VERB", "PRON", "AUX", "ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "PRON", "AUX", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "DET", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PART", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["INTJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PRON", "AUX", "ADJ", "ADV", "ADV", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADV", "DET", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["SPACE", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PUNCT"]}]], "clean": ["a winter tale for alaska shakespeare fan", "a look at the film vie for good picture at the academy awards", "george galloway radio show breach ofcom rule", "sag award black panther win top prize at sag award", "parent anger over fortnite live norwich festival", "forbes under letitia wright and tom holland among uk name", "from gormley to rodin the famous artwork hide in plain sight", "ozzy osbourne cancel tour date to recover from pneumonia", "karl lagerfeld the life of a design icon in picture", "give a voice to -pron- friend song", "johnny depp sue ex wife amber heard over article", "national gallery group win worker right", "the soldier with a secret talent ballet", "banksy tribute to bataclan terror victim steal in paris", "in picture baftas red carpet glamour", "michael jackson accuser michael choose -pron-", "pretty woman musical be come to london in bryan adams say", "rajar figure greg james boost radio breakfast audience by", "dick miller gremlins and terminator actor die aged", "ryan adams fbi investigate sexually explicit text", "ryan adams fan demand money back ahead of uk tour", "oscar nominate short tell of black teen who make friend with monster", "hamilton lead with five win at what on stage awards", "jeremy hardy comedy highlight", "burberry sorry for suicide hoodie with noose around neck", "john malkovich weinstein play may upset people", "what happen since the controversy of", "bbc licence fee set to rise by in april", "bafta film awards highlight from the ceremony", "savage rapper release on bond ahead of us deportation hearing", "a tale of two merlins sir patrick wizard transformation", "juliette binoche say harvey weinstein have have enough", "paul mccartney award gold blue peter badge", "oscars ceremony to go without host after row", "r kelly singer charge with sexual abuse in chicago", "oscar all award will be show live after backlash", "joe sugg on strictly give youtuber hope for tv success", "andré previn die at the age of", "amy shark stowaway find on singer bus near uk border", "oscars why be there more female director", "rosamund pike on play the fierce war reporter kill by the syrian regime", "oscar spike lee say green book not -pron- cup of tea", "oscar what this short speech winner do with -pron- jet ski", "tessa thompson and brie larson join call for more woman film director", "mr greedy almost as hard to read as steinbeck classic", "oscar green book good picture win prove divisive", "trevor noah sorry for india pakistan comment", "glenn close spirit awards doggy date", "jackson family say michael naivety be -pron- downfall", "grow up with grime in blackpool", "selma blair open up about ms people with disability be invisible", "desert island discs great radio show of all time", "bafta win for vegan farmer who give away herd", "uk need black culture museum say architect sir david adjaye", "oscar james bulger film to remain in oscars", "maroon super bowl show fail to catch fire", "richard hawley to co write musical set in flat", "baftas star descend on london for ceremony", "only fools and horse from peckham to the west end", "us rnb singer songwriter james ingram die aged", "man booker lose m hedge fund sponsor amid talk of tension", "bbc and itv set to launch netflix rival", "facebook and google news should be regulate report say", "independent spirit awards beale street win big ahead of oscars", "the other oscars in oscar week", "superhero spin off and sequel dominate uk cinema top", "fleabag be back and -pron- find religion", "oscar nominate film capernaum show real people in beirut", "ryan adams accuse of sexual misconduct by several woman", "graham norton and alan carr to judge rupaul drag race", "hollywood hitmaker fight for an oscar", "tnt boys the teen tribute act captivate the philippines", "george orwell get food essay apology from british council after year", "love sonia why freida pinto make a film about sex slave", "lily james in all about eve no more goody one shoe", "jamie lee curtis oscar change be misstep not chaos", "oscar olivia colman and green book spring surprise win", "why vanessa redgrave new play be a family affair", "lunar new year meet the last lion dance costume maker", "child to study doctor who theme tune in bbc ten pieces", "attacked empire actor jussie smollett have taste brutality of hatred", "fyre festival -pron- front row seat for the chaos in the exumas", "pledgemusic the day the music die", "why -pron- break silence surround -pron- sister suicide", "super bowl half time show controversy explain", "how nina nesbitt fight the pop machine and find -pron-", "gruffalo artist axel scheffler zog transform for the stage", "fespaco nominee mohamed boureima -pron- can handle watch -pron- own film", "how -pron- make the effect on solo a star wars story", "ariana grande hit back after pride backlash", "john humphrys to leave today later in", "oscar roma success show there more to movie than hollywood", "boy george the thing -pron- learn", "long nosed lover cyrano return to woo paris in hit play edmond", "julie adams creature from the black lagoon star die", "yalitza aparicio oscars an opportunity to break through stereotype", "spike lee on liam neeson racism row -pron- bad all around", "how sesame street charm us then the world", "venezuela crisis univision team briefly detain after maduro interview", "user manila try to fix -pron- notorious traffic bad news for jeepney and trolley boy"]}