{"py/object": "data.Author", "author_id": "ceojvjjthre8av5nkgmw7ei4sdcwmc20", "truth": 1, "tweets": ["The breakup phone cleanse: How we move on in a digital world #URL#", "'Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery' let's you live your Hogwarts dreams #URL#", "Amazon is giving Alexa a kid-friendly personality #URL#", "Get an Instant Pot on sale for just $56, which is a *great* deal #URL#", "OnePlus 6 will be unveiled in all of its glory on May 16 #URL#", "Amazon is giving Alexa a kid-friendly personality #URL#", "Mercedes-Maybach concept car is electric, ultra-luxurious, and ready for tea time #URL#", "Save $100 on an iPad mini 4 at Walmart #URL#", "How to get your hands on 'God of War' and limited edition merchandise #URL#", "This robot pizza company's delivery trucks can now bake 120 pizzas per hour #URL#", "'Black Mirror' has taken a part of London into the 1980s #URL#", "Student artist installs 'cry closet' at university library #URL#", "Referee apologises for missing handball, instantly becomes meme #URL#", "Referee apologises for missing handball, instantly becomes meme #URL#", "Watch space dust shoot around a comet as it tumbles through our solar system #URL#", "It's National DNA Day, which means AncestryDNA, 23andMe, Living DNA, and more are on sale #URL#", "You might enjoy 'Infinity War' more if you're not a hardcore Marvel fan #URL#", "How to get your hands on 'God of War' and limited edition merchandise #URL#", "'Coco' and more of what's coming to Netflix in May #URL#", "All the very weird stuff you need to start an 'oddly satisfying' Instagram account #URL#", "This robot pizza company's delivery trucks can now bake 120 pizzas per hour #URL#", "Listen up: Lots of Bose headphones are currently on sale #URL#", "People are horny as hell for the new 'Venom' trailer #URL#", "Listen up: Lots of Bose headphones are currently on sale #URL#", "5 easy ways to clean your tech products #URL#", "Highly resourceful woman has the wildest birth story of all time #URL#", "Here's why the alt-right loves Kanye West #URL#", "Watch space dust shoot around a comet as it tumbles through our solar system #URL#", "It's National DNA Day, which means AncestryDNA, 23andMe, Living DNA, and more are on sale #URL#", "The Ultimate Lego Millennium Falcon is back in stock for Amazon Prime members only #URL#", "'Simpsons' actor Hank Azaria said he's ready to step aside as Apu #URL#", "Google gun emoji becomes water pistol #URL#", "Why does everyone who's ever ghosted me still watch my Instagram Stories? #URL#", "This robot pizza company's delivery trucks can now bake 120 pizzas per hour #URL#", "Here&amp;#HASHTAG#;s why you&amp;#HASHTAG#;re getting all those terms of service update emails #URL#", "Mercedes-Maybach concept car is electric, ultra-luxurious, and ready for tea time #URL#", "Referee apologises for missing handball, instantly becomes meme #URL#", "2-year-old drummer is way, way too good at his instrument #URL#", "'Coco' and more of what's coming to Netflix in May #URL#", "Mark Ruffalo shares the time Disney yelled at him for 'Thor: Ragnarok' spoilers #URL#", "Everyone (except Microsoft) is using the water pistol emoji now #URL#", "Amazon is giving Alexa a kid-friendly personality #URL#", "Google's big Gmail update makes your inbox smarter and more secure #URL#", "Google's big Gmail update makes your inbox smarter and more secure #URL#", "WhatsApp is banning teens under 16 in Europe ahead of privacy law changes #URL#", "People are horny as hell for the new 'Venom' trailer #URL#", "5 easy ways to clean your tech products #URL#", "For your entertainment, a long list of the funniest yearbook quotes #URL#", "The breakup phone cleanse: How we move on in a digital world #URL#", "'Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery' let's you live your Hogwarts dreams #URL#", "The 'big story coming' tweets need to end #URL#", "For your entertainment, a long list of the funniest yearbook quotes #URL#", "OnePlus 6 will be unveiled in all of its glory on May 16 #URL#", "The 'big story coming' tweets need to end #URL#", "It's National DNA Day, which means AncestryDNA, 23andMe, Living DNA, and more are on sale #URL#", "Here&amp;#HASHTAG#;s why you&amp;#HASHTAG#;re getting all those terms of service update emails #URL#", "The breakup phone cleanse: How we move on in a digital world #URL#", "Fancy a French farm for free? #URL#", "How to get your hands on 'God of War' and limited edition merchandise #URL#", "Mark Ruffalo shares the time Disney yelled at him for 'Thor: Ragnarok' spoilers #URL#", "Pets with human names deserve their time to shine #URL#", "Congrats to Ben Platt on joining John Krasinski and Emily Blunt's marriage #URL#", "Subscription service Setapp is aiming to become the Netflix for Mac apps #URL#", "John Travolta is unrecognizable as stalker in Fred Durst movie 'Moose' #URL#", "Here's why the alt-right loves Kanye West #URL#", "Amazon daily deals for Wednesday, April 25: Instant Pots, Bose headphones, AncestryDNA kits… #URL#", "Here's why the alt-right loves Kanye West #URL#", "Mark Ruffalo shares the time Disney yelled at him for 'Thor: Ragnarok' spoilers #URL#", "'Black Mirror' has taken a part of London into the 1980s #URL#", "9 drunk shopping purchases that you'll feel good about in the morning #URL#", "Galileo: UK plan to launch rival to EU sat-nav system #URL#", "WhatsApp is banning teens under 16 in Europe ahead of privacy law changes #URL#", "BuzzFeed partners with Netflix for documentary series #URL#", "Google's big Gmail update makes your inbox smarter and more secure #URL#", "'Coco' and more of what's coming to Netflix in May #URL#", "2-year-old drummer is way, way too good at his instrument #URL#", "Watch space dust shoot around a comet as it tumbles through our solar system #URL#", "The 'big story coming' tweets need to end #URL#", "Here&amp;#HASHTAG#;s why you&amp;#HASHTAG#;re getting all those terms of service update emails #URL#", "All the very weird stuff you need to start an 'oddly satisfying' Instagram account #URL#", "Google's Gmail gets self-destruct option ahead of GDPR #URL#", "TSB is 'up and running' - for some #URL#", "You might enjoy 'Infinity War' more if you're not a hardcore Marvel fan #URL#", "Tensions are rising in 'Dear White People' Volume 2 trailer #URL#", "9 drunk shopping purchases that you'll feel good about in the morning #URL#", "'Black Mirror' has taken a part of London into the 1980s #URL#", "9 drunk shopping purchases that you'll feel good about in the morning #URL#", "Everyone (except Microsoft) is using the water pistol emoji now #URL#", "The Ultimate Lego Millennium Falcon is back in stock for Amazon Prime members only #URL#", "Save $100 on an iPad mini 4 at Walmart #URL#", "'Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery' let's you live your Hogwarts dreams #URL#", "Amazon Alexa to reward kids who say: 'Please' #URL#", "Congrats to Ben Platt on joining John Krasinski and Emily Blunt's marriage #URL#", "Amazon daily deals for Wednesday, April 25: Instant Pots, Bose headphones, AncestryDNA kits… #URL#", "For your entertainment, a long list of the funniest yearbook quotes #URL#", "WhatsApp is banning teens under 16 in Europe ahead of privacy law changes #URL#", "5 easy ways to clean your tech products #URL#", "Mercedes-Maybach concept car is electric, ultra-luxurious, and ready for tea time #URL#", "'Avengers: Infinity War' cast play a hilariously awkward guessing game #URL#", "Pets with human names deserve their time to shine #URL#"], "ents": [[], [["Harry Potter", "PERSON"], ["Hogwarts Mystery", "PERSON"], ["Hogwarts", "PERSON"]], [["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Alexa", "ORG"]], [["just $56", "MONEY"]], [["OnePlus 6", "PERSON"], ["May 16", "DATE"]], [["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Alexa", "ORG"]], [["Mercedes", "ORG"]], [["100", "MONEY"], ["4", "CARDINAL"], ["Walmart", "FAC"]], [], [["120", "CARDINAL"]], [["Black Mirror'", "ORG"], ["London", "GPE"], ["the 1980s", "DATE"]], [], [], [], [], [], [["Infinity War'", "EVENT"], ["Marvel", "ORG"]], [], [["Coco", "ORG"], ["Netflix", "ORG"], ["May", "DATE"]], [["Instagram", "ORG"]], [["120", "CARDINAL"]], [], [["Venom", "PRODUCT"]], [], [["5", "CARDINAL"]], [], [["Kanye West", "GPE"]], [], [], [["The Ultimate Lego Millennium Falcon", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"]], [["Simpsons", "PERSON"], ["Hank Azaria", "PERSON"], ["Apu", "PERSON"]], [["Google", "ORG"]], [["Instagram Stories", "ORG"]], [["120", "CARDINAL"]], [["you;;re", "PERSON"]], [["Mercedes", "ORG"]], [], [], [["Coco", "ORG"], ["Netflix", "ORG"], ["May", "DATE"]], [["Mark Ruffalo", "PERSON"], ["Disney", "ORG"], ["Thor", "PERSON"], ["Ragnarok", "PERSON"]], [["Microsoft", "ORG"]], [["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Alexa", "ORG"]], [["Google", "ORG"], ["Gmail", "ORG"]], [["Google", "ORG"], ["Gmail", "ORG"]], [["WhatsApp", "ORG"], ["under 16", "DATE"], ["Europe", "LOC"]], [["Venom", "PRODUCT"]], [["5", "CARDINAL"]], [], [], [["Harry Potter", "PERSON"], ["Hogwarts Mystery", "PERSON"], ["Hogwarts", "PERSON"]], [], [], [["OnePlus 6", "PERSON"], ["May 16", "DATE"]], [], [], [["you;;re", "PERSON"]], [], [["French", "NORP"]], [], [["Mark Ruffalo", "PERSON"], ["Disney", "ORG"], ["Thor", "PERSON"], ["Ragnarok", "PERSON"]], [], [["Ben Platt", "PERSON"], ["John Krasinski", "PERSON"], ["Emily Blunt's", "PERSON"]], [["Setapp", "ORG"], ["Netflix", "PRODUCT"], ["Mac", "ORG"]], [["John Travolta", "PERSON"], ["Fred Durst", "PERSON"], ["Moose", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Kanye West", "GPE"]], [["Amazon", "ORG"], ["daily", "DATE"], ["Wednesday, April 25", "DATE"], ["Bose", "ORG"]], [["Kanye West", "GPE"]], [["Mark Ruffalo", "PERSON"], ["Disney", "ORG"], ["Thor", "PERSON"], ["Ragnarok", "PERSON"]], [["Black Mirror'", "ORG"], ["London", "GPE"], ["the 1980s", "DATE"]], [["9", "CARDINAL"]], [["Galileo", "PRODUCT"], ["UK", "GPE"], ["EU", "ORG"]], [["WhatsApp", "ORG"], ["under 16", "DATE"], ["Europe", "LOC"]], [["Netflix", "ORG"]], [["Google", "ORG"], ["Gmail", "ORG"]], [["Coco", "ORG"], ["Netflix", "ORG"], ["May", "DATE"]], [], [], [], [["you;;re", "PERSON"]], [["Instagram", "ORG"]], [["Google", "ORG"], ["Gmail", "PRODUCT"], ["GDPR", "ORG"]], [["TSB", "ORG"]], [["Infinity War'", "EVENT"], ["Marvel", "ORG"]], [], [["9", "CARDINAL"]], [["Black Mirror'", "ORG"], ["London", "GPE"], ["the 1980s", "DATE"]], [["9", "CARDINAL"]], [["Microsoft", "ORG"]], [["The Ultimate Lego Millennium Falcon", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"]], [["100", "MONEY"], ["4", "CARDINAL"], ["Walmart", "FAC"]], [["Harry Potter", "PERSON"], ["Hogwarts Mystery", "PERSON"], ["Hogwarts", "PERSON"]], [["Amazon Alexa", "PERSON"]], [["Ben Platt", "PERSON"], ["John Krasinski", "PERSON"], ["Emily Blunt's", "PERSON"]], [["Amazon", "ORG"], ["daily", "DATE"], ["Wednesday, April 25", "DATE"], ["Bose", "ORG"]], [], [["WhatsApp", "ORG"], ["under 16", "DATE"], ["Europe", "LOC"]], [["5", "CARDINAL"]], [["Mercedes", "ORG"]], [["Infinity War'", "EVENT"]], []], "POS_tags": [[{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PRON", "PRON", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "PROPN", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["AUX", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADV", "SYM", "NUM", "PUNCT", "DET", "AUX", "DET", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NUM", "VERB", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "PROPN", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "ADJ", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "SYM", "NUM", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "AUX", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "VERB", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "AUX", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "VERB", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "VERB", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "AUX", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "AUX", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "SCONJ", "PRON", "AUX", "PART", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "AUX", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "ADP", "PRON", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "DET", "ADV", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "VERB", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "AUX", "ADJ", "SCONJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "ADJ", "NOUN", "AUX", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "AUX", "ADV", "DET", "NOUN", "ADJ", "ADJ", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "AUX", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "AUX", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PRON", "AUX", "ADJ", "PART", "VERB", "ADV", "SCONJ", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "AUX", "PRON", "PRON", "AUX", "ADV", "VERB", "PRON", "ADV", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "VERB", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADV", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "ADJ", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "VERB", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "AUX", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADV", "ADJ", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "ADP", "PRON", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PRON", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "PUNCT", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "AUX", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "PROPN", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "ADV", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "ADV", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "AUX", "ADJ", "SCONJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PRON", "PRON", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NUM", "VERB", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "AUX", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "AUX", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADV", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "AUX", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PRON", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADJ", "SCONJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "AUX", "ADV", "DET", "NOUN", "ADJ", "ADJ", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "AUX", "ADV", "DET", "NOUN", "ADJ", "ADJ", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PRON", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "AUX", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "DET", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "VERB", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "ADV", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "ADP", "PRON", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "AUX", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADV", "ADJ", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADV", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "DET", "ADV", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "PUNCT", "ADP", "CCONJ", "VERB", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "ADP", "DET"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "SCONJ", "PRON", "AUX", "PART", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "NUM", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "DET", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "AUX", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "DET", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "PUNCT", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "AUX", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "SYM", "NUM", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PRON", "PRON", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "INTJ", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "ADJ", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "ADV", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB"]}]], "clean": ["the breakup phone cleanse how -pron- move on in a digital world", "harry potter hogwarts mystery let -pron- live -pron- hogwarts dream", "amazon be give alexa a kid friendly personality", "get an instant pot on sale for just which be a great deal", "oneplus will be unveil in all of -pron- glory on may", "amazon be give alexa a kid friendly personality", "mercedes maybach concept car be electric ultra luxurious and ready for tea time", "save on an ipad mini at walmart", "how to get -pron- hand on god of war and limited edition merchandise", "this robot pizza company delivery truck can now bake pizza per hour", "black mirror have take a part of london into the", "student artist install cry closet at university library", "referee apologise for miss handball instantly become meme", "referee apologise for miss handball instantly become meme", "watch space dust shoot around a comet as -pron- tumble through -pron- solar system", "-pron- national dna day which mean ancestrydna living dna and more be on sale", "-pron- may enjoy infinity war more if -pron- not a hardcore marvel fan", "how to get -pron- hand on god of war and limited edition merchandise", "coco and more of what come to netflix in may", "all the very weird stuff -pron- need to start an oddly satisfying instagram account", "this robot pizza company delivery truck can now bake pizza per hour", "listen up lot of bose headphone be currently on sale", "people be horny as hell for the new venom trailer", "listen up lot of bose headphone be currently on sale", "easy way to clean -pron- tech product", "highly resourceful woman have the wild birth story of all time", "here why the alt right love kanye west", "watch space dust shoot around a comet as -pron- tumble through -pron- solar system", "-pron- national dna day which mean ancestrydna living dna and more be on sale", "the ultimate lego millennium falcon be back in stock for amazon prime member only", "simpson actor hank azaria say -pron- ready to step aside as apu", "google gun emoji become water pistol", "why do everyone who ever ghost -pron- still watch -pron- instagram stories", "this robot pizza company delivery truck can now bake pizza per hour", "why get all those term of service update email", "mercedes maybach concept car be electric ultra luxurious and ready for tea time", "referee apologise for miss handball instantly become meme", "old drummer be way way too good at -pron- instrument", "coco and more of what come to netflix in may", "mark ruffalo share the time disney yell at -pron- for thor ragnarok spoiler", "everyone except microsoft be use the water pistol emoji now", "amazon be give alexa a kid friendly personality", "google big gmail update make -pron- inbox smart and more secure", "google big gmail update make -pron- inbox smart and more secure", "whatsapp be ban teen under in europe ahead of privacy law change", "people be horny as hell for the new venom trailer", "easy way to clean -pron- tech product", "for -pron- entertainment a long list of the funniest yearbook quote", "the breakup phone cleanse how -pron- move on in a digital world", "harry potter hogwarts mystery let -pron- live -pron- hogwarts dream", "the big story come tweet need to end", "for -pron- entertainment a long list of the funniest yearbook quote", "oneplus will be unveil in all of -pron- glory on may", "the big story come tweet need to end", "-pron- national dna day which mean ancestrydna living dna and more be on sale", "why get all those term of service update email", "the breakup phone cleanse how -pron- move on in a digital world", "fancy a french farm for free", "how to get -pron- hand on god of war and limited edition merchandise", "mark ruffalo share the time disney yell at -pron- for thor ragnarok spoiler", "pet with human name deserve -pron- time to shine", "congrat to ben platt on join john krasinski and emily blunt marriage", "subscription service setapp be aim to become the netflix for mac app", "john travolta be unrecognizable as stalker in fred durst movie moose", "here why the alt right love kanye west", "amazon daily deal for wednesday april instant pot bose headphone ancestrydna kit", "here why the alt right love kanye west", "mark ruffalo share the time disney yell at -pron- for thor ragnarok spoiler", "black mirror have take a part of london into the", "drunk shopping purchase that -pron- feel good about in the morning", "galileo uk plan to launch rival to eu sit nav system", "whatsapp be ban teen under in europe ahead of privacy law change", "buzzfeed partner with netflix for documentary series", "google big gmail update make -pron- inbox smart and more secure", "coco and more of what come to netflix in may", "old drummer be way way too good at -pron- instrument", "watch space dust shoot around a comet as -pron- tumble through -pron- solar system", "the big story come tweet need to end", "why get all those term of service update email", "all the very weird stuff -pron- need to start an oddly satisfying instagram account", "google gmail get self destruct option ahead of gdpr", "tsb be up and run for some", "-pron- may enjoy infinity war more if -pron- not a hardcore marvel fan", "tension be rise in dear white people volume trailer", "drunk shopping purchase that -pron- feel good about in the morning", "black mirror have take a part of london into the", "drunk shopping purchase that -pron- feel good about in the morning", "everyone except microsoft be use the water pistol emoji now", "the ultimate lego millennium falcon be back in stock for amazon prime member only", "save on an ipad mini at walmart", "harry potter hogwarts mystery let -pron- live -pron- hogwarts dream", "amazon alexa to reward kid who say please", "congrat to ben platt on join john krasinski and emily blunt marriage", "amazon daily deal for wednesday april instant pot bose headphone ancestrydna kit", "for -pron- entertainment a long list of the funniest yearbook quote", "whatsapp be ban teen under in europe ahead of privacy law change", "easy way to clean -pron- tech product", "mercedes maybach concept car be electric ultra luxurious and ready for tea time", "avenger infinity war cast play a hilariously awkward guessing game", "pet with human name deserve -pron- time to shine"]}