{"py/object": "data.Author", "author_id": "d8y3v2kh07gdtlym8k8yjorulc6gua92", "truth": 0, "tweets": ["How To Draw Anime Shirts Ann Arbor #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie In 5 Easy Steps Modesto #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Number Dog Salt Lake City #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog 5553 Rochester #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog W The Word Dog Norman #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Art Hub Athens #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Wedding Lexington #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Realistic Dog Worcester #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A 4 Fold Stock Tie Montgomery #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Complex Richmond #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime Step By Step Easy Lowell #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie 101 Greensboro #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime Wolf Boy Paterson #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime Jawlines Phoenix #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Golden Retriever Anchorage #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Visual Lafayette #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime Girl Thousand Oaks #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Half Windsor Daly City #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog House Step By Step Escondido #URL# #URL#", "5 Steps To Draw A Dog San Bernardino #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Wedding Centennial #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog With 6 Circles Naperville #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog German Shepherd Gainesville #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Video Half Windsor Grand Rapids #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Quilt Tyler #URL# #URL#", "8 Ways To Tie A Tie Oakland #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Donut Evansville #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie With A Dimple Huntsville #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog With Sunglasses Lafayette #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime Running Ann Arbor #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Beginner Brownsville #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Harry Potter Peoria #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Anime Character Kansas City #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime In 5 Minutes Indianapolis #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Video Mirror View Frisco #URL# #URL#", "How to Draw a Cute Kawaii / Chibi Elephant Holding a Pig Balloon Easy Steps Drawing Lesson for Kids… #URL#", "How2 Tie A Tie Annoying Orange Chula Vista #URL# #URL#", "W To Tie A Bow Tie Austin #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Vampire Dog Detroit #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime Dragon Greensboro #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime Faces Antioch #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Out Of A 5 West Valley City #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime Kissing Antioch #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Very Easy Santa Clara #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog That Is Cute Costa Mesa #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie In 8 Seconds Aurora #URL# #URL#", "How 2 Draw Dog Face Athens #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie 2019 Corpus Christi #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie 4 Ways Little Rock #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog House Step By Step Buffalo #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Picture Steps Lakewood #URL# #URL#", "How 2 Tie A Tie Knot Fresno #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Doing The Dab Berkeley #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Harry Potter Sioux Falls #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie A Shoe Tempe #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie 3 Steps Worcester #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime On Ipad Davenport #URL# #URL#", "Audi’s E-Tron becomes first electric car to win top safety award #URL# #URL#", "How 2 Draw Anime Cat Girl Stockton #URL# #URL#", "Youtube How To Tie A Tie Fairfield #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime Pants Springfield #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Narrated Step By Step Torrance #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Right Handed Buffalo #URL# #URL#", "How 2 Tie A Tie Cambridge #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Mouth Henderson #URL# #URL#", "7 Ways To Tie A Tie Chicago #URL# #URL#", "How to Draw a Cute Cuddle Team Leader from Fortnite #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Up Shirt Akron #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Complex San Jose #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Yorkie Las Cruces #URL# #URL#", "5 New Ways To Tie A Tie Wilmington #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog That Looks Real Midland #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie A Full Windsor Knot Akron #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Gentleman Irvine #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Colored Pencils Salt Lake City #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog That Looks Real West Valley City #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Art Ala Carte New Haven #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Narrow Knot Aurora #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime Smile Wichita #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Using The Word Dog Clovis #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog With Circles Pasadena #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Cartoon Dog Youtube Montgomery #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Cartoon Dog Video Hillsboro #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog And Cat Step By Step Carrollton #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Kid Sandy Springs #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Real Easy Allentown #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie In 2 Minutes Sunnyvale #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime Profile Atlanta #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie 30 Ways Temecula #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie To A Bow Tie Cambridge #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Collar Renton #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw The Zodiac Dog Midland #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie A Bandana Fairfield #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Quick Brownsville #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Tie Rose Knot Vancouver #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog Tail Oxnard #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A Bow Tie H&amp;m Syracuse #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw A Dog From Behind Boulder #URL# #URL#", "How To Tie A 2 Half Hitch Lexington #URL# #URL#", "How To Draw Anime People San Jose #URL# #URL#"], "ents": [[], [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["Modesto", "GPE"]], [], [], [["Norman  ", "PERSON"]], [["Athens", "GPE"]], [["Lexington", "GPE"]], [], [], [["Richmond", "GPE"]], [["Lowell  ", "PERSON"]], [["101", "CARDINAL"], ["Greensboro", "GPE"]], [["Paterson  ", "PERSON"]], [["Phoenix", "GPE"]], [["Anchorage", "GPE"]], [["Lafayette", "GPE"]], [], [], [["Escondido", "GPE"]], [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["Bernardino", "GPE"]], [], [["Naperville", "GPE"]], [["Gainesville", "GPE"]], [], [["Tyler  ", "PERSON"]], [["8", "CARDINAL"], ["Oakland", "GPE"]], [["Evansville", "GPE"]], [["Huntsville", "GPE"]], [["Lafayette", "GPE"]], [], [["Brownsville", "GPE"]], [["Peoria", "GPE"]], [["Kansas", "GPE"]], [["5 Minutes", "TIME"], ["Indianapolis", "GPE"]], [["Frisco", "GPE"]], [], [["How2 Tie", "PERSON"], ["Chula", "PERSON"], ["Vista", "ORG"]], [["Austin  ", "PERSON"]], [["Detroit", "GPE"]], [["Greensboro", "GPE"]], [["Antioch", "GPE"]], [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["West Valley", "LOC"]], [["Antioch", "GPE"]], [["Clara", "GPE"]], [["Mesa  ", "PERSON"]], [["8 Seconds", "TIME"], ["Aurora  ", "PERSON"]], [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Athens", "GPE"]], [["Christi", "GPE"]], [], [["Buffalo", "GPE"]], [["Lakewood", "GPE"]], [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Fresno", "GPE"]], [["Berkeley", "GPE"]], [], [["Tempe", "GPE"]], [["Worcester  ", "PERSON"]], [], [["Audi", "ORG"], ["E-Tron", "PRODUCT"], ["first", "ORDINAL"]], [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Stockton", "GPE"]], [["Youtube How To Tie A Tie", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Fairfield", "GPE"]], [["Springfield", "GPE"]], [["Torrance", "GPE"]], [["Buffalo", "GPE"]], [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Cambridge", "GPE"]], [["Henderson", "GPE"]], [["7", "CARDINAL"], ["Chicago", "GPE"]], [["Fortnite  ", "PERSON"]], [["Akron", "GPE"]], [["Jose  ", "PERSON"]], [["Cruces", "GPE"]], [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["Wilmington  ", "PERSON"]], [["Midland", "GPE"]], [["Akron", "GPE"]], [["Irvine  ", "PERSON"]], [], [], [], [], [["Wichita", "GPE"]], [["Clovis", "GPE"]], [["Pasadena", "GPE"]], [], [["Hillsboro", "GPE"]], [["Carrollton", "GPE"]], [], [], [["2 Minutes", "TIME"], ["Sunnyvale", "GPE"]], [["Atlanta", "GPE"]], [["30", "CARDINAL"], ["Temecula", "GPE"]], [["Cambridge", "GPE"]], [["Renton", "GPE"]], [["Midland", "GPE"]], [["Fairfield", "GPE"]], [["Brownsville", "GPE"]], [["Vancouver", "GPE"]], [["Oxnard", "GPE"]], [["Syracuse", "GPE"]], [["Boulder", "GPE"]], [["Lexington", "GPE"]], [["Jose  ", "PERSON"]]], "POS_tags": [[{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NUM", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NUM", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADJ", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADJ", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "SYM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "SPACE", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "DET", "PROPN", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "ADP", "DET", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADV", "ADJ", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "DET", "AUX", "ADJ", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "NUM", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "NUM", "PROPN", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "NUM", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADJ", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["X", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "DET", "VERB", "ADJ", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "DET", "VERB", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "VERB", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "DET", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADP", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}]], "clean": ["how to draw anime shirts ann arbor", "how to tie a tie in easy steps modesto", "how to draw a number dog salt lake city", "how to draw a dog rochester", "how to draw a dog w the word dog norman", "how to draw a dog art hub athens", "how to tie a tie wedding lexington", "how to draw a realistic dog worcester", "how to tie a fold stock tie montgomery", "how to tie a tie complex richmond", "how to draw anime step by step easy lowell", "how to tie a tie greensboro", "how to draw anime wolf boy paterson", "how to draw anime jawlines phoenix", "how to draw a dog golden retriever anchorage", "how to tie a tie visual lafayette", "how to draw anime girl thousand oak", "how to tie a tie half windsor daly city", "how to draw a dog house step by step escondido", "step to draw a dog san bernardino", "how to tie a tie wedding centennial", "how to draw a dog with circles naperville", "how to draw a dog german shepherd gainesville", "how to tie a tie video half windsor grand rapids", "how to tie a tie quilt tyler", "way to tie a tie oakland", "how to draw a dog donut evansville", "how to tie a tie with a dimple huntsville", "how to draw a dog with sunglasses lafayette", "how to draw anime run ann arbor", "how to tie a tie beginner brownsville", "how to tie a tie harry potter peoria", "how to draw a anime character kansas city", "how to draw anime in minutes indianapolis", "how to tie a tie video mirror view frisco", "how to draw a cute kawaii chibi elephant hold a pig balloon easy step drawing lesson for kid", "tie a tie annoying orange chula vista", "w to tie a bow tie austin", "how to draw a vire dog detroit", "how to draw anime dragon greensboro", "how to draw anime face antioch", "how to draw a dog out of a west valley city", "how to draw anime kissing antioch", "how to draw a dog very easy santa clara", "how to draw a dog that be cute costa mesa", "how to tie a tie in seconds aurora", "how draw dog face athens", "how to tie a tie corpus christi", "how to tie a tie ways little rock", "how to draw a dog house step by step buffalo", "how to tie a tie picture steps lakewood", "how tie a tie knot fresno", "how to draw a dog do the dab berkeley", "how to tie a tie harry potter sioux falls", "how to tie a tie a shoe tempe", "how to tie a tie steps worcester", "how to draw anime on ipad davenport", "audi e tron become first electric car to win top safety award", "how draw anime cat girl stockton", "youtube how to tie a tie fairfield", "how to draw anime pants springfield", "how to draw a dog narrated step by step torrance", "how to tie a tie right handed buffalo", "how tie a tie cambridge", "how to draw a dog mouth henderson", "way to tie a tie chicago", "how to draw a cute cuddle team leader from fortnite", "how to tie a tie up shirt akron", "how to draw a dog complex san jose", "how to draw a dog yorkie las cruces", "new way to tie a tie wilmington", "how to draw a dog that look real midland", "how to tie a tie a full windsor knot akron", "how to tie a tie gentleman irvine", "how to draw a dog colored pencil salt lake city", "how to draw a dog that look real west valley city", "how to draw a dog art ala carte new haven", "how to tie a tie narrow knot aurora", "how to draw anime smile wichita", "how to draw a dog use the word dog clovis", "how to draw a dog with circles pasadena", "how to draw a cartoon dog youtube montgomery", "how to draw a cartoon dog video hillsboro", "how to draw a dog and cat step by step carrollton", "how to tie a tie kid sandy springs", "how to draw a dog real easy allentown", "how to tie a tie in minutes sunnyvale", "how to draw anime profile atlanta", "how to tie a tie ways temecula", "how to tie a tie to a bow tie cambridge", "how to draw a dog collar renton", "how to draw the zodiac dog midland", "how to tie a tie a bandana fairfield", "how to tie a tie quick brownsville", "how to tie a tie rose knot vancouver", "how to draw a dog tail oxnard", "how to tie a bow tie syracuse", "how to draw a dog from behind boulder", "how to tie a half hitch lexington", "how to draw anime people san jose"]}