{"author_id": "dgm54nxhyr9cextksr1tnflxu416sama", "truth": 0, "tweets": ["Oscars 2020 red carpet: Stars embrace sustainability and sleeves #URL# #URL#", "10 must-watch WNBA games in 2020 #URL# #URL#", "A guide to the impeachment trial's new phase #URL# #URL#", "Van Jones: Trump isn't the biggest threat on the ballot #URL# #URL#", "The President plans to add high-profile lawyers to his legal defense team, sources say #URL# #URL#", "Klobuchar: Impeachment is a decency check #URL# #URL#", "A Chinese tourist who tested positive for the virus died in France, health officials confirm #URL# #URL#", "Sun trade 3 1st-round picks to sign star Bonner #URL# #URL#", "Virginia braces for gun-rights rally that the governor fears could turn violent #URL# #URL#", "Iowa conspiracy theories show US democracy has big issues #URL# #URL#", "The virus has infected more than 60,000 people globally. Only two deaths have occurred outside China.… #URL#", "McConnell warns against witnesses in pitch for quick impeachment trial resolution #URL# #URL#", "Kobe and Gianna Bryant, a tribute at Manila's famed basketball court #URL# #URL#", "Organizer of conservative conference won't invite Mitt Romney after impeachment trial vote #URL# #URL#", "Impeachment manager Adam Schiff: You 'gotta give Trump credit for this' #URL# #URL#", "Clayton Christensen, pioneer of 'disruptive innovation,' dies at 67 #URL# #URL#", "McConnell is expected to move quickly to acquit Trump if witness vote fails Friday #URL# #URL#", "UH QB King reverses course, says he will transfer #URL# #URL#", "Ukraine opens criminal probe into possible surveillance of ex-US ambassador #URL# #URL#", "Baylor hires LSU DC Aranda as new head coach #URL# #URL#", "Why the census is starting months early in this remote Alaskan fishing village #URL# #URL#", "Survey: Fans want Astros players punished too #URL# #URL#", "Washington Post criticized for suspending reporter over Kobe Bryant tweets #URL# #URL#", "Opinion: GOP needs to do what I did during Nixon impeachment #URL# #URL#", "Senators spill the story on milk at trial #URL# #URL#", "Redskins releasing CB Norman after 4 seasons #URL# #URL#", "Biden calls Iowa a 'toss up' #URL# #URL#", "A police officer who said he was told to 'tone down your gayness' reaches $10 million settlement and gets promoted… #URL#", "Trump rages against impeachment while overseas #URL# #URL#", "Sources: Baylor expected to hire LSU's Aranda #URL# #URL#", "Chief justice: Roberts stares down a possible legacy moment #URL# #URL#", "See how Sanders responded to Warren's accusation #URL# #URL#", "Analysis: Trump's decision to expand his power stuns Washington #URL# #URL#", "Ronaldo 'too old' to join Bayern - president #URL# #URL#", "Opening contest: Messy delay leaves Iowa without a winner #URL# #URL#", "Airlines adopt preventative measures #URL# #URL#", "A taxi driver saved an elderly woman from being scammed out of $25,000 #URL# #URL#", "Trump says he'll award Medal of Freedom to Rush Limbaugh #URL# #URL#", "Iraq War haunts the 2020 vote #URL# #URL#", "Bubble Watch 2020: Good news for Penn State and Kentucky #URL# #URL#", "Travel restrictions placed on third Chinese city over Wuhan coronavirus outbreak #URL# #URL#", "This remote Alaskan village is getting ready for the 2020 census #URL# #URL#", "Opinion: Yes, Pompeo, Americans do care about Ukraine #URL# #URL#", "This coat design isn't just saving lives. It's launching new careers for homeless people #URL# #URL#", "Daytona 500 starts Jimmie Johnson's farewell tour #URL# #URL#", "Analysis: GOP theory for acquittal could unleash Trump #URL# #URL#", "NFL reinstates Browns' Garrett from suspension #URL# #URL#", "Analysis: 5 scenarios from tonight's Iowa caucuses #URL# #URL#", "Wild deal Zucker to Pens for 2 players, draft pick #URL# #URL#", "Fact check: 65 ways Trump's been dishonest about impeachment #URL# #URL#", "Pelosi may send impeachment to Senate tomorrow #URL# #URL#", "Authorities recover the bodies of American firefighters killed in Australia #URL# #URL#", "Prince Harry and Meghan Markle to close Buckingham Palace office #URL# #URL#", "Nigerians shocked after being included in new ban #URL# #URL#", "Pioneer of 'disruptive innovation' dies #URL# #URL#", "Now-deceased man responsible for murder of Stephanie Parze, authorities say #URL# #URL#", "Grimes confirms that she's pregnant, and 'woefully ill prepared' #URL# #URL#", "Opinion roundup: Bad omens for Warren and Biden #URL# #URL#", "Impeachment guide: How the trial will work #URL# #URL#", "Organizer of conservative conference won't invite Mitt Romney after impeachment vote #URL# #URL#", "The biggest unanswered questions going into the 2020 F1 season #URL# #URL#", "Photos: Kobe Bryant's life in pictures #URL# #URL#", "Power Rankings: Can the Raptors win the East? #URL# #URL#", "House impeachment managers fear Trump is emboldened #URL# #URL#", "Opinion roundup: Sanders victory scrambles the race #URL# #URL#", "The President's speech comes as the Senate is expected to acquit him and Iowa votes on his challengers… #URL#", "Hinch: 'Fair question' if Astros' Series win tainted #URL# #URL#", "US prepares to evacuate cruise ship as infections climb #URL# #URL#", "Iowa conspiracy theories show US has bigger problems than foreign interference #URL# #URL#", "Analysis: Chris Cillizza's winners and losers of the 8th Democratic debate #URL# #URL#", "Schiff gets choked up during emotional speech #URL# #URL#", "Offseason predictions for all 32 NFL teams: Gurley trade, QBs on move #URL# #URL#", "Coronavirus cases rise to more than 67,000 #URL# #URL#", "8 unanswered questions about Trump and Ukraine that will live on after impeachment #URL# #URL#", "Whom should you root for? #URL# #URL#", "A guide to the Senate trial's new phase #URL# #URL#", "8 unanswered questions about Trump and Ukraine that will live on #URL# #URL#", "Robotic Ronaldo! Amazing giant CR7 figure towers over Italian carnival #URL# #URL#", "The truth behind baseball's sign stealing legend #URL# #URL#", "Analysis: Iowa caucuses just died forever #URL# #URL#", "A driver thought his skeleton passenger meant he could drive in the HOV lane #URL# #URL#", "The Utah senator says he wants John Bolton to testify and it's likely other GOP lawmakers will join him… #URL#", "US women's soccer star eyes 'potential' career as NFL kicker #URL# #URL#", "AO qualifier forced to retire after coughing fit #URL# #URL#", "Analysis: A week like no other looms in American politics #URL# #URL#", "Lawmakers around the nation are proposing bills for -- and against -- vaccinations #URL# #URL#", "Jaguars hire ex-Redskins coach Gruden as OC #URL# #URL#", "What happened when Democrats played a clip of Graham in 1999 #URL# #URL#", "Myanmar ordered to prevent genocide against Rohingya by top UN court #URL# #URL#", "Wawa goes after the dinner crowd with burgers and chicken sandwiches #URL# #URL#", "Lev Parnas says Trump 'knew exactly what was going on' with Ukraine pressure campaign #URL# #URL#", "See the highlights of the 2020 Oscars red carpet #URL# #URL#", "Premier League preview: Man City should switch things up, focus on UCL #URL# #URL#", "Watch: Schiff's sarcastic dig at President Trump #URL# #URL#", "China warns people can spread the Wuhan virus before realizing they're ill, calling into question the US' method of… #URL#", "Debate question silenced candidates. Then Klobuchar raised her hand #URL# #URL#", "Vodka pouches, CO2 cannons and Bill Belichick: Six hours at Gronk Beach #URL# #URL#", "Tagliabue, Steve Sabol among 13 picked for HOF #URL# #URL#", "Kobe Bryant on leadership, failure, critics and more #URL# #URL#", "Trump defends firing of key impeachment witness Vindman #URL# #URL#"], "ents": [[["Oscars 2020", "ORG"]], [["10", "CARDINAL"], ["WNBA", "ORG"], ["2020", "DATE"]], [], [["Van Jones", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "LOC"]], [], [], [["Chinese", "NORP"], ["France", "GPE"]], [["Sun", "ORG"], ["3 1st", "DATE"]], [["Virginia", "GPE"]], [["Iowa", "GPE"], ["US", "GPE"]], [["more than 60,000", "CARDINAL"], ["Only two", "CARDINAL"], ["China", "GPE"]], [["McConnell", "ORG"]], [["Kobe", "GPE"], ["Gianna Bryant", "PERSON"], ["Manila", "GPE"]], [["Mitt Romney", "ORG"]], [["Adam Schiff", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "PERSON"]], [["Clayton Christensen", "PERSON"], ["67", "CARDINAL"]], [["McConnell", "ORG"], ["Trump", "PRODUCT"], ["Friday", "DATE"]], [], [["Ukraine", "GPE"], ["ex-US", "GPE"]], [["Aranda", "PERSON"]], [["months early", "DATE"], ["Alaskan", "NORP"]], [["Astros", "PERSON"]], [["Washington Post", "ORG"], ["Kobe Bryant", "ORG"]], [["GOP", "ORG"], ["Nixon", "PERSON"]], [], [["Norman", "PERSON"], ["4 seasons", "DATE"]], [["Iowa", "GPE"]], [["$10 million", "MONEY"]], [], [["LSU", "ORG"], ["Aranda", "PERSON"]], [], [["Sanders", "ORG"], ["Warren", "PERSON"]], [["Trump", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Washington", "GPE"]], [], [["Iowa", "GPE"]], [], [["25,000", "MONEY"]], [["Trump", "PERSON"]], [["Iraq", "GPE"], ["2020", "CARDINAL"]], [["Penn State", "ORG"], ["Kentucky", "GPE"]], [["third", "ORDINAL"], ["Chinese", "NORP"], ["Wuhan", "GPE"]], [["Alaskan", "NORP"], ["2020", "DATE"]], [["Pompeo", "PERSON"], ["Americans", "NORP"], ["Ukraine", "GPE"]], [], [["Jimmie Johnson's", "PERSON"]], [["GOP", "ORG"], ["Trump", "PRODUCT"]], [["NFL", "ORG"], ["Garrett", "PERSON"]], [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["tonight", "TIME"], ["Iowa", "GPE"]], [["Zucker", "PERSON"], ["2", "CARDINAL"]], [["65", "CARDINAL"], ["Trump", "PERSON"]], [["Pelosi", "ORG"], ["Senate", "ORG"], ["tomorrow", "DATE"]], [["American", "NORP"], ["Australia", "GPE"]], [["Prince Harry", "PERSON"], ["Meghan Markle", "PERSON"], ["Buckingham Palace", "FAC"]], [["Nigerians", "NORP"]], [["Pioneer", "ORG"]], [["Stephanie Parze", "PERSON"]], [], [["Warren", "PERSON"], ["Biden", "PERSON"]], [], [["Mitt Romney", "ORG"]], [["2020 F1 season", "DATE"]], [["Kobe Bryant's", "PERSON"]], [["East", "LOC"]], [["House", "ORG"], ["Trump", "PRODUCT"]], [], [["Senate", "ORG"], ["Iowa", "GPE"]], [["Astros", "PERSON"]], [["US", "GPE"]], [["Iowa", "GPE"], ["US", "GPE"]], [["Chris Cillizza's", "PERSON"], ["8th", "ORDINAL"], ["Democratic", "NORP"]], [], [["Offseason", "ORG"], ["all 32", "CARDINAL"], ["NFL", "ORG"], ["Gurley", "PERSON"]], [["Coronavirus", "ORG"], ["more than 67,000", "CARDINAL"]], [["8", "CARDINAL"], ["Trump", "LOC"], ["Ukraine", "GPE"]], [], [["Senate", "ORG"]], [["8", "CARDINAL"], ["Trump", "LOC"], ["Ukraine", "GPE"]], [["Italian", "NORP"]], [], [["Iowa", "GPE"]], [["HOV", "ORG"]], [["Utah", "GPE"], ["John Bolton", "PERSON"], ["GOP", "ORG"]], [["US", "GPE"], ["NFL", "ORG"]], [["AO qualifier", "ORG"]], [["A week", "DATE"], ["American", "NORP"]], [], [["Jaguars", "PERSON"], ["ex-Redskins", "ORG"], ["Gruden", "PERSON"]], [["Democrats", "NORP"], ["Graham", "PERSON"], ["1999", "DATE"]], [["Myanmar", "GPE"], ["Rohingya", "PERSON"], ["UN", "ORG"]], [["Wawa", "ORG"]], [["Trump", "LOC"], ["Ukraine", "GPE"]], [["2020", "CARDINAL"]], [["Premier League", "ORG"], ["Man City", "GPE"], ["UCL", "ORG"]], [["Trump", "PERSON"]], [["China", "GPE"], ["Wuhan", "GPE"], ["US", "GPE"]], [["Klobuchar", "ORG"]], [["Bill Belichick", "PERSON"], ["Six hours", "TIME"], ["Gronk Beach", "FAC"]], [["Tagliabue", "ORG"], ["Steve Sabol", "PERSON"], ["13", "CARDINAL"], ["HOF", "ORG"]], [["Kobe Bryant", "PERSON"]], [["Vindman", "ORG"]]], "POS_tags": [[{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NUM", "VERB", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "AUX", "PART", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "AUX", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADJ", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "AUX", "VERB", "ADJ", "SCONJ", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADV", "PUNCT", "ADV", "NUM", "NOUN", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADV", "DET", "NOUN", "AUX", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "AUX", "PRON", "PRON", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "DET", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "PRON", "AUX", "VERB", "PART", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "SYM", "NUM", "NUM", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "VERB", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "ADV", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["VERB", "ADV", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "AUX", "VERB", "SCONJ", "ADP", "SYM", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NUM", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "AUX", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "DET", "NUM", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "INTJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "AUX", "PART", "ADV", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "AUX", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NUM", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "VERB", "VERB", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PART", "PROPN", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "PROPN", "AUX", "AUX", "ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADV", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "SCONJ", "PRON", "AUX", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADV", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "DET", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "VERB", "SCONJ", "DET", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PRON", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NUM", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "SCONJ", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "DET", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "ADP", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PART", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "DET", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADV", "VERB", "ADV", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "CCONJ", "PRON", "AUX", "ADV", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "PRON", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "VERB", "ADJ", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "AUX", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "ADV", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADV", "PRON", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADJ", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NUM", "PROPN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["VERB", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "VERB", "PRON", "AUX", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADJ", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}]], "clean": ["oscars red carpet star embrace sustainability and sleeve", "must watch wnba game in", "a guide to the impeachment trial new phase", "van jones trump be the big threat on the ballot", "the president plan to add high profile lawyer to -pron- legal defense team source say", "klobuchar impeachment be a decency check", "a chinese tourist who test positive for the virus die in france health official confirm", "sun trade round pick to sign star bonner", "virginia brace for gun right rally that the governor fear could turn violent", "iowa conspiracy theory show us democracy have big issue", "the virus have infect more than people globally only two death have occur outside china", "mcconnell warn against witness in pitch for quick impeachment trial resolution", "kobe and gianna bryant a tribute at manila famed basketball court", "organizer of conservative conference will invite mitt romney after impeachment trial vote", "impeachment manager adam schiff -pron- get to give trump credit for this", "clayton christensen pioneer of disruptive innovation die at", "mcconnell be expect to move quickly to acquit trump if witness vote fail friday", "uh qb king reverse course say -pron- will transfer", "ukraine open criminal probe into possible surveillance of ex us ambassador", "baylor hire lsu dc aranda as new head coach", "why the census be start month early in this remote alaskan fishing village", "survey fan want astros player punish too", "washington post criticize for suspend reporter over kobe bryant tweet", "opinion gop need to do what -pron- do during nixon impeachment", "senator spill the story on milk at trial", "redskin release cb norman after season", "biden call iowa a toss up", "a police officer who say -pron- be tell to tone down -pron- gayness reach million settlement and get promote", "trump rage against impeachment while overseas", "source baylor expect to hire lsu aranda", "chief justice roberts stare down a possible legacy moment", "see how sander respond to warren accusation", "analysis trump decision to expand -pron- power stun washington", "ronaldo too old to join bayern president", "opening contest messy delay leave iowa without a winner", "airline adopt preventative measure", "a taxi driver save an elderly woman from be scamme out of", "trump say -pron- award medal of freedom to rush limbaugh", "iraq war haunt the vote", "bubble watch good news for penn state and kentucky", "travel restriction place on third chinese city over wuhan coronavirus outbreak", "this remote alaskan village be get ready for the census", "opinion yes pompeo americans do care about ukraine", "this coat design be just save life -pron- launch new career for homeless people", "daytona start jimmie johnson farewell tour", "analysis gop theory for acquittal could unleash trump", "nfl reinstate browns garrett from suspension", "analysis scenario from tonight iowa caucus", "wild deal zucker to pens for player draft pick", "fact check way trump be dishonest about impeachment", "pelosi may send impeachment to senate tomorrow", "authority recover the body of american firefighter kill in australia", "prince harry and meghan markle to close buckingham palace office", "nigerian shock after be include in new ban", "pioneer of disruptive innovation die", "now deceased man responsible for murder of stephanie parze authority say", "grime confirm that -pron- pregnant and woefully ill prepared", "opinion roundup bad omen for warren and biden", "impeachment guide how the trial will work", "organizer of conservative conference will invite mitt romney after impeachment vote", "the big unanswered question go into the season", "photo kobe bryant life in picture", "power rankings can the raptor win the east", "house impeachment manager fear trump be embolden", "opinion roundup sander victory scramble the race", "the president speech come as the senate be expect to acquit -pron- and iowa vote on -pron- challenger", "hinch fair question if astros series win taint", "us prepare to evacuate cruise ship as infection climb", "iowa conspiracy theory show us have big problem than foreign interference", "analysis chris cillizza winner and loser of the democratic debate", "schiff get choke up during emotional speech", "offseason prediction for all nfl team gurley trade qb on move", "coronavirus case rise to more than", "unanswered question about trump and ukraine that will live on after impeachment", "whom should -pron- root for", "a guide to the senate trial new phase", "unanswered question about trump and ukraine that will live on", "robotic ronaldo amazing giant figure tower over italian carnival", "the truth behind baseball sign steal legend", "analysis iowa caucus just die forever", "a driver think -pron- skeleton passenger mean -pron- could drive in the hov lane", "the utah senator say -pron- want john bolton to testify and -pron- likely other gop lawmaker will join -pron-", "us woman soccer star eye potential career as nfl kicker", "ao qualifier force to retire after cough fit", "analysis a week like no other loom in american politic", "lawmaker around the nation be propose bill for and against vaccination", "jaguar hire ex redskins coach gruden as oc", "what happen when democrats play a clip of graham in", "myanmar order to prevent genocide against rohingya by top un court", "wawa go after the dinner crowd with burger and chicken sandwich", "lev parnas say trump know exactly what be go on with ukraine pressure caign", "see the highlight of the oscars red carpet", "premier league preview man city should switch thing up focus on ucl", "watch schiff sarcastic dig at president trump", "china warn people can spread the wuhan virus before realize -pron- ill call into question the us method of", "debate question silence candidate then klobuchar raise -pron- hand", "vodka pouch cannon and bill belichick six hour at gronk beach", "tagliabue steve sabol among pick for hof", "kobe bryant on leadership failure critic and more", "trump defend firing of key impeachment witness vindman"]}