{"py/object": "data.Author", "author_id": "dnmht6eebqauwh4w6akiy9q1zb0ebl0g", "truth": 1, "tweets": ["Latest iOS 13.3.1 Beta Includes Toggle for Disabling U1 Ultra Wideband Chip #URL#", "LastPass to Drop Support for Native Mac App and Replace it With Universal Web App #URL#", "Avelina Lésper: Critic apologises for shattering artwork at Mexico fair #URL#", "Brad Pitt calls out Congress and impeachment hearings in Oscar speech #URL#", "When a homeless couple moved in with a millionaire #URL#", "Tekashi 6ix9ine Plans to Leave NYC After Prison with Top-Notch Security #URL#", "What's The Big Frigin' Difference? #URL#", "NYPD Abandons Paper Memo Books for New iPhone App #URL#", "EU Lawmakers Vote Overwhelmingly in Favor of Common Charging Standard, Despite Apple's Protestations [Updated] #URL#", "Should schools be allowed to ban slang words like 'peng'? #URL#", "Super Bowl 2020 Sign Language Artist Condemns Fox for Excluding Her Performance On Air #URL#", "Beyonce and Blue Ivy Wearing Adidas x Ivy Park Gear #URL#", "NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 20:00 (JST), February 07 #URL#", "Ecuador president says women 'only report harassment from ugly men' #URL#", "Facebook apologetic after a 'technical issue' calls China's leader 'Mr. Shithole' #URL#", "Bernie Madoff Says He's Dying and Deserves Release from Prison #URL#", "Alicia Keys &amp; Boyz II Men sing touching tribute to Kobe Bryant at Grammys #URL#", "The best VPN for Netflix in 2020: Deals and how to watch American Netflix in the UK #URL#", "Washington State’s Department of Transportation Tweets That It Maybe, Just Maybe, Found Bigfoot. ‘We Will Leave Tha… #URL#", "The fake 'kitchen hacks' with billions of views #URL#", "NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 20:00 (JST), January 17 #URL#", "Grab a futuristic Tempur-Pedic mattress on sale for Presidents Day #URL#", "Zsa Zsa Gabor's Husband Says Bernie Madoff Should Rot in Prison #URL#", "NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 20:00 (JST), January 21 #URL#", "Deals: Low Prices Hit 13-Inch and 16-Inch MacBook Pro (Up to $300 Off) #URL#", "Amazon cancels its Mobile World Congress plan over coronavirus fears #URL#", "Samsung's new foldable phone already sounds way better than the Galaxy Fold #URL#", "NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 20:00 (JST), January 15 #URL#", "L.A. Politicians Officially Demand MLB Turn Over WS Titles To Dodgers #URL#", "Porto footballer quits match over racist abuse #URL#", "Kristin Chenoweth Scared Of Deadly Coronavirus, Traveling With Mask #URL#", "Best hookup apps and online dating sites to help you get it on #URL#", "The best dating sites to find a connection by this weekend #URL#", "Mama June Not Making Money Off New Reality Show 'From Not To Hot' #URL#", "Apple Reportedly Working on 'AirPod Pro Lite' Earphones #URL#", "Coronavirus forces Huawei to postpone developer conference #URL#", "Australia weather: How much rain did it take to put out NSW fires? #URL#", "Safeguard your online privacy with PureVPN #URL#", "Protesters take their '.org' sale criticism offline #URL#", "The Valentine's Day gifts your husband wants — but would never buy for himself #URL#", "Excitement for 'Mulan' builds in sneak peak for upcoming trailer #URL#", "15 inspirational 'Harry Potter' quotes to live by #URL#", "How the camp became centre of Nazi Holocaust #URL#", "NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 04:30 (JST), January 27 #URL#", "Shanina Shaik's Divorce to DJ Ruckus Will Be Official Next Week #URL#", "Japan's economy shrinks at fastest rate since 2014 #URL#", "NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 04:30 (JST), February 03 #URL#", "Strava for iOS Gains HealthKit Integration for Importing Apple Watch Workouts #URL#", "All in good time: Why Brazil wants its teens not to have sex #URL#", "We found these ergonomic Tempur-Pedic pillows on sale for super cheap #URL#", "11 of the best Bluetooth speakers #URL#", "It’s Always a Good Day to Bask in the Platonic Love Between Leonardo DiCaprio and Brad Pitt #URL#", "WTF is a Theragun? A look at the best massage guns for percussive therapy. #URL#", "‘Look at the Sizes of That Thing.’ Colorado Sheriff Department’s Confusing Boulder Description is Ruling Social Med… #URL#", "Pitbull Canceled on Steven Tyler Event Due to Kobe Bryant Tragedy #URL#", "Miley Cyrus Closes Out Doors' 50th Anniversary 'Morrison Hotel' Party #URL#", "NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 20:00 (JST), February 03 #URL#", "'She's more qualified than you are for your job': Seth Meyers blasts Pompeo over bizarre NPR tantrum #URL#", "Amy Schumer Shares IVF Results and Thanks Fans as She Continues Journey #URL#", "San Francisco Giants Hire First Full-Time Female Coach in MLB History #URL#", "Google's Super Bowl ad will totally make you cry #URL#", "Kellyanne Conway Invokes MLK Jr.'s Name to Blast Trump Impeachment Trial #URL#", "Tom and Jerry: 80 years of cat v mouse #URL#", "Kelly Rowland Proudly Sports Beyonce's New Adidas x Ivy Park Gear #URL#", "I used emoji to order groceries #URL#", "2020 Mazda CX-9 review: When fashion trumps function - Roadshow #URL#", "PnB Rock Totals Car in Alleged Street Race, Arrested For DUI #URL#", "23andMe CEO lays off 100, attributes sluggish sales to consumer privacy concerns #URL#", "Apple Shares New 'Slofie' Videos Highlighting iPhone 11 and 11 Pro Cameras #URL#", "Apple to Show Off Apple TV+ Show 'Mythic Quest: Raven's Banquet' at PAX South #URL#", "Trump impeachment: All eyes on moderate Republicans in witnesses battle #URL#", "Bradley Whitford Says Stephen King's Diversity Oscar Tweet is Ignorant #URL#", "'Captain America' Actress Claims Self-Defense in Mom's Murder #URL#", "Chuck Liddell Hopes Cowboy Cerrone Beats Conor McGregor At UFC 246 #URL#", "Lee Harvey Oswald's Final Uncashed Paycheck, Up for Auction #URL#", "EA Retiring Tetris Apps for iOS in April 2020 #URL#", "Apple Was the Fastest Growing Premium Smartphone Brand of 2019 in India #URL#", "Tim Cook Shares Behind-the-Scenes Look at Apple TV+ Show 'Little America' #URL#", "Guess Who This Happy Kid Turned Into! #URL#", "Find your lobster with a little help from Match #URL#", "Felicity Huffman &amp; Daughter Wear Masks at Airport Amid Coronavirus Scare #URL#", "Cleveland Browns Mascot Swagger Dead At 6 #URL#", "Wrapped Up Stars ... Hot And Dry! #URL#", "Belgium's ex-King Albert II admits fathering child after DNA test #URL#", "‘I Cracked Up So Hard.’ This Woman’s Romantic Dinner Date Is Precisely What Her Dreams Were Never Made Of #URL#", "Kangaroo Island: Tree climber helps save koalas #URL#", "12 of the best automatic cat feeders to keep your pet fed and happy #URL#", "Apple Stops Signing iOS 13.3 Following Release of iOS 13.3.1 #URL#", "This deepfake of Robert Downey Jr. and Tom Holland in 'Back to the Future' is unreal #URL#", "Blueface Says Tekashi's Bodyguards Are Smart for Passing on the Job #URL#", "Seth Meyers pokes fun at Trump's weird obsession with badgers #URL#", "Apple Joins the FIDO Alliance to Help Develop and Promote Authentication Standards #URL#", "Samsung Galaxy S20 leaks again, this time on Samsung's own website #URL#", "Top Stories: 5G iPhone and iPad Rumors, AirPods Pro Lite?, HomePod Turns Two #URL#", "Nikki Bella Showing Off Her Baby Bump After Pregnancy Reveal #URL#", "Davos 2020: What is the World Economic Forum and is it elitist? #URL#", "Justin Bieber Works Yummy Food Truck with James Corden #URL#", "The Truth About Meghan Markle and Ellen DeGeneres' Alleged Interview #URL#", "The best BT broadband deals in the UK #URL#", "Pamela Anderson &amp; New 'Husband' Split 12 Days After Secret Wedding #URL#"], "ents": [[], [["LastPass", "ORG"], ["Drop Support for", "ORG"], ["Universal Web App", "ORG"]], [["Avelina Lésper", "PERSON"], ["Mexico", "GPE"]], [["Brad Pitt", "PERSON"], ["Congress", "ORG"], ["Oscar", "PERSON"]], [], [["Tekashi 6ix9ine", "PERSON"]], [], [["NYPD", "ORG"]], [["EU", "ORG"]], [["peng", "PERSON"]], [["Super Bowl 2020 Sign Language Artist Condemns Fox for Excluding Her Performance On Air", "EVENT"]], [["Beyonce", "PERSON"]], [["20:00", "TIME"], ["February 07", "DATE"]], [["Ecuador", "GPE"]], [["Facebook", "ORG"], ["China", "GPE"], ["Shithole", "PERSON"]], [["Bernie Madoff", "PERSON"]], [["Alicia Keys", "PERSON"], ["Kobe Bryant", "PERSON"], ["Grammys", "PERSON"]], [["VPN", "PRODUCT"], ["Netflix", "PRODUCT"], ["2020", "DATE"], ["American Netflix", "ORG"], ["UK", "GPE"]], [["Washington State’s", "GPE"], ["Department of Transportation Tweets That It Maybe", "ORG"], ["Bigfoot", "GPE"]], [["billions", "CARDINAL"]], [["20:00", "TIME"], ["January 17", "DATE"]], [["Tempur-Pedic", "ORG"], ["Presidents Day", "DATE"]], [["Zsa Zsa Gabor's", "PERSON"], ["Bernie Madoff", "PERSON"]], [["20:00", "TIME"], ["January 21", "DATE"]], [["Up to $300", "MONEY"]], [["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Mobile World Congress", "ORG"]], [["Samsung", "ORG"]], [["20:00", "TIME"], ["January 15", "DATE"]], [["L.A.", "GPE"]], [["Porto", "GPE"]], [["Kristin Chenoweth Scared Of Deadly Coronavirus", "PERSON"]], [], [["this weekend", "DATE"]], [["June", "DATE"]], [["Apple", "ORG"]], [["Coronavirus", "ORG"], ["Huawei", "ORG"]], [["Australia", "GPE"], ["NSW", "ORG"]], [], [], [["Valentine", "PERSON"]], [["Mulan", "ORG"]], [["15", "CARDINAL"], ["Harry Potter'", "PERSON"]], [["Nazi", "NORP"]], [["04:30", "TIME"], ["January 27", "DATE"]], [["Shanina Shaik's", "PERSON"], ["Next Week", "DATE"]], [["Japan", "GPE"], ["2014", "DATE"]], [["04:30", "TIME"], ["February 03", "DATE"]], [["Strava", "ORG"], ["iOS Gains HealthKit Integration for Importing Apple Watch", "ORG"]], [["Brazil", "GPE"]], [], [["11", "CARDINAL"]], [["Bask", "PERSON"], ["Leonardo DiCaprio", "PERSON"], ["Brad Pitt", "PERSON"]], [["WTF", "ORG"]], [["Look at the Sizes of That Thing", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Colorado Sheriff Department’s", "ORG"], ["Confusing Boulder Description", "LAW"]], [["Steven Tyler", "PERSON"], ["Kobe Bryant Tragedy", "ORG"]], [["Miley Cyrus", "PERSON"], ["50th", "ORDINAL"], ["Morrison Hotel' Party", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["20:00", "TIME"], ["February 03", "DATE"]], [["Seth Meyers", "PERSON"], ["Pompeo", "PERSON"], ["NPR", "ORG"]], [["Amy Schumer", "PERSON"]], [["San Francisco Giants Hire First Full-Time Female Coach", "ORG"]], [["Google", "ORG"], ["Super Bowl", "EVENT"]], [["Kellyanne Conway", "PERSON"], ["MLK Jr.'s", "PERSON"], ["Name to Blast Trump Impeachment Trial", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Tom", "PERSON"], ["Jerry", "PERSON"], ["80 years", "DATE"]], [["Kelly Rowland Proudly", "PERSON"], ["Beyonce", "PERSON"], ["New Adidas", "EVENT"]], [], [["2020", "CARDINAL"], ["Mazda", "ORG"]], [["PnB", "GPE"], ["DUI", "PERSON"]], [["23andMe", "CARDINAL"], ["100", "CARDINAL"]], [["Apple Shares New '", "ORG"], ["11", "CARDINAL"], ["11", "CARDINAL"]], [["Show Off Apple TV+ Show 'Mythic", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Raven", "PERSON"]], [["Republicans", "NORP"]], [["Bradley Whitford", "PERSON"], ["Stephen King's", "PERSON"], ["Oscar Tweet", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [], [["Chuck Liddell", "PERSON"], ["Conor McGregor", "PERSON"], ["246", "CARDINAL"]], [["Lee Harvey Oswald's", "PERSON"]], [["EA", "ORG"], ["Tetris Apps", "PERSON"], ["iOS", "ORG"], ["April 2020", "DATE"]], [["Apple", "ORG"], ["2019", "DATE"], ["India", "GPE"]], [["Tim Cook", "PERSON"], ["Scenes Look", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [], [], [["Felicity Huffman", "PERSON"]], [["Cleveland", "GPE"]], [], [["Belgium", "GPE"], ["Albert II", "PERSON"]], [["This Woman’s Romantic", "PERSON"]], [["Kangaroo Island", "GPE"]], [["12", "CARDINAL"]], [["Apple Stops Signing iOS 13.3 Following Release", "ORG"]], [["Robert Downey Jr.", "PERSON"], ["Tom Holland", "PERSON"]], [["Blueface", "PERSON"], ["Tekashi", "PERSON"]], [["Seth Meyers", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "ORG"]], [["Apple", "ORG"], ["the FIDO Alliance", "ORG"]], [["Samsung Galaxy S20", "PRODUCT"], ["Samsung", "ORG"]], [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["iPad Rumors", "PRODUCT"], ["AirPods Pro Lite", "PRODUCT"], ["HomePod Turns", "PERSON"], ["Two", "CARDINAL"]], [["Nikki Bella Showing Off Her Baby Bump After", "PERSON"]], [["Davos", "PERSON"], ["the World Economic Forum", "ORG"]], [["Justin Bieber", "PERSON"], ["James Corden", "PERSON"]], [["Meghan Markle", "PERSON"], ["Ellen DeGeneres'", "PERSON"]], [["UK", "GPE"]], [["Pamela Anderson", "PERSON"], ["12 Days", "DATE"]]], "POS_tags": [[{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "PRON", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "AUX", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "NOUN", "AUX", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PART", "ADJ", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADJ", "ADP", "DET", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PRON", "AUX", "VERB", "CCONJ", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "ADV", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "PRON", "ADV", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADV", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NUM", "CCONJ", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PART", "SYM", "NUM", "ADV", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADV", "VERB", "ADV", "ADJ", "SCONJ", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "ADV", "VERB", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "ADV", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "PRON", "AUX", "PRON", "ADP"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PART", "ADP", "ADJ", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADV", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADJ", "NOUN", "AUX", "PRON", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "X"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PART", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "VERB", "ADV", "VERB", "ADP", "PRON"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "AUX", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PART", "PART", "AUX", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "ADV", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PART", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PRON", "AUX", "ADV", "ADJ", "SCONJ", "PRON", "AUX", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "PRON", "VERB", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "NUM", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NUM", "CCONJ", "NUM", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "DET", "ADJ", "VERB", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "DET", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PRON", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "ADV", "ADV", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "PART", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADV", "PRON", "DET", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADV", "VERB", "ADP"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "PROPN", "NUM", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "AUX", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADJ", "ADP", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "VERB", "CCONJ", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADV", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PRON", "AUX", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "AUX", "PRON", "ADJ", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}]], "clean": ["late ios beta include toggle for disabling ultra wideband chip", "lastpass to drop support for native mac app and replace -pron- with universal web app", "avelina lésper critic apologise for shatter artwork at mexico fair", "brad pitt call out congress and impeachment hearing in oscar speech", "when a homeless couple move in with a millionaire", "tekashi plan to leave nyc after prison with top notch security", "what the big frigin difference", "nypd abandons paper memo books for new iphone app", "eu lawmaker vote overwhelmingly in favor of common charging standard despite apple protestation update", "should school be allow to ban slang word like peng", "super bowl sign language artist condemn fox for exclude -pron- performance on air", "beyonce and blue ivy wearing adidas x ivy park gear", "nhk world radio japan english news at jst february", "ecuador president say woman only report harassment from ugly man", "facebook apologetic after a technical issue call china leader shithole", "bernie madoff say -pron- die and deserve release from prison", "alicia keys boyz ii men sing touch tribute to kobe bryant at grammys", "the good vpn for netflix in deal and how to watch american netflix in the uk", "washington state department of transportation tweets that -pron- maybe just maybe find bigfoot -pron- will leave tha", "the fake kitchen hack with billion of view", "nhk world radio japan english news at jst january", "grab a futuristic tempur pedic mattress on sale for president day", "zsa zsa gabor husband say bernie madoff should rot in prison", "nhk world radio japan english news at jst january", "deal low price hit and macbook pro up to off", "amazon cancel -pron- mobile world congress plan over coronavirus fear", "samsung new foldable phone already sound way well than the galaxy fold", "nhk world radio japan english news at jst january", "politician officially demand mlb turn over ws title to dodgers", "porto footballer quit match over racist abuse", "kristin chenoweth scare of deadly coronavirus travel with mask", "good hookup app and online dating site to help -pron- get -pron- on", "the good dating site to find a connection by this weekend", "mama june not make money off new reality show from not to hot", "apple reportedly work on airpod pro lite earphone", "coronavirus force huawei to postpone developer conference", "australia weather how much rain do -pron- take to put out nsw fire", "safeguard -pron- online privacy with purevpn", "protester take -pron- sale criticism offline", "the valentine day gift -pron- husband want but would never buy for -pron-", "excitement for mulan build in sneak peak for upcoming trailer", "inspirational harry potter quote to live by", "how the c become centre of nazi holocaust", "nhk world radio japan english news at jst january", "shanina shaik divorce to dj ruckus will be official next week", "japan economy shrink at fast rate since", "nhk world radio japan english news at jst february", "strava for ios gain healthkit integration for import apple watch workout", "all in good time why brazil want -pron- teen not to have sex", "-pron- find these ergonomic tempur pedic pillow on sale for super cheap", "of the good bluetooth speaker", "-pron- always a good day to bask in the platonic love between leonardo dicaprio and brad pitt", "wtf be a theragun a look at the good massage gun for percussive therapy", "look at the size of that thing colorado sheriff department confusing boulder description be rule social med", "pitbull cancel on steven tyler event due to kobe bryant tragedy", "miley cyrus close out door anniversary morrison hotel party", "nhk world radio japan english news at jst february", "-pron- more qualified than -pron- be for -pron- job seth meyers blast pompeo over bizarre npr tantrum", "amy schumer shares ivf results and thank fan as -pron- continue journey", "san francisco giants hire first full time female coach in mlb history", "google super bowl ad will totally make -pron- cry", "kellyanne conway invoke mlk name to blast trump impeachment trial", "tom and jerry year of cat v mouse", "kelly rowland proudly sports beyonce new adidas x ivy park gear", "-pron- use emoji to order grocery", "mazda review when fashion trump function roadshow", "pnb rock totals car in allege street race arrest for dui", "ceo lay off attribute sluggish sale to consumer privacy concern", "apple share new slofie video highlight iphone and pro cameras", "apple to show off apple show mythic quest raven banquet at pax south", "trump impeachment all eye on moderate republicans in witness battle", "bradley whitford say stephen king diversity oscar tweet be ignorant", "captain america actress claim self defense in mom murder", "chuck liddell hope cowboy cerrone beat conor mcgregor at ufc", "lee harvey oswald final uncashed paycheck up for auction", "ea retiring tetris apps for ios in april", "apple be the fast grow premium smartphone brand of in india", "tim cook shares behind the scene look at apple show little america", "guess who this happy kid turn into", "find -pron- lobster with a little help from match", "felicity huffman daughter wear mask at airport amid coronavirus scare", "cleveland browns mascot swagger dead at", "wrap up stars hot and dry", "belgium ex king albert ii admit father child after dna test", "-pron- crack up so hard this woman romantic dinner date be precisely what -pron- dream be never make of", "kangaroo island tree climber help save koala", "of the good automatic cat feeder to keep -pron- pet fed and happy", "apple stop sign ios follow release of ios", "this deepfake of robert downey and tom holland in back to the future be unreal", "blueface say tekashi bodyguard be smart for pass on the job", "seth meyers poke fun at trump weird obsession with badger", "apple join the fido alliance to help develop and promote authentication standard", "samsung galaxy leak again this time on samsung own website", "top story g iphone and ipad rumors airpods pro lite homepod turns two", "nikki bella show off -pron- baby bump after pregnancy reveal", "davos what be the world economic forum and be -pron- elitist", "justin bieber work yummy food truck with james corden", "the truth about meghan markle and ellen degeneres allege interview", "the good bt broadband deal in the uk", "pamela anderson new husband split day after secret wedding"]}