{"py/object": "data.Author", "author_id": "iejmhz7ospkdpfy5ma3uc4b9ry4a764b", "truth": 0, "tweets": ["Henderson Poised To Win The PFA Player Of The Year #URL# #URL#", "Fireboy Could Possibly Be Wande Coal’s Number 1 Fan #URL# #URL#", "Tonto Dikeh Gets Sued For Defamation By Her Ex-Husband #URL# #URL#", "Nollywood Actress Left Her Marriage Due Fear For Her Life – See Who #URL# #URL#", "Yvonne Nelson Has An Advise For Christians #URL# #URL#", "Deadline Day Missed Deals – Upcoming Summer Deals? #URL# #URL#", "Meet The Nigerians To Ever Won The Grammys #URL# #URL#", "Bode George To Become A Citizen Of Togo #URL# #URL#", "Patoranking Reveals How He Takes Care Of 150 Children From His Village #URL# #URL#", "Nicki Minaj Has Never Collaborated With Kendrick Lamar And Here Is Why #URL# #URL#", "Extreme Weather Causes Manchester City’s Match Postponement #URL# #URL#", "Women Should Share Their Husbands With Side Chicks – Sir Shina Peters’s wIfe #URL# #URL#", "Governor Obiano Loves Yansh More Than Matters Of The State #URL# #URL#", "New Brand Ambassador For Crepaway Restaurant – Chioma #URL# #URL#", "Living Faith Bomber Was Not Carrying A Bomb #URL# #URL#", "Which Clubs Made The Highest Profit In The Last 2 Transfer Windows #URL# #URL#", "Popular Fruits You Eat and Probably Don’t Know Their Names #URL# #URL#", "Pep Guardiola Advised To Leave Manchester City #URL# #URL#", "Ex-Boyfriend Disrupt Wedding Organized With His Money #URL# #URL#", "New US Immigration Laws That Could Affect Nigerians #URL# #URL#", "People Believe I Am Rich But I Am Not – Tacha Reveals In A Video #URL#", "Painter Impregnates Two Students In The University Of Ibadan #URL# #URL#", "Real Madrid And Barcelona Both Got Knocked Out #URL# #URL#", "Victoria Inyama Has Stopped Taking Her Kids To Church – Here Is Why #URL# #URL#", "Popular Snapchat Queen “Hajia Pussy” Is Dead #URL# #URL#", "New NCC Rule – Bad News For Those With 4 Sims #URL# #URL#", "Cardi B Reveals When She Will Be Releasing Her Next Album #URL# #URL#", "Masturbation Is A Beautiful Thing – Stephanie Benson #URL# #URL#", "Deadline Day Transfer News #URL# #URL#", "Zlatan Rates Olamide Over Pastors #URL# #URL#", "Poch Might Be Manchester United Next Coach #URL# #URL#", "Peruzzi Defrauded Me And Tried To Have His Way With Me – Daffy Blanco #URL# #URL#", "BBNaija Star, Nina Got Married In Imo – See Photos #URL# #URL#", "Marriage Is Overated – Mercy Aigbe Reveals #URL# #URL#", "No Pay No Work – ASUU Strike Looms #URL# #URL#", "If You Are Dating A Married Man You Need To Be Cashing Out – Mercy Aigbe #URL# #URL#", "Nigeria Is The 7th Most Populated Country In the World – See List #URL# #URL#", "One of Bill Gates Daughters Is Off The Singles Market #URL# #URL#", "Transfer News As Of 30-01-2020 #URL# #URL#", "Concerns Over Nuno’s Future At Wolves? #URL# #URL#", "Uche Elendu and Oge Okoye Accused of Sleeping With Married Men || See Photos #URL# #URL#", "Pastor Arrested After 20 People Dies In His Church #URL# #URL#", "Governor-Elect Of Bayelsa Got Sacked By Supreme Court #URL# #URL#", "Nigeria Listed As A High Risk Country For Coronavirus #URL# #URL#", "Eedris Abdulkareem Arrested For Allegedly Assaulting His Landlord #URL# #URL#", "New Super Eagle Kit Unveiled #URL# #URL#", "The Publishing Of A Fake News Caused My Wife To Have A Miscariage – Olukayode Salako #URL# #URL#", "Romantic Movies To Go See At the Cinema Today – Valentine’s Day #URL# #URL#", "Joro Reveals Why Marriages And Relationship Suffers #URL# #URL#", "Yvonne Jegede hocking Revelation About Her Marriage #URL# #URL#", "Transfer News As Of 26-01-2020 #URL# #URL#", "EPL to Tweak VAR Rulings #URL# #URL#", "Jealous Husband Resulted To Unprecedented Measure || Find Out #URL# #URL#", "Why Can’t He Give Me A Womb – Brobrisky Laments #URL# #URL#", "How To Make Money With Clixsense From The Comfort Of Your Home #URL# #URL#", "Secret Behind DAvid Lyon’s Misfortune Revealed #URL# #URL#", "Jay Z and Beyonce Were Sitted During The National Anthem – See Reason #URL# #URL#", "Transfer News As Of 28-01-2020 #URL# #URL#", "New Bokoharam Attack Death Toll Is About 30 #URL# #URL#", "The Legend of Inikpi Sets A New Record #URL# #URL#", "Iyanya Arraigned For Stealing A Car #URL# #URL#", "Portharcour Landlord Declares Marlians Persona Non Grata In His House #URL# #URL#", "Transfer News As of 27-01-2020 #URL# #URL#", "Ighalo and Olè walked into a bar...", "Naira Marley Was Hacked #URL# #URL#", "What Sanwo-Olu Should Do After The Protest By Lagosians – Jimi Agbaje Reveals #URL# #URL#", "Chelsea Very Close To Signing Ziyech #URL# #URL#", "Man Threatens Murder Just To Divorce His Wife In Court #URL#", "Ondo State Government Approved A Draft Bill Of Amotekun Corps #URL# #URL#", "England Gets Boost Ahead of Euro 2020 #URL# #URL#", "Transfer News As Of 29-01-2020 #URL# #URL#", "Us Visa Ban Will Be Reversed #URL# #URL#", "Bishop Oyedepo Plans To Spend 10bn Naira For Churches #URL# #URL#", "Davido And Chioma Seen On A Jet Amidst Breakup Rumours #URL# #URL#", "Good News For Corpers – Allawee Has Been Increased #URL# #URL#", "Record Breaking Liverpool – Find Out The Potential Records They could break #URL# #URL#", "Nigerian Singer Electrocuted To death On Stage #URL# #URL#", "Nollywood Should Stop Promoting Money Ritual And Kidnapping – Fashola speaks #URL# #URL#", "Will Smith Almost Beat Up Another Actor On Set #URL# #URL#", "MC Oluomo Reacts To Motorcycle and Tricycle Ban In Lagos State #URL# #URL#", "Ycee Slams Vic O Over Rap Battle Challenge #URL# #URL#", "Messi Came For Sporting Director Eric Abidal #URL# #URL#", "Good News For Titans – New Tvshow “Keeping Up With Tacha” #URL# #URL#", "Toke Makinwa Display Her Camel Toe In Biker Short || See Photos #URL# #URL#", "I Was Emotionally Abused – Selena Gomez Opens Up #URL# #URL#", "Jcole Finally Bags His First Grammys – See Full List Of Winners #URL# #URL#", "Many Artiste Were Pained That Burna Boy Got Nominated For Grammy’s – Erriga #URL# #URL#", "UEFA Bans Manchester City For The Next Two Seasons #URL# #URL#", "Nigerian Banks Becomes New Target For Russian Hackers #URL# #URL#", "Liam Hensworth and Miley Cyrus Divorce is Finally Official #URL# #URL#", "Olamide’s New Look Shocks Everyone #URL# #URL#", "Pep Wants Messi To Stay In Barcelona #URL# #URL#", "Neymar Injured Yet Again Days After His Birthday #URL# #URL#", "RT #USER#: Here is an easy step-by-step guide to on how to apply for the Tony Elumelu Foundation Entrepreneurship Programme.  Visi…", "Woman Tries Too Kill Herself After Finding Herself In A Depressing Situation #URL# #URL#", "Paul Okoye Accuses National Copyright Commission Of Kidnapping #URL# #URL#", "Reno Omokri Explains Why Side Chicks Look Hotter Than The Wives #URL# #URL#", "I Am The Best Since Fela Kuti – Burna Boy #URL# #URL#", "Horrifying News-Kobe Bryant Is Dead #URL# #URL#", "Couple Became The First Nigerians To Finish The Lagos Marathon Race #URL# #URL#"], "ents": [[["Henderson", "PERSON"]], [["Fireboy", "PERSON"], ["1", "CARDINAL"]], [["Tonto Dikeh", "PERSON"]], [["Nollywood", "GPE"]], [["Yvonne Nelson", "PERSON"], ["Christians", "NORP"]], [["Deadline Day", "DATE"], ["Summer", "DATE"]], [["Nigerians", "NORP"], ["Grammys  ", "PERSON"]], [["George To Become A Citizen Of", "PERSON"], ["Togo", "GPE"]], [["Patoranking", "PERSON"], ["150", "CARDINAL"]], [["Nicki Minaj", "PERSON"], ["Kendrick Lamar", "PERSON"]], [["Manchester City’s", "GPE"]], [["Shina Peters", "PERSON"]], [["Obiano", "PERSON"], ["Yansh", "PERSON"]], [["Crepaway Restaurant", "ORG"], ["Chioma  ", "PERSON"]], [], [], [], [["Pep Guardiola", "PERSON"], ["Manchester", "GPE"]], [], [["New US Immigration Laws", "ORG"], ["Nigerians", "NORP"]], [], [["Two", "CARDINAL"]], [["Barcelona", "GPE"]], [["Victoria Inyama", "PERSON"]], [], [["New NCC Rule –", "ORG"], ["4", "CARDINAL"]], [], [["Benson  ", "PERSON"]], [], [["Zlatan", "GPE"], ["Olamide", "NORP"]], [["Poch", "PERSON"], ["Manchester United Next", "ORG"]], [["Peruzzi", "PERSON"]], [["BBNaija Star", "ORG"], ["Nina Got Married", "PERSON"]], [], [], [], [["Nigeria", "GPE"], ["7th", "ORDINAL"], ["Most Populated Country In the World", "EVENT"]], [["One", "CARDINAL"]], [["30-01-2020", "DATE"]], [["Nuno", "PERSON"]], [["Uche Elendu", "ORG"], ["Oge Okoye", "PERSON"], ["Sleeping With Married Men || See ", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["20", "CARDINAL"]], [], [["Nigeria", "GPE"]], [["Eedris Abdulkareem", "PERSON"]], [["New Super Eagle Kit", "ORG"]], [["The Publishing Of A Fake News Caused My Wife To", "ORG"], ["Salako  ", "PERSON"]], [["Valentine", "PERSON"]], [], [["Yvonne Jegede hocking", "PERSON"]], [["26-01-2020", "DATE"]], [["EPL", "ORG"], ["Tweak VAR ", "ORG"]], [], [], [], [], [["Jay Z", "PERSON"], ["Beyonce", "PERSON"], ["Sitted", "PERSON"]], [["28-01-2020", "DATE"]], [["New Bokoharam", "PERSON"], ["30", "CARDINAL"]], [], [["Iyanya", "GPE"]], [["Portharcour Landlord", "PERSON"]], [["27-01-2020", "DATE"]], [["Ighalo", "ORG"], ["Olè", "PRODUCT"]], [], [["Sanwo-Olu Should", "ORG"], ["Jimi Agbaje", "PERSON"]], [["Chelsea", "PERSON"], ["Ziyech  ", "PERSON"]], [], [["Ondo State Government Approved A Draft", "ORG"], ["Amotekun", "ORG"]], [["England", "GPE"], ["2020", "CARDINAL"]], [["29-01-2020", "DATE"]], [["Us", "GPE"]], [["Bishop Oyedepo Plans", "PERSON"]], [["Davido", "PERSON"]], [["Allawee", "PERSON"]], [], [["Nigerian", "NORP"]], [["Nollywood", "GPE"], ["Fashola", "PERSON"]], [["Smith", "PERSON"]], [["MC Oluomo", "PERSON"], ["Lagos", "GPE"]], [["Ycee", "ORG"]], [["Messi", "PERSON"], ["Eric", "PERSON"]], [], [["Toke Makinwa", "PERSON"]], [], [["Jcole", "PERSON"], ["Grammys", "PERSON"]], [["Grammy", "PERSON"], ["Erriga  ", "PERSON"]], [["UEFA", "GPE"], ["Manchester City", "GPE"], ["Two", "CARDINAL"]], [["Nigerian", "NORP"], ["Russian", "NORP"]], [["Liam Hensworth", "PERSON"], ["Miley Cyrus Divorce", "ORG"]], [["Olamide", "ORG"]], [["Messi", "PERSON"], ["Barcelona", "GPE"]], [["Neymar", "PERSON"]], [["the Tony Elumelu Foundation Entrepreneurship Programme", "ORG"]], [], [["Paul Okoye", "PERSON"], ["National Copyright Commission Of", "ORG"]], [["Reno Omokri", "PERSON"]], [["Fela Kuti", "PERSON"]], [], [["Nigerians", "NORP"]]], "POS_tags": [[{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADV", "AUX", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "NUM", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "SPACE", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "SPACE", "PRON", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "SPACE", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PART", "ADV", "VERB", "DET", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADV", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "ADV", "AUX", "SPACE", "ADV", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "SPACE", "X", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADJ", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NUM", "NOUN", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "CCONJ", "ADV", "AUX", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["INTJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "DET", "VERB", "VERB", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "PRON", "AUX", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "PRON", "AUX", "PART", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "DET", "VERB", "VERB", "SPACE", "ADV", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "AUX", "SPACE", "ADV", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "AUX", "SPACE", "ADJ", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "ADP", "NUM", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "AUX", "VERB", "PRON", "PROPN", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "AUX", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "AUX", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PRON", "CCONJ", "VERB", "PART", "AUX", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PRON", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADJ", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "AUX", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["SCONJ", "PRON", "AUX", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "PART", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "DET", "ADJ", "ADV", "ADJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "ADP", "SPACE", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "ADP", "SPACE", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "SCONJ", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PROPN", "ADP", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADV", "VERB", "DET", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADV", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "SPACE", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "ADP", "SPACE", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NUM", "VERB", "SPACE", "ADV", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "VERB", "PART", "PRON", "VERB", "PRON", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "SPACE", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "SPACE", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "AUX", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "ADP", "SPACE", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADV", "SPACE", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "ADP", "SPACE", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PROPN", "AUX", "SPACE", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "AUX", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADV", "ADV", "ADP", "VERB", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADP", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "SPACE", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "ADP", "SPACE", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "AUX", "SPACE", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "AUX", "AUX", "SPACE", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PRON", "VERB", "SPACE", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "SPACE", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PROPN", "ADV", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "SPACE", "VERB", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "ADP", "SPACE", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "X", "VERB", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "AUX", "ADV", "VERB", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "SPACE", "ADV", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADV", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADJ", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "NUM", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADV", "SPACE", "ADJ", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PRON", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "ADV", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["SPACE", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "AUX", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADP", "ADV", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "VERB", "PRON", "ADP", "VERB", "PRON", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADV", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADJ", "SCONJ", "DET", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "AUX", "DET", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "SPACE", "INTJ", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "SPACE", "ADJ", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "SPACE"]}]], "clean": ["henderson poise to win the pfa player of the year", "fireboy could possibly be wande coal number fan", "tonto dikeh get sue for defamation by -pron- ex husband", "nollywood actress leave -pron- marriage due fear for -pron- life see who", "yvonne nelson have an advise for christians", "deadline day missed deal upcome summer deal", "meet the nigerians to ever won the grammys", "bode george to become a citizen of togo", "patoranking reveal how -pron- take care of child from -pron- village", "nicki minaj have never collaborate with kendrick lamar and here be why", "extreme weather causes manchester city match postponement", "woman should share -pron- husband with side chicks sir shina peters wife", "governor obiano love yansh more than matters of the state", "new brand ambassador for crepaway restaurant chioma", "live faith bomber be not carry a bomb", "which club make the high profit in the last transfer window", "popular fruit -pron- eat and probably do know -pron- name", "pep guardiola advise to leave manchester city", "ex boyfriend disrupt wedding organize with -pron- money", "new us immigration law that could affect nigerians", "people believe -pron- be rich but -pron- be not tacha reveal in a video", "painter impregnates two student in the university of ibadan", "real madrid and barcelona both got knock out", "victoria inyama have stop take -pron- kid to church here be why", "popular snapchat queen hajia pussy be dead", "new ncc rule bad news for those with sim", "cardi b reveal when -pron- will be release -pron- next album", "masturbation be a beautiful thing stephanie benson", "deadline day transfer news", "zlatan rates olamide over pastor", "poch may be manchester united next coach", "peruzzi defraud -pron- and try to have -pron- way with -pron- daffy blanco", "bbnaija star nina got married in imo see photo", "marriage be overated mercy aigbe reveal", "no pay no work asuu strike loom", "if -pron- be date a married man -pron- need to be cash out mercy aigbe", "nigeria be the most populated country in the world see list", "one of bill gates daughters be off the singles market", "transfer news as of", "concerns over nuno future at wolf", "uche elendu and oge okoye accuse of sleep with married man see photo", "pastor arrested after people die in -pron- church", "governor elect of bayelsa got sack by supreme court", "nigeria list as a high risk country for coronavirus", "eedris abdulkareem arrest for allegedly assault -pron- landlord", "new super eagle kit unveil", "the publishing of a fake news cause -pron- wife to have a miscariage olukayode salako", "romantic movie to go see at the cinema today valentine day", "joro reveal why marriages and relationship suffer", "yvonne jegede hocking revelation about -pron- marriage", "transfer news as of", "epl to tweak var ruling", "jealous husband result to unprecedented measure find out", "why can -pron- give -pron- a womb brobrisky lament", "how to make money with clixsense from the comfort of -pron- home", "secret behind david lyon misfortune reveal", "jay z and beyonce be sitted during the national anthem see reason", "transfer news as of", "new bokoharam attack death toll be about", "the legend of inikpi set a new record", "iyanya arraigned for steal a car", "portharcour landlord declare marlians persona non grata in -pron- house", "transfer news as of", "ighalo and olè walk into a bar", "naira marley be hack", "what sanwo olu should do after the protest by lagosians jimi agbaje reveal", "chelsea very close to sign ziyech", "man threaten murder just to divorce -pron- wife in court", "ondo state government approve a draft bill of amotekun corps", "england get boost ahead of euro", "transfer news as of", "us visa ban will be reverse", "bishop oyedepo plan to spend naira for church", "davido and chioma see on a jet amidst breakup rumours", "good news for corpers allawee have be increase", "record breaking liverpool find out the potential records -pron- could break", "nigerian singer electrocute to death on stage", "nollywood should stop promote money ritual and kidnapping fashola speak", "will smith almost beat up another actor on set", "mc oluomo react to motorcycle and tricycle ban in lagos state", "ycee slams vic o over rap battle challenge", "messi come for sporting director eric abidal", "good news for titans new tvshow keep up with tacha", "toke makinwa display -pron- camel toe in biker short see photo", "-pron- be emotionally abuse selena gomez open up", "jcole finally bag -pron- first grammys see full list of winner", "many artiste be pained that burna boy got nominate for grammy erriga", "uefa ban manchester city for the next two season", "nigerian bank become new target for russian hacker", "liam hensworth and miley cyrus divorce be finally official", "olamide new look shock everyone", "pep want messi to stay in barcelona", "neymar injured yet again day after -pron- birthday", "user here be an easy step by step guide to on how to apply for the tony elumelu foundation entrepreneurship programme visi", "woman try too kill -pron- after find -pron- in a depressing situation", "paul okoye accuse national copyright commission of kidnapping", "reno omokri explain why side chick look hot than the wife", "-pron- be the best since fela kuti burna boy", "horrifying news kobe bryant be dead", "couple become the first nigerians to finish the lagos marathon race"]}