{"py/object": "data.Author", "author_id": "jmkq5i3hibtrv4v20g9hjnkplucfai6d", "truth": 0, "tweets": ["How the Iowa caucuses came ‘crashing down,’ under watchful eye of DNC #URL#", "Questions swirl around whether Bloomberg will make Las Vegas debate #URL#", "Some anxiousness as moderates split Democratic vote #URL#", "Trump pushed CIA to find bin Laden's son over higher priority targets #URL#", "Aide defends Trump tweets: 'very effective way' to communicate #URL#", "I want to give $100,000 a year to my kids but not to my stepdaughter #URL#", "For years, Bloomberg fought claims of profane, sexist comments #URL#", "Barr complained to president 'for weeks' about tweets, source says #URL#", "Trump quoting Emerson to refer to himself as 'the King' sparks outrage #URL#", "How country music star Tim McGraw stays fit on tour #URL#", "Trump speaks with Turkey's Erdogan amid growing tensions in Syria #URL#", "AOC lowers expectations on achieving Medicare for All if Sanders wins #URL#", "Master of false news gives right-wing Americans headlines they believe #URL#", "Which are the least tax-friendly states in America? California doesn’t crack the top 10, but Illinois sure does #URL#", "Pelosi defends decision to rip Trump's State of the Union address #URL#", "Vermont governor endorses Bill Weld for GOP presidential nomination #URL#", "Diversity test: 2020 Democrats seek their fortunes in Nevada #URL#", "Analysis: Trump looks to rev up his base at Daytona 500 #URL#", "Trump campaign manager tweets photo of big crowd near Air Force One from 2004 #URL#", "Senate braces for fight over impeachment whistleblower testimony #URL#", "2019's Social Security raise was downright pathetic, data shows #URL#", "Trump impeachment lawyer scolds him for tweeting about Stone case #URL#", "Senate Democrats say Trump administration skimps on virus fight #URL#", "Roger Stone asks for new trial in sealed motion #URL#", "Senators reaffirm Ukraine support at first meeting since impeachment #URL#", "Iowa Democratic Party names new chairman after caucus chaos #URL#", "A struggling Elizabeth Warren spends 30 minutes on the press bus #URL#", "They Documented the Coronavirus Crisis in Wuhan. Then They Vanished. #URL#", "Police detain Rashida Tlaib during low wages protest at Detroit airport #URL#", "Harry Reid says Biden will do well in diverse Nevada's caucuses #URL#", "GOP senator on Trump: 'Tweeting less would not cause brain damage' #URL#", "Rival Democrats accuse Mike Bloomberg of trying to 'buy' election #URL#", "Barr-Trump relationship is facing its gravest threat yet #URL#", "Nikola reveals Badger electric pickup truck with 600-mile range #URL#", "Warren urged to revive fighter persona after 'unity' pitch falls flat #URL#", "AOC calls for 'turnout machine' as 12 Dem rivals eye her House seat #URL#", "Analysis: A Presidency Increasingly Guided by Suspicion and Distrust #URL#", "Nasty rivalry cast aside as Ted Cruz worked to save Trump's presidency #URL#", "'Something has to be done': Trump's quest to rewrite history of Russia probe #URL#", "In Nevada, Amy Klobuchar's shifts on immigration are under scrutiny #URL#", "William Barr's actions spark unease among U.S. prosecutors #URL#", "Analysis: Another case Trump meddled in, another Barr intervention #URL#", "Bernie Sanders leads Democratic field in latest Nevada poll #URL#", "Investigation of Russia probe looks at '3 important things,' Gowdy says #URL#", "Trump, Barr fuel DOJ turmoil over cases tied to White House #URL#", "Bernie Sanders Is on the Rise. But How High Can His Numbers Go? #URL#", "Family builds $3.8 billion fortune 1 pint of blood at a time #URL#", "This man paid off his $300K house in 3 months. Here's why didn't invest the money #URL#", "I’ve Been Plastic-Free for 6 Years—Here’s What I Use Instead #URL#", "Dairies are desperate to get Americans to drink milk again #URL#", "A Twist in California’s Homeless Crisis: Evictions by the Evicted #URL#", "Sanders tears into Bloomberg, says Dem billionaire can't beat Trump #URL#", "McCabe: 'I don't think I will ever be free of’ Trump #URL#", "Donald Trump expected to raise $10 million during Florida stop #URL#", "Senate Democrats pressure Trump to drop ObamaCare lawsuit #URL#", "House uses Trump impeachment team arguments in suit seeking tax returns #URL#", "Bloomberg’s Billions: How the Candidate Built an Empire of Influence #URL#", "Doctors on the signs of heart failure everyone should be able to recognize #URL#", "WH Memo Justifying Suleimani Strike Cites No Imminent Threat #URL#", "This warehouse of JDM jewels is tucked away in small-town Virginia #URL#", "Deep cracks emerge in Joe Biden’s firewall state of South Carolina #URL#", "Former No. 2 U.S. intel official 'didn't want to be anyone's agenda' #URL#", "Ala. Senate contender's ad hits Sessions: 'Hillary still ain't in jail' #URL#", "Trump’s soft touch with China’s Xi on coronavirus worries some advisers #URL#", "Las Vegas precinct shows people waiting 3.5 hours for early voting #URL#", "How Jerry Seinfeld found Steve McQueen's Porsche 917 on a used car lot #URL#", "Inside the president's week of rage and retribution #URL#", "Meet the Nigerian Buttigeig fan whose 'It’s Lis’ tweet created a stir #URL#", "Powerful Ukrainian playing both sides of Giuliani's Ukraine project #URL#", "Sally Yates blasts Trump for using DOJ as 'personal grudge squad' #URL#", "Democrats Look Ahead From Nevada and See a Common Enemy: Bloomberg #URL#", "Trump repeats the same stories, but the details often change #URL#", "Emerging GOP climate change strategy aims to court young conservatives #URL#", "Your foam coffee cup is fighting for its life #URL#", "Deporting 3 million 'was a big mistake,' Joe Biden tells Univision #URL#", "Dem presidential hopefuls take aim at red Texas as Super Tuesday looms #URL#", "President gives command for Daytona 500 drivers to start their engines #URL#", "Scandal-plagued Bronx politician plots against AOC #URL#", "Why claiming Social Security is really just a gamble #URL#", "1,100 ex-Justice Department officials call for Barr to resign #URL#", "Trump, William Barr, Roger Stone made for turbulent week at DOJ #URL#", "What is a million-mile truck actually worth? #URL#", "Fearful of Trump’s Attacks, Justice Dept. Lawyers Worry Barr Will Leave Them Exposed #URL#", "This is why you should never paint your house a dark color #URL#", "District court judge sets Tuesday phone hearing in Roger Stone case #URL#", "Analysis: The Democratic nomination contest doesn't look like any from the past #URL#", "Prosecutor says Flynn review is ruse for new probe into former FBI men #URL#", "Graham requests DOJ, FBI interviews in probe into Russia investigation #URL#", "Defense secretary defends OKing Trump shifting of funds to border wall #URL#", "This Is Why Airplanes Make Weird Noises Before Take-off #URL#", "Sanders' 'Medicare-for-all' in crosshairs of powerful Nevada union #URL#", "Democratic campaigns warn of chaos ahead of the Nevada caucuses #URL#", "What you should know about walking for weight loss #URL#", "Campaign downplays report of possible Bloomberg-Clinton ticket #URL#", "In interview, Amy Klobuchar, Tom Steyer can't name Mexican president #URL#", "Why would a billionaire charge the Secret Service $650 a night? #URL#", "Biden Calls on Sanders to Show Accountability for 'Outrageous' Online Threats by Followers #URL#", "Barr calls for outside prosecutor to review the Flynn case #URL#", "After split results, Democrats brace for a long primary. Just what Bloomberg wants. #URL#", "Here's why more travelers are joining the 'do not tip' movement #URL#"], "ents": [[["Iowa", "GPE"], ["DNC", "ORG"]], [["Bloomberg", "ORG"], ["Las Vegas", "GPE"]], [["Democratic", "NORP"]], [["Trump", "ORG"], ["CIA", "ORG"], ["bin Laden's", "PERSON"]], [["Trump", "ORG"]], [["100,000", "MONEY"]], [["years", "DATE"], ["Bloomberg", "ORG"]], [["Barr", "ORG"], ["weeks", "DATE"]], [["Emerson", "PERSON"]], [["Tim McGraw", "PERSON"]], [["Trump", "ORG"], ["Turkey", "GPE"], ["Erdogan", "ORG"], ["Syria", "GPE"]], [["Medicare", "ORG"], ["Sanders", "PERSON"]], [["Americans", "NORP"]], [["America", "GPE"], ["California", "GPE"], ["10", "CARDINAL"], ["Illinois", "GPE"]], [["Pelosi", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "ORG"]], [["Vermont", "GPE"], ["Bill Weld", "PERSON"], ["GOP", "ORG"]], [["2020", "CARDINAL"], ["Democrats", "NORP"], ["Nevada", "GPE"]], [["Trump", "ORG"]], [["Trump", "ORG"], ["Air Force One", "PRODUCT"], ["2004", "DATE"]], [["Senate", "ORG"]], [["2019", "DATE"], ["Social Security", "ORG"]], [["Stone", "ORG"]], [["Senate", "ORG"], ["Democrats", "NORP"], ["Trump", "ORG"]], [["Roger Stone", "PERSON"]], [["Ukraine", "GPE"], ["first", "ORDINAL"]], [["Iowa Democratic Party", "ORG"]], [["Elizabeth Warren", "PERSON"], ["30 minutes", "TIME"]], [["Wuhan", "GPE"]], [["Rashida Tlaib", "PERSON"], ["Detroit", "GPE"]], [["Harry Reid", "PERSON"], ["Biden", "NORP"], ["Nevada", "GPE"]], [["GOP", "ORG"], ["Trump", "ORG"]], [["Democrats", "NORP"], ["Mike Bloomberg", "PERSON"]], [["Barr-Trump", "ORG"]], [["Nikola", "ORG"], ["Badger", "ORG"]], [["Warren", "ORG"]], [["12", "CARDINAL"], ["Dem", "NORP"], ["House", "ORG"]], [], [["Ted Cruz", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "ORG"]], [["Trump", "ORG"], ["Russia", "GPE"]], [["Nevada", "GPE"], ["Amy Klobuchar's", "PERSON"]], [["William Barr's", "PERSON"], ["U.S.", "GPE"]], [["Trump", "ORG"], ["Barr", "PERSON"]], [["Bernie Sanders", "PERSON"], ["Democratic", "NORP"], ["Nevada", "GPE"]], [["Russia", "GPE"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["Gowdy", "PERSON"]], [["Trump", "ORG"], ["Barr", "ORG"], ["DOJ", "ORG"], ["White House", "ORG"]], [["Bernie Sanders", "PERSON"]], [["$3.8 billion", "MONEY"]], [["300", "MONEY"], ["3 months", "DATE"]], [["6 Years", "DATE"]], [["Americans", "NORP"]], [["Twist", "ORG"], ["California", "GPE"]], [["Sanders", "PERSON"], ["Bloomberg", "ORG"], ["Dem", "NORP"]], [], [["Donald Trump", "PERSON"], ["$10 million", "MONEY"], ["Florida", "GPE"]], [["Senate", "ORG"], ["Democrats", "NORP"], ["Trump", "ORG"], ["ObamaCare", "ORG"]], [["House", "ORG"], ["Trump", "ORG"]], [["Bloomberg", "ORG"], ["Billions: How the Candidate Built an Empire of Influence", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [], [], [["JDM", "ORG"], ["Virginia", "GPE"]], [["Joe Biden’s", "PERSON"], ["South Carolina", "GPE"]], [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["U.S.", "GPE"]], [["Ala. Senate", "ORG"], ["Sessions: 'Hillary still ai", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Trump", "ORG"], ["China", "GPE"], ["Xi", "PERSON"]], [["Las Vegas", "GPE"], ["3.5 hours", "TIME"]], [["Jerry Seinfeld", "PERSON"], ["Steve McQueen's", "PERSON"], ["Porsche 917", "PRODUCT"]], [], [["Nigerian", "NORP"], ["Buttigeig", "PERSON"], ["Lis", "PERSON"]], [["Ukrainian", "NORP"], ["Giuliani", "PERSON"], ["Ukraine", "GPE"]], [["Sally Yates", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "ORG"], ["DOJ", "ORG"]], [["Democrats", "NORP"], ["Nevada", "GPE"]], [["Trump", "ORG"]], [["GOP", "ORG"]], [], [["3 million", "CARDINAL"], ["Joe Biden", "PERSON"], ["Univision", "ORG"]], [["Dem", "NORP"], ["Texas", "GPE"], ["Tuesday", "DATE"]], [["Daytona 500", "ORG"]], [["Bronx", "GPE"]], [["Social Security", "ORG"]], [["1,100", "CARDINAL"], ["ex-Justice Department", "ORG"], ["Barr", "PERSON"]], [["Trump", "ORG"], ["William Barr", "PERSON"], ["Roger Stone", "PERSON"], ["week", "DATE"], ["DOJ", "ORG"]], [["a million-mile", "QUANTITY"]], [["Trump", "ORG"], ["Attacks", "ORG"], ["Justice Dept", "ORG"]], [], [["Tuesday", "DATE"], ["Roger Stone", "PERSON"]], [["Democratic", "NORP"]], [["Flynn", "PERSON"], ["FBI", "ORG"]], [["Graham", "PERSON"], ["DOJ", "ORG"], ["FBI", "ORG"], ["Russia", "GPE"]], [["Defense", "ORG"], ["OKing Trump", "ORG"]], [], [["Sanders", "ORG"], ["Medicare", "ORG"], ["Nevada", "GPE"]], [["Democratic", "NORP"], ["Nevada", "GPE"]], [], [["Caign", "ORG"], ["Bloomberg-Clinton", "ORG"]], [["Amy Klobuchar", "PERSON"], ["Tom Steyer", "PERSON"], ["Mexican", "NORP"]], [["the Secret Service", "ORG"], ["650", "MONEY"]], [["Biden", "NORP"], ["Sanders", "PERSON"]], [["Barr", "ORG"], ["Flynn", "PERSON"]], [["Democrats", "NORP"], ["Bloomberg", "ORG"]], []], "POS_tags": [[{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PART", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "SYM", "NUM", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "PART", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "NOUN", "PART", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PRON", "SCONJ", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "AUX", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "AUX", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NUM", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "ADV", "AUX"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["X", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADV", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PRON", "ADP", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "VERB", "AUX", "ADV", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADV", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "PART", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "AUX", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "SCONJ", "NUM", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "ADV", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PRON", "AUX", "PART", "AUX", "VERB", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADV", "ADJ", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "SYM", "NUM", "NUM", "NOUN", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "SYM", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "AUX", "ADV", "AUX", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "AUX", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "VERB", "PRON", "PRON", "VERB", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "AUX", "ADJ", "PART", "AUX", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PRON", "AUX", "PART", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "ADV", "AUX", "ADJ", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "SYM", "NUM", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "AUX", "ADJ", "PART", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "AUX", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "AUX", "PART", "VERB", "PART", "AUX", "PRON", "PART", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADV", "VERB", "PART", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "VERB", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "NUM", "ADP", "DET", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "DET", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "ADJ", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "DET", "NOUN", "ADV", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "NOUN", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "NUM", "NUM", "PUNCT", "AUX", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADV", "ADV", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "AUX", "DET", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADJ", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "AUX", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "ADV", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "AUX", "PART", "VERB", "SCONJ", "DET", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "AUX", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "AUX", "ADV", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "VERB", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PUNCT", "DET", "PUNCT", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SYM", "NUM", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PRON", "PROPN", "VERB", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "AUX", "ADV", "ADJ", "NOUN", "AUX", "VERB", "DET", "PUNCT", "AUX", "PART", "VERB", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}]], "clean": ["how the iowa caucus come crash down under watchful eye of dnc", "question swirl around whether bloomberg will make las vegas debate", "some anxiousness as moderate split democratic vote", "trump push cia to find bin laden son over high priority target", "aide defend trump tweet very effective way to communicate", "-pron- want to give a year to -pron- kid but not to -pron- stepdaughter", "for year bloomberg fight claim of profane sexist comment", "barr complain to president for week about tweet source say", "trump quote emerson to refer to -pron- as the king spark outrage", "how country music star tim mcgraw stay fit on tour", "trump speak with turkey erdogan amid grow tension in syria", "aoc lower expectation on achieve medicare for all if sanders win", "master of false news give right wing americans headline -pron- believe", "which be the least tax friendly state in america california do crack the top but illinois sure do", "pelosi defend decision to rip trump state of the union address", "vermont governor endorse bill weld for gop presidential nomination", "diversity test democrats seek -pron- fortune in nevada", "analysis trump look to rev up -pron- base at daytona", "trump caign manager tweet photo of big crowd near air force one from", "senate brace for fight over impeachment whistleblower testimony", "social security raise be downright pathetic datum show", "trump impeachment lawyer scold -pron- for tweet about stone case", "senate democrats say trump administration skimp on virus fight", "roger stone ask for new trial in seal motion", "senator reaffirm ukraine support at first meeting since impeachment", "iowa democratic party name new chairman after caucus chaos", "a struggle elizabeth warren spend minute on the press bus", "-pron- document the coronavirus crisis in wuhan then -pron- vanish", "police detain rashida tlaib during low wage protest at detroit airport", "harry reid say biden will do well in diverse nevada caucus", "gop senator on trump tweet less would not cause brain damage", "rival democrats accuse mike bloomberg of try to buy election", "barr trump relationship be face -pron- grave threat yet", "nikola reveal badger electric pickup truck with range", "warren urge to revive fighter persona after unity pitch fall flat", "aoc call for turnout machine as dem rival eye -pron- house seat", "analysis a presidency increasingly guide by suspicion and distrust", "nasty rivalry cast aside as ted cruz work to save trump presidency", "something have to be do trump quest to rewrite history of russia probe", "in nevada amy klobuchar shift on immigration be under scrutiny", "william barr action spark unease among prosecutor", "analysis another case trump meddle in another barr intervention", "bernie sanders lead democratic field in late nevada poll", "investigation of russia probe look at important thing gowdy say", "trump barr fuel doj turmoil over case tie to white house", "bernie sanders be on the rise but how high can -pron- number go", "family build billion fortune pint of blood at a time", "this man pay off -pron- k house in month here why do invest the money", "-pron- be plastic free for year here what -pron- use instead", "dairy be desperate to get americans to drink milk again", "a twist in california homeless crisis eviction by the evicted", "sanders tear into bloomberg say dem billionaire can beat trump", "mccabe -pron- do think -pron- will ever be free of trump", "donald trump expect to raise million during florida stop", "senate democrats pressure trump to drop obamacare lawsuit", "house use trump impeachment team argument in suit seek tax return", "bloomberg billion how the candidate build an empire of influence", "doctor on the sign of heart failure everyone should be able to recognize", "wh memo justify suleimani strike cite no imminent threat", "this warehouse of jdm jewel be tuck away in small town virginia", "deep crack emerge in joe biden firewall state of south carolina", "former no intel official do want to be anyone agenda", "senate contender ad hit session hillary still be in jail", "trump soft touch with china xi on coronavirus worry some adviser", "las vegas precinct show people wait hour for early voting", "how jerry seinfeld find steve mcqueen porsche on a use car lot", "inside the president week of rage and retribution", "meet the nigerian buttigeig fan whose -pron- lis tweet create a stir", "powerful ukrainian play both side of giuliani ukraine project", "sally yates blast trump for use doj as personal grudge squad", "democrats look ahead from nevada and see a common enemy bloomberg", "trump repeat the same story but the detail often change", "emerge gop climate change strategy aim to court young conservative", "-pron- foam coffee cup be fight for -pron- life", "deport million be a big mistake joe biden tell univision", "dem presidential hopeful take aim at red texas as super tuesday loom", "president give command for daytona driver to start -pron- engine", "scandal plague bronx politician plot against aoc", "why claim social security be really just a gamble", "ex justice department official call for barr to resign", "trump william barr roger stone make for turbulent week at doj", "what be a million mile truck actually worth", "fearful of trump attacks justice dept lawyer worry barr will leave -pron- expose", "this be why -pron- should never paint -pron- house a dark color", "district court judge set tuesday phone hearing in roger stone case", "analysis the democratic nomination contest do look like any from the past", "prosecutor say flynn review be ruse for new probe into former fbi man", "graham request doj fbi interview in probe into russia investigation", "defense secretary defend oke trump shifting of fund to border wall", "this be why airplane make weird noise before take off", "sanders medicare for all in crosshair of powerful nevada union", "democratic caign warn of chaos ahead of the nevada caucus", "what -pron- should know about walk for weight loss", "caign downplay report of possible bloomberg clinton ticket", "in interview amy klobuchar tom steyer can name mexican president", "why would a billionaire charge the secret service a night", "biden call on sander to show accountability for outrageous online threats by follower", "barr call for outside prosecutor to review the flynn case", "after split result democrats brace for a long primary just what bloomberg want", "here why more traveler be join the do not tip movement"]}