{"author_id": "l7o357ot2banopizg7vid5tbso9h4y3m", "truth": 0, "tweets": ["His Novel’s Hero Is a Middle-Aged Canadian Catholic Professor. And a Suicide Bomber. #URL#", "Lyon Bombing Suspect Says He Pledged Allegiance to ISIS #URL#", "Leader of Smithsonian’s African American Museum to Direct Entire Institution #URL#", "Punching Iran Over Its Foreign Policy Could Lead to a Faster Path to War #URL#", "Watch Martha Graham’s Dance of Empowerment #URL#", "‘The Weekly’ Wants to Show You That ‘Reporters Are Not Robots’ #URL#", "Disney May Halt Productions in Georgia if Abortion Law Is Enforced #URL#", "An Impeccable Oberon, Flexing His Power #URL#", "Richard Prince and the New Meaning of High Art #URL#", "For Kishi Bashi, History Teaches Compassion #URL#", "What’s on TV Wednesday: ‘Archer’ and ‘The InBetween’ #URL#", "The Music Nearly Lost to AIDS #URL#", "What’s on TV Tuesday: ‘Running With Beto’ and ‘Songland’ #URL#", "Court Denies Italy’s Request for Return of Disputed da Vinci Work #URL#", "Were You at Woodstock 1969? #URL#", "The Best Movies and TV Shows New to Netflix, Amazon and More in June #URL#", "France Hands ISIS Suspects to Iraq, Which Sentences Them to Hang #URL#", "The Hand of Native American Women, Visible at Last #URL#", "Resonance Records to Stream Its Trove of Historical Jazz Albums #URL#", "When a Ballerina Gets to Be Goofy #URL#", "5 Comedy Shows to Catch in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#", "Merkel Tells Harvard Grads to Tear Down 'Walls of Ignorance' #URL#", "A Tibetan Collection Fights a Battle That Small Museums Often Face #URL#", "The Pop and Spark of ‘Too Darn Hot’ #URL#", "What to Do in New York This Weekend #URL#", "Review: In ‘Good Omens,’ Angel and Demon Try to Save the World #URL#", "The Central Park Five: ‘We Were Just Baby Boys’ #URL#", "Documents Suggest Prosecutors Quickly Changed Mind on Jussie Smollett Case #URL#", "The Central Park Five: ‘We Were Just Baby Boys’ #URL#", "New York Art Galleries: What to See Right Now #URL#", "What’s on TV Thursday: Ava DuVernay on ‘Desus &amp; Mero’ and ‘BlacKkKlansman’ #URL#", "6 Classical Music Concerts to See in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#", "‘Deadwood’: What to Remember for the HBO Movie #URL#", "This Summer, Opera Grapples With Race #URL#", "Iraq Sentences 2 More French IS Members to Death, 6 So Far #URL#", "Baltimore Symphony Musicians Are ‘Stunned’ After Concerts Are Canceled #URL#", "22 Art Exhibitions to View in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#", "The Leader Who Was ‘Trump Before Trump’ #URL#", "The Playlist: Cardi B Is Stressed, and 13 More New Songs #URL#", "Review: The Searing Power of an AIDS Symphony #URL#", "With ‘NOS4A2,’ Joe Hill Finally Sinks His Teeth Into TV #URL#", "When Resistance Became Too Loud to Ignore #URL#", "The Latest: Egypt's Leader Says Gulf Security Vital to Cairo #URL#", "Analysis: India's Modi Faces Foreign Pressures in 2nd Term #URL#", "Your House Is My House, Pakistan’s Rich Say to Its Poor #URL#", "Review: Angel and Demon Cross the Aisle to Save the World. (Sorry, It’s Fiction) #URL#", "Pakistan Arrests 6 Men for Raising Funds for Outlawed Group #URL#", "Lyon Bomb Suspect Had Pledged Allegiance to IS #URL#", "Some Enchanted Ending: Debuts and Other Spectacular Feats at City Ballet #URL#", "A Tibetan Collection Fights a Battle That Small Museums Often Face #URL#", "Turkey Frees American NASA Scientist Imprisoned for 2 Years #URL#", "How the Rockettes Fall Like Dominoes #URL#", "In Harvard Speech, Merkel Rebukes Trump’s Worldview in All but Name #URL#", "Disney May Halt Productions in Georgia if Abortion Law Is Enforced #URL#", "9 Things to Do With Your Kids in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#", "Florida Cabinet Meets in Israel Under Media Objection #URL#", "India's New Government Signals Hindu and India-First Goals #URL#", "Next Out of Prince’s Vaults: The Hits He Gave Away #URL#", "After a Scandal, the New Orleans Jazz Market Rises Again #URL#", "‘Time Is Up’: Pakistan’s Army Targets Protest Movement, Stifling Dissent #URL#", "The Best Movies and TV Shows New to Netflix Australia in June #URL#", "At This Techno Club, the Party Is Political #URL#", "Leonardo Drew Rides His Magic Carpet to a New Field #URL#", "Leader of Smithsonian’s African American Museum to Direct Entire Institution #URL#", "UN Assembly Remembers Victims of Violence Against Religion #URL#", "Iraq Hands Over 188 Turkish Children of Suspected IS Members #URL#", "12 Pop, Rock and Jazz Concerts to Check Out in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#", "The Latest: Florida Cabinet Meeting Underway in Jerusalem #URL#", "New Sexual Assault Charges Filed Against R. Kelly #URL#", "Harry Potter E-Books Offer Hogwarts Lessons for All #URL#", "Modi Begins Second Term as India’s Prime Minister After Crushing Victory #URL#", "Queer Muslims Are Still Rare on TV. One Writer Wants to Change That. #URL#", "Syria Rejects Arab Summit Statement on Iran Intervention #URL#", "The Latest: Saudi King Says Islamic Summit Confronts Threats #URL#", "What’s on TV Friday: ‘Deadwood: The Movie’ and ‘When They See Us’ #URL#", "Tyler, the Creator Beats DJ Khaled to Hit No. 1 With ‘Igor’ #URL#", "7 Dance Performances to See in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#", "Pride Events: Here’s How to Celebrate #URL#", "The Broken Saucers in Alan Faena’s House Are Purely Aesthetic #URL#", "Why Robert Mueller Should Testify on TV #URL#", "Review: Twyla Tharp’s Enduring ‘You Can Have It All’ Vision #URL#", "Where Subway Dancers Practice Their Art #URL#", "Art Festival Is Welcome, but Not the Huge Crowds #URL#", "Oklahoma City Bombing Trial Judge Richard Matsch Dies at 88 #URL#", "David Letterman 2.0, the Non-Ironic Version #URL#", "In Turkey, Keeping Alive a Language of Whistles #URL#", "Their Beach Opera Won at the Biennale. But They Can Hardly Afford It. #URL#", "France Calls on Iraq to Spare Six of Its Citizens From Death Penalty #URL#", "There’s Great Dance on Broadway. Hello, Tony Awards? #URL#", "The Best Movies and TV Shows New on Netflix Canada in June #URL#", "Two Transgender Activists Are Getting a Monument in New York #URL#", "‘When They See Us’ Transforms Its Victims Into Heroes #URL#", "Pakistan Sentences 3 to 5-Year in Jail Over Terror Financing #URL#", "How a City in Fear Brutalized the Central Park Five #URL#", "Still Pondering the End of ‘Game of Thrones’? Here’s What to Read About It #URL#", "On Walt Whitman’s Big Birthday, 10 Glorious Relics #URL#", "Review: In One Last ‘Deadwood,’ the Future Prevails and the Past Endures #URL#", "Japan Announces Aid to Bangladesh During Leader's Visit #URL#", "Arab Leaders Meet in Mecca to Unify Ranks Amid Iran Tensions #URL#", "‘Good Omens’ Unites an Angel and a Demon for Judgment Day #URL#"], "ents": [[["Canadian", "NORP"], ["a Suicide Bomber", "ORG"]], [["Lyon Bombing Suspect", "PERSON"]], [["Smithsonian", "ORG"], ["African American Museum", "ORG"]], [], [["Martha Graham", "PERSON"], ["Dance of Empowerment", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["The Weekly’ Wants to Show You That ‘Reporters Are Not Robots", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Disney May Halt Productions", "ORG"], ["Georgia", "GPE"], ["Law", "PERSON"]], [], [["Richard Prince", "PERSON"], ["the New Meaning of High Art", "ORG"]], [["Kishi Bashi", "PERSON"], ["History Teaches Compassion", "ORG"]], [["Wednesday", "DATE"], ["‘The InBetween’", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [], [["Tuesday", "DATE"], ["Running With Beto’", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Italy", "GPE"], ["Request for Return of Disputed da Vinci Work", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["1969", "DATE"]], [["Netflix", "GPE"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["June", "DATE"]], [["France", "GPE"], ["Iraq", "GPE"]], [], [], [], [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["This Weekend", "DATE"]], [["Merkel Tells", "PERSON"], ["Harvard Grads", "PERSON"]], [["Tibetan", "NORP"]], [], [["New York", "GPE"], ["This Weekend", "DATE"]], [["Angel", "PERSON"], ["Demon Try", "PERSON"]], [["Five", "CARDINAL"], ["We Were Just Baby Boys", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Jussie Smollett Case", "PERSON"]], [["Five", "CARDINAL"], ["We Were Just Baby Boys", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["New York Art Galleries", "GPE"]], [["Thursday", "DATE"], ["DuVernay", "PERSON"]], [["6", "CARDINAL"], ["This Weekend", "DATE"]], [["HBO", "ORG"]], [["This Summer", "DATE"], ["Opera Grapples With Race", "PERSON"]], [["Iraq", "GPE"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["French", "NORP"], ["6", "CARDINAL"]], [["Baltimore Symphony Musicians Are ‘", "PERSON"]], [["22", "CARDINAL"], ["This Weekend", "DATE"]], [["Trump Before Trump’", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["13", "CARDINAL"]], [], [["Joe Hill", "PERSON"]], [], [["Egypt", "GPE"], ["Cairo", "GPE"]], [["India", "GPE"], ["Modi Faces Foreign Pressures", "ORG"], ["2nd", "CARDINAL"]], [["House", "ORG"], ["Pakistan", "GPE"]], [["Angel", "ORG"], ["Demon Cross", "ORG"], ["Save the World", "ORG"]], [], [["Lyon Bomb", "PERSON"]], [["City Ballet", "ORG"]], [["Tibetan", "NORP"]], [["Turkey", "GPE"], ["American", "NORP"], ["NASA", "ORG"], ["2 Years", "DATE"]], [], [["Harvard Speech", "GPE"], ["Merkel Rebukes", "PERSON"]], [["Disney May Halt Productions", "ORG"], ["Georgia", "GPE"], ["Law", "PERSON"]], [["9", "CARDINAL"], ["This Weekend", "DATE"]], [["Florida Cabinet Meets", "ORG"], ["Israel", "GPE"]], [["India", "GPE"], ["Hindu", "NORP"], ["India", "GPE"]], [], [["New Orleans", "GPE"]], [["Pakistan", "GPE"], ["Army Targets Protest Movement", "ORG"], ["Stifling Dissent", "PERSON"]], [["Australia", "GPE"], ["June", "DATE"]], [["This Techno Club", "ORG"], ["Party", "ORG"]], [["Leonardo Drew Rides His Magic Carpet", "PERSON"], ["New Field", "GPE"]], [["Smithsonian", "ORG"], ["African American Museum", "ORG"]], [["UN Assembly Remembers Victims of Violence Against Religion", "ORG"]], [["Iraq", "GPE"], ["Over 188", "CARDINAL"], ["Turkish", "NORP"]], [["12", "CARDINAL"], ["This Weekend", "DATE"]], [["Florida Cabinet Meeting Underway", "ORG"], ["Jerusalem", "GPE"]], [["R. Kelly", "PERSON"]], [["Harry Potter E-", "PERSON"]], [["India", "GPE"]], [["Muslims", "NORP"], ["One", "CARDINAL"]], [["Syria", "GPE"], ["Arab", "NORP"]], [], [["Friday", "DATE"], ["Deadwood: The Movie", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["When They See Us", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Tyler", "ORG"], ["1", "CARDINAL"]], [["7", "CARDINAL"], ["This Weekend", "DATE"]], [], [["Alan Faena", "PERSON"], ["House", "ORG"]], [["Robert Mueller", "PERSON"]], [["You Can Have It All’ Vision", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [], [], [["Oklahoma City Bombing Trial", "EVENT"], ["Richard Matsch Dies", "PERSON"], ["88", "CARDINAL"]], [["David Letterman", "PERSON"], ["the Non-Ironic", "ORG"]], [["Turkey", "GPE"]], [["Biennale", "FAC"]], [["France", "GPE"], ["Six", "CARDINAL"]], [["Broadway", "FAC"], ["Tony Awards", "PERSON"]], [["Netflix Canada", "ORG"], ["June", "DATE"]], [["Two", "CARDINAL"], ["New York", "GPE"]], [], [["Pakistan", "GPE"], ["3", "CARDINAL"]], [], [], [["Walt Whitman", "PERSON"], ["10", "CARDINAL"]], [["One", "CARDINAL"], ["Deadwood", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Japan", "GPE"]], [["Arab", "NORP"], ["Mecca", "GPE"]], [["Omens", "PERSON"]]], "POS_tags": [[{"py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "AUX", "DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PRON", "SCONJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "AUX", "PART", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "X", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "ADV", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["AUX", "PRON", "ADP", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "VERB", "PRON", "PART", "VERB"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADV", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "AUX", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NUM", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADV", "VERB"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PRON", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PRON", "AUX", "ADV", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADV", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PRON", "AUX", "ADV", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "PART", "VERB", "ADV", "ADV"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PUNCT", "PRON", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PRON", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "NUM", "ADJ", "ADJ", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "ADV", "ADV"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT", "ADP", "NOUN", "AUX", "VERB"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "PRON", "AUX", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "NUM", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADP", "PUNCT", "X", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADV", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "ADJ", "ADP", "VERB"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "AUX", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "DET", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "INTJ", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "NUM", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADV", "VERB"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADV", "DET", "PROPN", "VERB", "SCONJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "SCONJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "AUX", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PRON", "VERB", "ADV"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "NOUN", "AUX", "ADV", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NUM", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "ADP", "PROPN", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADV", "ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "PRON", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NUM", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["X", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "VERB", "ADV", "PART", "VERB"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADV", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADV", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "AUX", "PRON", "DET", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADV", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PART", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NUM"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PRON", "VERB", "ADV", "VERB", "PRON", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "NUM", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "INTJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NUM", "PROPN", "NOUN", "AUX", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "PRON", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "ADP", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADV", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADV", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "ADV", "VERB", "PRON", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PRON"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "ADJ", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "NUM", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}]], "clean": ["-pron- novel hero be a middle aged canadian catholic professor and a suicide bomber", "lyon bombing suspect say -pron- pledge allegiance to isis", "leader of smithsonian african american museum to direct entire institution", "punch iran over -pron- foreign policy could lead to a fast path to war", "watch martha graham dance of empowerment", "the weekly want to show -pron- that reporter be not robot", "disney may halt productions in georgia if abortion law be enforce", "an impeccable oberon flex -pron- power", "richard prince and the new meaning of high art", "for kishi bashi history teach compassion", "what on tv wednesday archer and the inbetween", "the music nearly lose to aids", "what on tv tuesday run with beto and songland", "court deny italy request for return of dispute da vinci work", "be -pron- at woodstock", "the good movies and tv show new to netflix amazon and more in june", "france hands isis suspect to iraq which sentence -pron- to hang", "the hand of native american women visible at last", "resonance records to stream -pron- trove of historical jazz albums", "when a ballerina get to be goofy", "comedy show to catch in this weekend", "merkel tell harvard grad to tear down wall of ignorance", "a tibetan collection fight a battle that small museum often face", "the pop and spark of too darn hot", "what to do in new york this weekend", "review in good omens angel and demon try to save the world", "the central park five -pron- be just baby boy", "document suggest prosecutor quickly change mind on jussie smollett case", "the central park five -pron- be just baby boy", "new york art galleries what to see right now", "what on tv thursday ava duvernay on desus mero and blackkklansman", "classical music concert to see in this weekend", "deadwood what to remember for the hbo movie", "this summer opera grapple with race", "iraq sentence more french be member to death so far", "baltimore symphony musicians be stun after concert be cancel", "art exhibition to view in this weekend", "the leader who be trump before trump", "the playlist cardi b be stress and more new song", "review the searing power of an aids symphony", "with joe hill finally sink -pron- tooth into tv", "when resistance become too loud to ignore", "the late egypt leader say gulf security vital to cairo", "analysis india modi face foreign pressures in term", "-pron- house be -pron- house pakistan rich say to -pron- poor", "review angel and demon cross the aisle to save the world sorry -pron- fiction", "pakistan arrest men for raise funds for outlawed group", "lyon bomb suspect have pledge allegiance to be", "some enchant ending debut and other spectacular feats at city ballet", "a tibetan collection fight a battle that small museum often face", "turkey frees american nasa scientist imprison for year", "how the rockettes fall like domino", "in harvard speech merkel rebuke trump worldview in all but name", "disney may halt productions in georgia if abortion law be enforce", "thing to do with -pron- kid in this weekend", "florida cabinet meets in israel under media objection", "india new government signals hindu and india first goals", "next out of prince vaults the hits -pron- give away", "after a scandal the new orleans jazz market rise again", "time be up pakistan army targets protest movement stifle dissent", "the good movies and tv show new to netflix australia in june", "at this techno club the party be political", "leonardo drew ride -pron- magic carpet to a new field", "leader of smithsonian african american museum to direct entire institution", "un assembly remembers victims of violence against religion", "iraq hands over turkish child of suspected be member", "pop rock and jazz concerts to check out in this weekend", "the late florida cabinet meeting underway in jerusalem", "new sexual assault charges file against kelly", "harry potter e book offer hogwarts lesson for all", "modi begin second term as india prime minister after crush victory", "queer muslims be still rare on tv one writer want to change that", "syria rejects arab summit statement on iran intervention", "the late saudi king say islamic summit confronts threats", "what on tv friday deadwood the movie and when -pron- see -pron-", "tyler the creator beat dj khaled to hit no with igor", "dance performances to see in this weekend", "pride event here how to celebrate", "the broken saucers in alan faena house be purely aesthetic", "why robert mueller should testify on tv", "review twyla tharp enduring -pron- can have -pron- all vision", "where subway dancer practice -pron- art", "art festival be welcome but not the huge crowd", "oklahoma city bombing trial judge richard matsch die at", "david letterman the non ironic version", "in turkey keeping alive a language of whistles", "-pron- beach opera won at the biennale but -pron- can hardly afford -pron-", "france call on iraq to spare six of -pron- citizens from death penalty", "there great dance on broadway hello tony awards", "the good movies and tv show new on netflix canada in june", "two transgender activist be get a monument in new york", "when -pron- see -pron- transform -pron- victim into heroes", "pakistan sentences to in jail over terror financing", "how a city in fear brutalize the central park five", "still ponder the end of game of thrones here what to read about -pron-", "on walt whitman big birthday glorious relics", "review in one last deadwood the future prevails and the past endure", "japan announces aid to bangladesh during leader visit", "arab leader meet in mecca to unify rank amid iran tension", "good omens unite an angel and a demon for judgment day"]}