{"py/object": "data.Author", "author_id": "q4om4iaf2uvwyvjzifd6kcvuul5xm8a4", "truth": 0, "tweets": ["American Crime Story: ‘The Assassination of Gianni Versace’: Tom Rob Smith on Making Meaning From Pain #URL#", "The Alienist: ‘The Alienist’ Season 1, Episode 9: The Doctor Is Out #URL#", "12 Travel Sites That Accept PayPal #URL#", "‘Westworld’ and ‘Cobra Kai’ to Have Premieres at the Tribeca Film Festival #URL#", "Trump, the Television President, Expands His Cast #URL#", "Mike MacDonald, Canadian Stand-Up Star, Is Dead at 62 #URL#", "‘S.N.L.’ Takes Aim at Betsy DeVos, Jeff Sessions and Rex Tillerson #URL#", "Pacific Ocean Garbage Patch Growing Rapidly, Study Finds #URL#", "Breakthrough Reported in South Africa’s Worst Listeria Outbreak #URL#", "Prehistoric Giant Shark Tooth Stolen in Australia #URL#", "Making the Dogs of ‘Isle of Dogs’ #URL#", "A Composer of Dark Explosions Turns 100 #URL#", "After Trump, an Oratorio About ‘Dreamers’ Changes Key #URL#", "We’d Like to Know: Where Would You Go in Wakanda? #URL#", "Five Ways to Make Parched Cities Cooler #URL#", "‘The Sound of Music,’ ‘Rumours’ and More Join the National Recording Registry #URL#", "Personal Information Of 880,000 Orbitz Customers Likely Breached #URL#", "Roots Show at SXSW in Austin Is Canceled After Bomb Threat #URL#", "There's A Secret Code Thieves Use To Break Into Hotel Room Safes #URL#", "‘Tomb Raider’ Can’t Topple ‘Black Panther’ at Box Office #URL#", "A Data-Driven Approach Aims to Help Cities Recover After Earthquakes #URL#", "Brian Eno Wants to Take You ‘Inside the Music’ #URL#", "‘Scarface’ Cast Will Reunite at the Tribeca Film Festival #URL#", "WHO: Tainted Food Outbreak Threatens 16 African Nations #URL#", "Kim Petras Just Wants to Be a Pop Star #URL#", "Review: Soderbergh Plays With iPhones and Claire Foy in ‘Unsane’ #URL#", "New Technology Being Developed for Pacemakers #URL#", "Implantable Heart Defibrillators Deliver Shock in More Ways Than One #URL#", "Springsteen Signs Up for More Time on Broadway #URL#", "Women 'Weed Warriors' Leading the Way in US Pot Revolution #URL#", "South Africa's New Pharmacy ATM #URL#", "What’s on TV Wednesday: ‘Krypton’ and ‘The X-Files’ #URL#", "SXSW Film: The Movies and Performers That Stood Out #URL#", "Best of Late Night: Trevor Noah Attacks Facebook and Urges Users to ‘Be Vigilant’ #URL#", "FDA Plans to Slash Nicotine Levels in Cigarettes #URL#", "Review: ‘12 Days’ and the Rights of the Mentally Ill #URL#", "Venezuelan Health System Decays Further, Opposition-led Survey Says #URL#", "Review: In ‘Pacific Rim Uprising,’ Scary Monsters and Super Robots #URL#", "Review: In ‘Dear Dictator,’ a Despot Does Housework #URL#", "Critic’s Notebook: South by Southwest Music Festival: 17 Acts That Stood Out #URL#", "Daylight Turns Plastic Sheet into Germ-Killing Material #URL#", "Best of Late Night: Jimmy Kimmel Pitches for Stormy Daniels’s Legal Fund #URL#", "Review: ‘Roxanne Roxanne’ Is a Slice of Old-School Hip-Hop Life #URL#", "Rare, Endangered Primate is Born in Jerusalem Zoo #URL#", "Rihanna Protests Ad on Snapchat that Mocks Domestic Violence #URL#", "South Sudan Eliminates Guinea Worm #URL#", "World's Last Male Northern White Rhino, Sudan, Dies #URL#", "The State of Water in the World 2018 #URL#", "World Bank Says Climate Change Could Create 140 Million Migrants by 2050 #URL#", "UNESCO Study: More Investment Needed in ‘Green’ Water Management Systems #URL#", "Implantable Heart Defibrillators Deliver Shock in More Ways Than One #URL#", "Here and Now: ‘Here and Now’ Season 1, Episode 6: The Butterfly Effect #URL#", "Brazil to Vaccinate Entire Country Against Yellow Fever #URL#", "HSBC Report: India Most Vulnerable Country to Climate Change #URL#", "Hawking's Ashes to Be Interred Near Graves of Newton, Darwin #URL#", "Best of Late Night: Jimmy Kimmel Criticizes Trump Administration for Its High Turnover #URL#", "The Future of Time Warner, Coming Soon to a Court Near You #URL#", "Child Meningitis Remains a Challenge for Sub-Saharan Africa, India #URL#", "Re-Imagining Refugee Camps as Livable Cities #URL#", "Last Three Years Hottest on Record, UN Report Says #URL#", "What’s on TV Sunday: ‘Instinct’ and ‘Brooklyn Nine-Nine’ #URL#", "Ambitious Opera Philadelphia Announces Its New Season #URL#", "Trump Seeks Death Penalty for Drug Traffickers to Curb US Opioid Abuse #URL#", "‘Avengers: Infinity War’ Trailer Unites Marvel’s All-Stars #URL#", "New Technology Being Developed for Pacemakers #URL#", "Our First Interstellar Visitor Likely Came From Two-star System #URL#", "What’s on TV Monday: ‘Arthur Miller: Writer’ and ‘Life Itself’ #URL#", "United Airlines Temporarily Suspends Cargo Travel For Pets #URL#", "The Walking Dead: ‘The Walking Dead’ Season 8, Episode 12: Barbed Affection #URL#", "5 Film Series to Catch in NYC This Weekend #URL#", "2,000 Years Before #HASHTAG#, a Central Asian Epic of ‘Girl Power’ #URL#", "First Responders Learn Lessons from Mass Shootings, Terror Acts #URL#", "Opera on Alzheimer's to Debut in Philadelphia Festival #URL#", "RuPaul’s Drag Race All Stars: ‘RuPaul’s Drag Race All Stars’ Finale: And the Winner Is … #URL#", "What’s on TV Tuesday: ‘Adam Ruins Everything’ and ‘The Standups’ #URL#", "Works in Progress: The Actor Incorporates #URL#", "Review: Ligeti Sounded Thrilling, When Alarm Will Sound Was Let Loose #URL#", "Judd Apatow Puts Garry Shandling Under the Microscope #URL#", "In California, Men Can Get Their Blood Pressure Checked in Barbershops #URL#", "Review: ‘Leonora and Alejandro’ and One Rather Trippy Encounter #URL#", "Blizzard Watching: What to Watch on a Snow Day #URL#", "The ‘Trust’ Equation: Wealth and Power Equals Misery #URL#", "'Beating' Human Heart Cells Help Spur Drug Discovery #URL#", "Review: Los Angeles Through a Stranger’s Eyes in ‘No Light and No Land Anywhere’ #URL#", "‘Bobby Tarantino II’ Gives Logic His Second No. 1 in Less Than a Year #URL#", "Netflix Adds a Warning Video to ‘13 Reasons Why’ #URL#", "Popcast: Ashlee Simpson: You Asked, We Answered #URL#", "James Levine, Fired Over Abuse Allegations, Sues the Met Opera #URL#", "Review: ‘Tomb Raider’ and the Perils of Blockbustering #URL#", "US-Russia Tensions Not Felt in Space #URL#", "Snow Science: Crystal Clues to Climate Change, Watersheds #URL#", "US-Russia Tensions Not Felt in Space #URL#", "Chris Evans, a.k.a. Captain America, Comes Back Down to Earth #URL#", "Want to Avoid the Flu While Flying? Try a Window Seat #URL#", "Polio Vaccination Team Members Killed in Pakistan #URL#", "Leading AIDS Researcher Picked to Head CDC #URL#", "China Gives Communist Party More Control Over Policy and Media #URL#", "Review: On Netflix, a Wild Story of Guns, Sex and a Guru #URL#", "Review: Haves and Have-Nots Collide in ‘Us and Them’ #URL#", "The Most Popular U.S. Destinations Of 2018, According To TripAdvisor #URL#"], "ents": [[["American Crime Story", "ORG"], ["Gianni Versace", "PERSON"], ["Tom Rob Smith", "PERSON"], ["Making Meaning From Pain", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Season 1", "DATE"], ["9", "CARDINAL"]], [["12", "CARDINAL"]], [["Westworld", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Cobra Kai", "PRODUCT"], ["Have Premieres", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["the Tribeca Film Festival", "EVENT"]], [["Trump", "ORG"]], [["Mike MacDonald", "PERSON"], ["Canadian", "NORP"], ["62", "CARDINAL"]], [["Betsy DeVos", "PERSON"], ["Jeff Sessions", "PERSON"], ["Rex Tillerson", "PERSON"]], [["Pacific Ocean Garbage Patch Growing Rapidly,", "ORG"]], [["Breakthrough Reported", "ORG"], ["South Africa’s", "GPE"], ["Worst Listeria Outbreak", "EVENT"]], [["Australia", "GPE"]], [], [["100", "CARDINAL"]], [["Trump", "ORG"]], [["Wakanda", "ORG"]], [["Five", "CARDINAL"]], [["‘The Sound of Music", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Rumours", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["880,000", "CARDINAL"], ["Orbitz", "ORG"]], [["SXSW", "GPE"], ["Austin", "GPE"]], [], [["Box Office", "ORG"]], [], [["Brian Eno", "PERSON"], ["Take You ‘Inside the Music", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Scarface", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["the Tribeca Film Festival", "EVENT"]], [["16", "CARDINAL"], ["African", "NORP"]], [["Kim Petras", "PERSON"]], [["Soderbergh", "PERSON"], ["Claire Foy", "PERSON"], ["Unsane", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [], [], [["Springsteen Signs Up for", "PERSON"], ["Time", "ORG"], ["Broadway", "FAC"]], [["US", "GPE"]], [["South Africa's", "GPE"], ["New Pharmacy", "ORG"]], [["Wednesday", "DATE"], ["Krypton", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["The X-Files", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["SXSW Film", "ORG"]], [["Trevor Noah", "PERSON"], ["Be Vigilant", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["FDA", "ORG"]], [["12 Days", "DATE"], ["the Rights of the Mentally Ill", "LAW"]], [["Venezuelan Health System Decays Further", "ORG"]], [["Pacific Rim Uprising", "LOC"], ["Scary Monsters and Super Robots", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Dear Dictator", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Southwest Music Festival", "EVENT"], ["17", "CARDINAL"]], [], [["Late Night", "TIME"], ["Jimmy Kimmel", "PERSON"], ["Stormy Daniels’s", "ORG"], ["Legal Fund", "ORG"]], [["Roxanne Roxanne", "PERSON"], ["Is a Slice of Old-School Hip-Hop Life", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [], [["Rihanna Protests Ad", "PERSON"]], [["South Sudan", "GPE"]], [["World", "ORG"], ["Sudan", "GPE"]], [["The State of Water in the World 2018", "ORG"]], [["World Bank Says Climate Change Could Create 140 Million", "ORG"], ["2050", "DATE"]], [["UNESCO Study: More Investment Needed", "ORG"], ["Green’ Water Management Systems", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [], [["Season 1", "DATE"], ["6", "CARDINAL"]], [["Brazil", "GPE"], ["Vaccinate Entire Country Against Yellow Fever", "ORG"]], [["HSBC Report", "ORG"], ["India", "GPE"]], [["Hawking's Ashes to Be Interred Near Graves", "ORG"], ["Newton", "GPE"], ["Darwin", "PERSON"]], [["Late Night", "TIME"], ["Jimmy Kimmel", "PERSON"]], [], [["Africa", "LOC"], ["India", "GPE"]], [], [["Last Three Years", "DATE"], ["UN", "ORG"]], [["Sunday", "DATE"], ["Instinct", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Brooklyn Nine-Nine", "EVENT"]], [["Opera Philadelphia", "ORG"]], [], [["Avengers: Infinity War’ Trailer Unites Marvel’s All-Stars", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [], [["Two", "CARDINAL"]], [["Monday", "DATE"], ["Arthur Miller", "PERSON"], ["‘Life Itself", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["United Airlines Temporarily Suspends Cargo Travel For Pets", "ORG"]], [["Season 8", "DATE"], ["12", "CARDINAL"]], [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["Series", "EVENT"], ["NYC", "GPE"], ["This Weekend", "DATE"]], [["2,000 Years Before", "DATE"], ["Central Asian", "NORP"], ["Girl Power", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["First Responders Learn Lessons", "ORG"], ["Mass Shootings", "ORG"]], [["Philadelphia", "GPE"]], [["RuPaul", "PERSON"], ["Drag Race All Stars", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Drag Race All Stars’ Finale", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Tuesday", "DATE"], ["Adam Ruins Everything", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Standups", "PERSON"]], [], [], [["Judd Apatow", "PERSON"], ["Garry Shandling", "PERSON"]], [["California", "GPE"]], [["Leonora", "PERSON"], ["Alejandro", "ORG"], ["One", "CARDINAL"], ["Rather Trippy Encounter", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [], [], [], [["Los Angeles", "GPE"], ["No Light and No Land Anywhere", "WORK_OF_ART"]], [["Bobby Tarantino II", "PERSON"], ["Gives Logic His Second No. 1 in", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Less Than a Year", "DATE"]], [["Netflix", "ORG"], ["13", "CARDINAL"]], [["Ashlee Simpson", "PERSON"]], [["James Levine", "PERSON"]], [], [["US", "GPE"], ["Russia", "GPE"]], [], [["US", "GPE"], ["Russia", "GPE"]], [["Chris Evans", "PERSON"], ["America", "PERSON"], ["Earth", "LOC"]], [], [["Pakistan", "GPE"]], [], [["China", "GPE"], ["Communist Party More Control Over Policy and Media", "ORG"]], [["Netflix", "ORG"]], [], [["2018", "DATE"], ["TripAdvisor", "PERSON"]]], "POS_tags": [[{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "DET", "VERB", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PART", "AUX", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "AUX", "ADJ", "ADP", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADV", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "INTJ", "PART", "VERB", "PUNCT", "ADV", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "AUX", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PRON", "PUNCT", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV", "VERB", "PART", "AUX", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "DET", "VERB", "ADP"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "NOUN", "PART", "PUNCT", "AUX", "ADJ", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "ADV", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "AUX", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PART", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "DET", "VERB", "ADP"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "AUX", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "DET", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "NUM", "NUM", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "CCONJ", "ADV", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "ADV", "CCONJ", "ADV", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADV", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PART", "AUX", "VERB", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "PRON"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "VERB", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "ADJ", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADJ", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "ADV", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "PROPN", "ADV", "VERB", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PRON", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "DET", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "NOUN", "ADV", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "NOUN", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "DET", "PROPN", "AUX", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "PRON", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "AUX", "VERB", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "AUX", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "DET", "PROPN", "ADV", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADV", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "VERB", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PRON", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN"]}]], "clean": ["american crime story the assassination of gianni versace tom rob smith on make meaning from pain", "the alienist the alienist season episode the doctor be out", "travel site that accept paypal", "westworld and cobra kai to have premieres at the tribeca film festival", "trump the television president expand -pron- cast", "mike macdonald canadian stand up star be dead at", "take aim at betsy devos jeff sessions and rex tillerson", "pacific ocean garbage patch grow rapidly study find", "breakthrough report in south africa bad listeria outbreak", "prehistoric giant shark tooth steal in australia", "make the dog of isle of dogs", "a composer of dark explosions turn", "after trump an oratorio about dreamer change key", "-pron- like to know where would -pron- go in wakanda", "five way to make parched city cooler", "the sound of music rumour and more join the national recording registry", "personal information of orbitz customers likely breach", "root show at sxsw in austin be cancel after bomb threat", "there a secret code thief use to break into hotel room safes", "tomb raider can topple black panther at box office", "a data driven approach aim to help city recover after earthquake", "brian eno want to take -pron- inside the music", "scarface cast will reunite at the tribeca film festival", "who tainted food outbreak threaten african nation", "kim petras just want to be a pop star", "review soderbergh play with iphones and claire foy in unsane", "new technology be develop for pacemaker", "implantable heart defibrillator deliver shock in more ways than one", "springsteen sign up for more time on broadway", "woman weed warriors lead the way in us pot revolution", "south africa new pharmacy atm", "what on tv wednesday krypton and the x file", "sxsw film the movies and performer that stand out", "good of late night trevor noah attacks facebook and urge user to be vigilant", "fda plan to slash nicotine levels in cigarette", "review day and the rights of the mentally ill", "venezuelan health system decays further opposition lead survey say", "review in pacific rim uprising scary monsters and super robot", "review in dear dictator a despot do housework", "critic notebook south by southwest music festival act that stand out", "daylight turn plastic sheet into germ killing material", "good of late night jimmy kimmel pitches for stormy daniels legal fund", "review roxanne roxanne be a slice of old school hip hop life", "rare endanger primate be bear in jerusalem zoo", "rihanna protests ad on snapchat that mock domestic violence", "south sudan eliminate guinea worm", "world last male northern white rhino sudan dies", "the state of water in the world", "world bank say climate change could create million migrants by", "unesco study more investment need in green water management systems", "implantable heart defibrillator deliver shock in more ways than one", "here and now here and now season episode the butterfly effect", "brazil to vaccinate entire country against yellow fever", "hsbc report india most vulnerable country to climate change", "hawking ashes to be inter near graves of newton darwin", "good of late night jimmy kimmel criticize trump administration for -pron- high turnover", "the future of time warner come soon to a court near -pron-", "child meningitis remain a challenge for sub saharan africa india", "re imagine refugee cs as livable cities", "last three year hot on record un report say", "what on tv sunday instinct and brooklyn nine nine", "ambitious opera philadelphia announce -pron- new season", "trump seek death penalty for drug trafficker to curb us opioid abuse", "avenger infinity war trailer unites marvel all star", "new technology be develop for pacemaker", "-pron- first interstellar visitor likely come from two star system", "what on tv monday arthur miller writer and life -pron-", "united airlines temporarily suspend cargo travel for pet", "the walk dead the walk dead season episode barbed affection", "film series to catch in nyc this weekend", "year before a central asian epic of girl power", "first responder learn lesson from mass shootings terror act", "opera on alzheimer to debut in philadelphia festival", "rupaul drag race all star rupaul drag race all stars finale and the winner be", "what on tv tuesday adam ruin everything and the standups", "work in progress the actor incorporate", "review ligeti sound thrilling when alarm will sound be let loose", "judd apatow put garry shandling under the microscope", "in california man can get -pron- blood pressure check in barbershop", "review leonora and alejandro and one rather trippy encounter", "blizzard watching what to watch on a snow day", "the trust equation wealth and power equals misery", "beat human heart cell help spur drug discovery", "review los angeles through a stranger eye in no light and no land anywhere", "bobby tarantino ii give logic -pron- second no in less than a year", "netflix add a warning video to reason why", "popcast ashlee simpson -pron- ask -pron- answer", "james levine fire over abuse allegations sue the met opera", "review tomb raider and the perils of blockbustering", "us russia tension not feel in space", "snow science crystal clue to climate change watersheds", "us russia tension not feel in space", "chris evans captain america come back down to earth", "want to avoid the flu while fly try a window seat", "polio vaccination team members kill in pakistan", "lead aids researcher pick to head cdc", "china give communist party more control over policy and medium", "review on netflix a wild story of guns sex and a guru", "review have and have nots collide in us and -pron-", "the most popular destination of accord to tripadvisor"]}