{"py/object": "data.Author", "author_id": "w0payh6v0jjxkkafl6vsvc4n8kgpv7ox", "truth": 1, "tweets": ["Trivago Spokesman's DWI Case Dismissed After Alcohol Ed Classes #URL#", "Dog the Bounty Hunter's Daughter, Lyssa Chapman, Arrested in Hawaii #URL#", "Rich the Kid Sued by Management Company for Over $3.5 Million #URL#", "Jessica Alba -- Good Genes or Good Docs?! #URL#", "Antonio Brown Suspect In Battery and Burglary, Cops Working On Arrest Warrant #URL#", "Information Society Singer Kurt Harland 'Memba Him?! #URL#", "President Trump Sarcastically Tweets About Cory Booker Dropping Out #URL#", "Guess Who This Brace Face Turned Into! #URL#", "Vanessa Bryant Says Kobe and Gigi Memorial Will Go Down Feb. 24 at Staples Center #URL#", "Serena Williams Gets Boxing Lesson From Mike Tyson #URL#", "Trick Daddy Looks Horrible in Mug Shot Because of Lupus #URL#", "Nicki Minaj's Brother Sentenced to 25 Years to Life for Child Rape #URL#", "'Cheer' Cast Hot Bods -- Guess Who! #URL#", "Keanu Reeves, Carrie-Anne Moss On Set for 'Matrix 4' in San Francisco #URL#", "Mary Carey Fighting 'Pippi Longstocking' Tami Erin in Celebrity Boxing #URL#", "Nathan Bookman on 'Good Times' 'Memba Him?! #URL#", "Rudy Giuliani Says Prez Trump's Right, Put Pete Rose In The HOF! #URL#", "'Love Island' Host Caroline Flack Dies by Suicide at 40 Before Trial #URL#", "'Bad News Bears' Jeffrey Davies Takes First Steps Months After Crash #URL#", "Jenelle Evans' Ex-Husband Courtland Rogers Arrested for Drugs, Larceny #URL#", "Aerosmith's Joey Kramer Says He's Going to Grammy Event Despite Court Ruling #URL#", "Amazing! The Photo Of Britney Spears That Will Leave You Shocked Doesn’t Look Like Her! - Code List #URL#", "Nicki Minaj's Rosa Parks Line Was No Disrespect, Timing a Coincidence #URL#", "Jennifer Hudson In Character For Aretha Franklin Biopic 'Respect' #URL#", "Mya Has Secret Wedding in Seychelles, First Look at Her Dress #URL#", "Joe Biden Calls Voter 'Lying Dog-Faced Pony Soldier,' Credits John Wayne #URL#", "Serena Williams Shuts Down Question About Meghan Markle, 'Good Try' #URL#", "Little Nathan Jr. in 'Raising Arizona' 'Memba Him?! #URL#", "Rick Fox Says WNBA Stars Can Ball Out In NBA, Kobe's Right! #URL#", "Antonio Brown Performs First Show in FL, Throws Cash Onstage #URL#", "Meghan Markle &amp; Prince Harry Abandon Royal Titles, Queen Bids Farewell #URL#", "Ronnie Ortiz-Magro Giddy As Woman Flashes Him in Hollywood #URL#", "E-40 Has Custom Tequila for the 49ers After Super Bowl, Win or Lose #URL#", "'1917' Sam Mendes Ad Claims Early Oscars Victory, Apparently a Mistake #URL#", "Antonio Brown 911 Call, Driver Claims AB Was High #URL#", "Quibi Teams Up With Chance The Rapper For First Super Bowl Ad #URL#", "Tell It To My Heart Singer Taylor Dayne 'Memba Her?! #URL#", "Bo Jackson's Rare Broken Bat From Final Season Up For Auction #URL#", "'Glee' Star Dot Jones Recovering After Emergency Heart Surgery #URL#", "Wendy Williams Didn't Break Girl Code with NeNe Leakes Quitting 'RHOA' #URL#", "Lindsay Lohan Shouts Out High School Production of 'Freaky Friday' #URL#", "The Ultimate Ranking of Britney Spears' 13 Top 10 Hits - E! Online #URL#", "Nicki Minaj, Meek Mill Reignite Beef with Outrageous Accusations #URL#", "Nicki Minaj Regrets Mudslinging With Meek Mill on Social Media #URL#", "Juice WRLD Died from Accidental OD of Oxycodone and Codeine #URL#", "Cardi B Masks Face With Bling At Offset's Fashion Show in Paris #URL#", "Mark Cuban Says 'I Would Support' Changing NBA Logo to Kobe Bryant #URL#", "Rep. Tim Ryan Says Obamas' First Oscar Nomination Wasn't About Luck #URL#", "L.A. High-Rise Fire Leads to Daring Rescues #URL#", "Jamie Lynn Spears' Baby Daddy Casey Aldridge Arrested For Burglary #URL#", "Guess Who This Happy Kid Turned Into! #URL#", "Guns N' Roses Ex-Guitarist DJ Ashba Cuts Plea Deal in DUI Case #URL#", "Shareef O'Neal Reveals Biggest Lesson He Learned From Kobe Bryant #URL#", "R. Kelly GF Joycelyn Savage's Sad Mug Shot After Fight with Azriel Clary #URL#", "Justin Bieber's Kobe Bryant Tribute Art Raises $12,000 for MambaOnThree #URL#", "Michelle Obama Releases 2020 Workout Playlist, Oldies &amp; Edited #URL#", "What's The Big Frigin' Difference? #URL#", "Rep. Andre Carson Says Political Ads During Super Bowl Better Be Fun #URL#", "Sergey Kovalev Blew Off $650k Payment to Female Assault Accuser, Lawsuit Claims #URL#", "Pamela Anderson, New Hubby Producer Jon Peters First Pic Together #URL#", "Vic Mensa Arrested for Felony Possession of Brass Knuckles #URL#", "Justin Bieber Opens Up About Lyme Disease and Health Struggles in Docuseries #URL#", "Guess Who This Bow Baby Turned Into! #URL#", "Netflix's 'Cheer' Producers Turned Down Daytona Footage, Varsity Claims #URL#", "Ugandan Disney Actress Nikita Pearl Waligwa Dead at 15 #URL#", "College Football Player Body Slams Cop During Arrest, Insane Police Video #URL#", "Jessica Simpson's Book Tour Security Beefing Up After Anti-Fur Protests #URL#", "Jenelle Evans and David Eason Back Living Together, Get New Pet #URL#", "WWE's Alexa Bliss, 'My Pig Is Cuter Than My Butt' #URL#", "Lizzo Rocks Strappy Gold Swimsuit on Heels of Jillian Michaels Remarks #URL#", "Nikki Bella Showing Off Her Baby Bump After Pregnancy Reveal #URL#", "YG Will Perform at Grammys After Arrest and Release, Lawyer Says #URL#", "Boosie Badazz Cops Sweet Plea Deal in Georgia Weed Case #URL#", "Future Claims Alleged Baby Mama Has Mental Health Issues #URL#", "Tom Brady Jokes About Julian Edelman's Arrest #URL#", "President Trump Attends Daytona 500, Jokes He Wants to Race #URL#", "Timbaland Aiming to Lose Nearly 200 lbs. After Kicking Opioid Addiction #URL#", "Dog the Bounty Hunter Has Chill Birthday at Benihana, No Sign of Moon #URL#", "Future's Covering His Son's Legal Case Financially, Kid's Not 'Indigent' #URL#", "Team Roc Leaks Mississippi Prison Video of Violence, Inhumane Conditions #URL#", "Cops Grab Alleged 'Penis Man' Graffiti Artist in Arizona #URL#", "Boosie Badazz Says White Battle Rapper Deserves Punch For Using N-Word #URL#", "Michelle Carter Released Early From Prison After Texting Suicide Conviction #URL#", "Mario Lopez and Elizabeth Berkley in Character For 'Saved By The Bell' #URL#", "Dwayne 'The Rock' Johnson Posts Emotional Goodbye To Dad After Death, 'I'm In Pain' #URL#", "DaBaby Sued By Alleged Miami Battery Victim #URL#", "NY Giants Owner Won't Commit To Eli Manning In 2020, 'Everything's Up In The Air' #URL#", "Tank Says Sex Absolutely Counts as Acceptable Valentine's Day Gift #URL#", "Jordan Belfort Says Bernie Madoff Deserves to Die in Prison #URL#", "Famous NFL Fans Having A Field Day! #URL#", "Chainsaw in 'Summer School' 'Memba Him?! #URL#", "Johnny Depp Jams on Guitar During High School Charity Concert #URL#", "Barstool Sports President Dave Portnoy Talks New Riches, Super Bowl Bets #URL#", "Tekashi 6ix9ine Sued for Using 'Stoopid' Intro Without Permission #URL#", "Meek Mill Gets Into Shouting Match With Ex Nicki Minaj's Husband #URL#", "Chuck Liddell Hopes Cowboy Cerrone Beats Conor McGregor At UFC 246 #URL#", "Khabib Shoots Down $100 Mil Rematch with 'Idiot' Conor McGregor #URL#", "Blac Chyna Says She Didn't Injure Rob Kardashian Besides a Broken Heart #URL#", "Death and Cynic Drummer Sean Reinert Dead at 48 #URL#", "Joe Giudice Parties with a Flock of Hot Babes in Mexico, Teresa Who? #URL#"], "ents": [[{"py/tuple": ["Trivago Spokesman's", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["the Bounty Hunter's", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Lyssa Chapman", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Hawaii", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["$3.5 Million", "MONEY"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Jessica Alba", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Antonio Brown Suspect", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Kurt Harland '", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Trump Sarcastically", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Vanessa Bryant", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Kobe", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Gigi Memorial", "LOC"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Feb. 24", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Staples Center", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Serena Williams", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Mike Tyson", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Nicki Minaj's", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["25 Years", "DATE"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Keanu Reeves", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Carrie-Anne Moss", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["San Francisco", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Mary Carey", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Tami Erin in Celebrity Boxing", "WORK_OF_ART"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Nathan Bookman", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Rudy Giuliani", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Prez Trump's", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["HOF", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Love Island' Host Caroline Flack Dies by Suicide", "WORK_OF_ART"]}, {"py/tuple": ["40", "CARDINAL"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Jenelle Evans'", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Drugs", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Joey Kramer", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["The Photo Of Britney Spears That Will Leave You Shocked Doesn’t Look Like Her! - Code List", "WORK_OF_ART"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Nicki Minaj's", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Jennifer Hudson", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Mya", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Secret Wedding in Seychelles, First Look at Her Dress", "WORK_OF_ART"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Joe Biden", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["John Wayne", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Serena Williams Shuts", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["'Raising Arizona' 'Memba Him", "WORK_OF_ART"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Rick Fox", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["NBA", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Kobe", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Antonio Brown", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["FL", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Meghan Markle", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Prince Harry Abandon Royal Titles", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Ronnie Ortiz-Magro Giddy", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Hollywood", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["49ers", "CARDINAL"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Super Bowl", "EVENT"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Win", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Lose", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["1917", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Sam Mendes", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Antonio Brown", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Taylor Dayne '", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Bo Jackson's", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Glee", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Wendy Williams", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["NeNe Leakes", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Lindsay Lohan", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Friday", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["The Ultimate Ranking of Britney Spears'", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["13", "CARDINAL"]}, {"py/tuple": ["10", "CARDINAL"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Nicki Minaj", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Meek Mill Reignite Beef", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Nicki Minaj Regrets Mudslinging With Meek Mill", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Social Media", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Accidental OD of Oxycodone and Codeine", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Paris", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Mark Cuban", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Kobe Bryant", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Tim Ryan", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Obamas", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["L.A. High-Rise Fire Leads", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Jamie Lynn Spears'", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Guns N'", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Roses Ex-Guitarist DJ Ashba Cuts Plea Deal", "WORK_OF_ART"]}, {"py/tuple": ["DUI", "ORG"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["R. Kelly", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Joycelyn Savage's", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Azriel Clary", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Justin Bieber's", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Kobe Bryant", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["12,000", "MONEY"]}, {"py/tuple": ["MambaOnThree", "CARDINAL"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Michelle Obama", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["2020", "CARDINAL"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Andre Carson", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Super Bowl", "EVENT"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Sergey Kovalev", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Pamela Anderson", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["New Hubby", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Jon Peters", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Vic Mensa", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Felony Possession of Brass Knuckles", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Justin Bieber", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Netflix", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Pearl Waligwa Dead", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["15", "CARDINAL"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Insane Police Video", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Jessica Simpson's", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Jenelle Evans", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["David Eason", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["WWE", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Alexa Bliss", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["My Pig Is Cuter Than My Butt'", "WORK_OF_ART"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Lizzo", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Jillian", "NORP"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["YG Will Perform", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Georgia", "GPE"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Tom Brady", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Julian Edelman's", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Trump Attends", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Nearly 200", "CARDINAL"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["the Bounty Hunter", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Benihana, No Sign of Moon", "FAC"]}], [], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Cops Grab Alleged '", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Penis Man' Graffiti Artist", "WORK_OF_ART"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Arizona", "GPE"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Michelle Carter", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Mario Lopez", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Elizabeth Berkley", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Saved By The Bell'", "WORK_OF_ART"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Dwayne 'The Rock' Johnson Posts Emotional Goodbye To Dad After Death", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["2020", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Acceptable Valentine's", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Day Gift", "WORK_OF_ART"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Jordan Belfort", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Bernie Madoff Deserves", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Die", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["NFL", "ORG"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Johnny Depp Jams", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Guitar During High School Charity Concert", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Barstool Sports", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Dave Portnoy", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["New Riches", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Super Bowl Bets", "EVENT"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Tekashi 6ix9ine", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Meek Mill", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Chuck Liddell", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Hopes Cowboy", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Conor McGregor", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["UFC", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["246", "CARDINAL"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["$100 Mil", "MONEY"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Idiot", "NORP"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Conor McGregor", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Blac Chyna", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Reinert Dead", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["48", "CARDINAL"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Joe Giudice", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Mexico", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Teresa Who", "GPE"]}]], "POS_tags": [[{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["X", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADP", "SYM", "NUM", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PRON", "PUNCT", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PRON", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PRON", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PRON", "PUNCT", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "INTJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PRON", "AUX", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "DET", "VERB", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "AUX", "PART", "VERB", "SCONJ", "DET", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PRON", "PUNCT", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "INTJ", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "VERB", "PRON", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "AUX", "NOUN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "AUX", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADP", "PROPN", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PRON", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PRON", "PUNCT", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NUM", "ADJ", "NUM", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "PART", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PRON", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "SYM", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PRON", "AUX", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV", "AUX", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "SYM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV", "PROPN", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "PRON", "DET", "NOUN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV", "VERB", "ADV", "PUNCT", "AUX", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "AUX", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "PART", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "ADV", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["X", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "AUX", "PART", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PRON", "AUX", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PRON", "AUX", "ADP", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADV", "VERB", "SCONJ", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PRON", "PUNCT", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "VERB", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "ADV", "SYM", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PRON", "AUX", "PART", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SCONJ", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PRON", "PUNCT"]}]], "clean": ["trivago spokesman dwi case dismiss after alcohol ed classes", "dog the bounty hunter daughter lyssa chapman arrest in hawaii", "rich the kid sue by management company for over million", "jessica alba good genes or good doc", "antonio brown suspect in battery and burglary cops work on arrest warrant", "information society singer kurt harland memba -pron-", "president trump sarcastically tweets about cory booker drop out", "guess who this brace face turn into", "vanessa bryant say kobe and gigi memorial will go down at staples center", "serena williams get box lesson from mike tyson", "trick daddy look horrible in mug shot because of lupus", "nicki minaj brother sentence to year to life for child rape", "cheer cast hot bod guess who", "keanu reeves carrie anne moss on set for matrix in san francisco", "mary carey fighting pippi longstocking tami erin in celebrity boxing", "nathan bookman on good times memba -pron-", "rudy giuliani say prez trump right put pete rose in the hof", "love island host caroline flack die by suicide at before trial", "bad news bears jeffrey davies take first step month after crash", "jenelle evans ex husband courtland rogers arrest for drug larceny", "aerosmith joey kramer say -pron- go to grammy event despite court ruling", "amazing the photo of britney spears that will leave -pron- shock do look like -pron- code list", "nicki minaj rosa parks line be no disrespect time a coincidence", "jennifer hudson in character for aretha franklin biopic respect", "mya have secret wedding in seychelles first look at -pron- dress", "joe biden call voter lie dog faced pony soldier credit john wayne", "serena williams shuts down question about meghan markle good try", "little nathan in raise arizona memba -pron-", "rick fox say wnba stars can ball out in nba kobe right", "antonio brown perform first show in fl throw cash onstage", "meghan markle prince harry abandon royal title queen bids farewell", "ronnie ortiz magro giddy as woman flash -pron- in hollywood", "have custom tequila for the after super bowl win or lose", "sam mendes ad claim early oscars victory apparently a mistake", "antonio brown call driver claim ab be high", "quibi team up with chance the rapper for first super bowl ad", "tell -pron- to -pron- heart singer taylor dayne memba -pron-", "bo jackson rare break bat from final season up for auction", "glee star dot jones recover after emergency heart surgery", "wendy williams do break girl code with nene leakes quitting rhoa", "lindsay lohan shout out high school production of freaky friday", "the ultimate ranking of britney spears top hits e online", "nicki minaj meek mill reignite beef with outrageous accusation", "nicki minaj regrets mudslinge with meek mill on social media", "juice wrld die from accidental od of oxycodone and codeine", "cardi b masks face with bling at offset fashion show in paris", "mark cuban say -pron- would support change nba logo to kobe bryant", "tim ryan say obamas first oscar nomination be about luck", "high rise fire lead to daring rescues", "jamie lynn spears baby daddy casey aldridge arrest for burglary", "guess who this happy kid turn into", "gun n roses ex guitarist dj ashba cuts plea deal in dui case", "shareef reveal big lesson -pron- learn from kobe bryant", "kelly gf joycelyn savage sad mug shot after fight with azriel clary", "justin bieber kobe bryant tribute art raise for mambaonthree", "michelle obama releases workout playlist oldie edit", "what the big frigin difference", "andre carson say political ads during super bowl better be fun", "sergey kovalev blew off payment to female assault accuser lawsuit claim", "pamela anderson new hubby producer jon peters first pic together", "vic mensa arrest for felony possession of brass knuckle", "justin bieber open up about lyme disease and health struggles in docuserie", "guess who this bow baby turn into", "netflix cheer producer turn down daytona footage varsity claims", "ugandan disney actress nikita pearl waligwa dead at", "college football player body slams cop during arrest insane police video", "jessica simpson book tour security beef up after anti fur protests", "jenelle evans and david eason back live together get new pet", "wwe alexa bliss -pron- pig be cuter than -pron- butt", "lizzo rocks strappy gold swimsuit on heels of jillian michaels remarks", "nikki bella show off -pron- baby bump after pregnancy reveal", "yg will perform at grammys after arrest and release lawyer say", "boosie badazz cops sweet plea deal in georgia weed case", "future claims alleged baby mama have mental health issues", "tom brady joke about julian edelman arrest", "president trump attends daytona joke -pron- want to race", "timbaland aim to lose nearly lb after kicking opioid addiction", "dog the bounty hunter have chill birthday at benihana no sign of moon", "future cover -pron- son legal case financially kid not indigent", "team roc leaks mississippi prison video of violence inhumane conditions", "cop grab allege penis man graffiti artist in arizona", "boosie badazz say white battle rapper deserve punch for use n word", "michelle carter release early from prison after texting suicide conviction", "mario lopez and elizabeth berkley in character for save by the bell", "dwayne the rock johnson posts emotional goodbye to dad after death -pron- in pain", "dababy sue by alleged miami battery victim", "ny giants owner will commit to eli manning in everything up in the air", "tank say sex absolutely count as acceptable valentine day gift", "jordan belfort say bernie madoff deserve to die in prison", "famous nfl fan have a field day", "chainsaw in summer school memba -pron-", "johnny depp jams on guitar during high school charity concert", "barstool sports president dave portnoy talk new riches super bowl bet", "tekashi sue for use stoopid intro without permission", "meek mill get into shouting match with ex nicki minaj husband", "chuck liddell hopes cowboy cerrone beats conor mcgregor at ufc", "khabib shoot down mil rematch with idiot conor mcgregor", "blac chyna say -pron- do injure rob kardashian besides a broken heart", "death and cynic drummer sean reinert dead at", "joe giudice parties with a flock of hot babes in mexico teresa who"]}