{"py/object": "data.Author", "author_id": "w73115nc8smn0t3xr1ojqp6dqpb1tq35", "truth": 0, "tweets": ["Ryan Gosling Eats His Cereal As Tribute to Vine Star Ryan McHenry", "Best of Phantom: James Harden's 2014-2015 Season Highlights #URL#", "Top 5 NBA Plays: May 5th #URL#", "The Witcher 3 Wild Hunt • Monsters Dev Diary • PS4 Xbox One PC #URL#", "INKED: The story behind Canadian Kish's tattoos #URL#", "Dubsmash by Aiman and Muneeb #URL#", "Mike Conley Returns to Lead Grizzlies to Game 2 Win #URL#", "Karl Lagerfeld's Interview - Cruise 2015/16 CHANEL show #URL#", "2 mai 2015 - Hondelatte Direct - BFMTV - Zohra BITAN et J.Christophe BUISSON #URL#", "Cute Girl Dubsmash Tamil Video #URL#", "WildStar • Invasion Nexus Trailer • FR • PC #URL#", "50 Shades trailer version LEGO #URL#", "The Other Side - Made in Hawaii - Part 3 #URL#", "The Royal Baby - Highlights! #URL#", "TV Actor Anita H Reddy dubsmashing haryanvi dialogue. A must watch! #URL#", "Destiny • House of Wolves Prison of Elders Reveal Teaser • PS4 Xbox One PS3 Xbox360 #URL#", "Cruise 2015/16 CHANEL Show - First Look #URL#", "Dubsmash of Indian TV actor of Asha Negi #URL#", "Dubsmash Pakistan Celebrity - 2015 #URL#", "Dragon Age Inquisition • Dragonslayer DLC Trailer • FR • PS4 Xbox One PS3 Xbox360 PC #URL#", "Hohokum • Action Trailer • PS4 PS3 PS Vita #URL#", "COMMENT JE PEUX GAGNER DE L ARGENT SUR INTERNET #URL#", "The Human Centipede 3 (Final Sequence) Official Trailer #HASHTAG# (2015) - Horror Movie HD #URL#", "Stephen Curry Accepts MVP Trophy #URL#", "L'intégrale Skyrim - Ep 396 - Playthrough FR HD par Bob Lennon #URL#", "The Witcher 3 Wild Hunt • Monsters Dev Diary • FR • PS4 Xbox One PC #URL#", "Tony Allen Steals and Flushes It Home #URL#", "Andrew Bogut Sends Courtney Lee Away with the Swat #URL#", "Wolfenstein The Old Blood • Gameplay Launch Trailer • FR • PS4 Xbox One PC #URL#", "Achieving long life and low cost in separators for fuel cells #HASHTAG# #URL#", "WildStar • Invasion Nexus Trailer • PC #URL#", "Dragon Age Inquisition • Dragonslayer DLC Trailer • PS4 Xbox One PS3 Xbox360 PC #URL#", "COMMENT SE FAIRE DE L ARGENT DE POCHE #URL#", "COMMENT TROUVE DE L ARGENT RAPIDEMENT #URL#", "Magic Mike XXL Official Trailer #HASHTAG# (2015) - Channing Tatum, Matt Bomer Movie HD #URL#", "House Of Crades : Bertrand Chameroy en prime sur D8 ! #URL#", "Madrid 2015 Tuesday Hot Shot Andujar #URL#", "Funny Telugu Dubsmash Viswanath naidu #URL#", "Dubsmash by Indian TV actor Anita Hassanandani #URL#", "Middle Earth Shadow of Mordor • Game of the Year Edition Trailer • FR • PS4 Xbox One PC #URL#", "NBA Daily Show: May 5 – The Starters #URL#", "COMMENT GAGNER DE L ARGENT SANS INTERNET #URL#", "DEVELOPMENT: Women's game gathering pace in Fiji #URL#", "Extreme Sailing Competition in Qingdao #URL#", "The Ultimate Kim Kardashian Paper Magazine Cake", "Laxmi Rai &amp; Friends Dubsmash - Kollywood #URL#", "Ramon Sessions Drops Circus Shot High Off the Glass #URL#", "Testament Of Youth Official US Release Trailer #HASHTAG# (2015) - Kit Harington, Hayley Atwell War Movie HD #URL#", "Another Dubsmash Video of Pakistani Actors and Actresses #URL#", "SCTM 2 : The Hidden Face of Paradise", "FKA Twigs Had A Penis On Her Dress At Met Gala &amp; It Wasn't Robert Pattinson's!", "Triomphe romain pour Bruno Peyron - Archive INA #URL#", "Justin Timberlake Dresses Like a Lime in Crazy Tequila Commercial", "Magicka 2 • Completely Unscripted Co Op Trailer • PC #URL#", "Super Clasheur VS Ari Touboul #URL#", "David Hasselhoff - True Survivor (Video Commentary) #URL#", "Myriam Abel : \"All by myself\" - Archive INA #URL#", "Interview \"Big Apple\" Amanda Big Apple - Archive INA #URL#", "Forza Horizon 2 • Alpine Stars Car Pack Trailer • FR • Xbox One #URL#", "COMMENT ON FAIT POUR GAGNER DE L ARGENT #URL#", "Kim Kardashian and Justin Bieber Give Two F*cks About Selfie Ban at Met Gala!| Hollyscoop News #URL#", "Stéphane Freiss \"Brooklyn boy\" et \"Le grand rôle\" - Archive INA #URL#", "Alia Bhatt's Dubsmash will Make you Laugh out Hard #URL#", "Kahui smashes Cooper with huge tackle #URL#", "COMMENT GAGNER DE L ARGENT FACILEMENT EN TRAVAILLANT #URL#", "Mr. Holmes Official US Release Trailer #HASHTAG# (2015) - Ian McKellen Mystery Drama HD #URL#", "Special Compilation of Pakistani Actresses Dubsmash Videos #URL#", "Wolfenstein The Old Blood • Gameplay Launch Trailer • PS4 Xbox One PC #URL#", "Phone Apps #HASHTAG# : Stupidizer, Linqapp, Drupe, Kolor #URL#", "Randi - Sex with Condom - Short Film - Hot Scenes Xxx #URL#", "Alia Bhatt Just Made Her Dubsmash Debut &amp; It's Not What You Expect #URL#", "People Share Their Secret Sex Moves #URL#", "Stephen Curry Shows Off His Ridiculous Handles in 2014-2015 #URL#", "'Montage of Heck' - VICE Meets Kurt Cobain Documentary Filmmaker Brett Morgen #URL#", "When The Sex Is Wack! #URL#", "NBA Conference Semifinals 2015 Commercial – Lessons in Storytelling: The Final Chapter, Part 2 #URL#", "Willow Shields Gives Exclusive Details about Her Last Day on Set with Jennifer Lawrence", "Uditi Bali - cute and funny dubsmash #URL#", "Yet another dubsmash by Salman Khan with Sonakshi Sinha #URL#", "Best of Phantom: Hawks and Grizzlies Even Their Series #URL#", "Al Horford Denies Nene to Protect the Paint #URL#", "Resultats on a pas fait grand chose #URL#", "Ellie Goulding - Love Me Like You Do (Vevo’s Do It YourSelfie) #URL#", "Minecraft : Across the Time #HASHTAG# #URL#", "NEW The Best Vines of May 2015", "EMBRZ - Silent ft. Amy Rose #URL#", "Downhill MTB Through an Abandoned Mine - Through My Eyes w/ Aaron Chase #URL#", "Silky - cute dubsmash, Queen movie dialogue #URL#", "Special Compilation of Pakistani Actor &amp; Actresses Dubsmash Videos #URL#", "Interview Psy de Lolita Pille - Archive INA #URL#", "The Last Frontier - Pat Moore: Blueprint - Season 2 Ep 8 #URL#", "Snoop Dogg, Pharrell Williams - BUSH Track By Track #URL#", "COMMENT GAGNER DE L ARGENT SUR INTERNET EN TUNISIE #URL#", "Chariot • Launch Trailer • PS3 #URL#", "Madrid 2015 Wednesday Hot Shot Cilic #URL#", "Return to Sender Official Trailer #HASHTAG# (2015) - Rosamund Pike Thriller HD #URL#", "SMOSH Schools Us on YouTube #URL#", "COMMENT GAGNER FACILEMENT DE L ARGENT SUR INTERNET #URL#", "Yo! Yo! Honey Singh - Dubsmash Debut - 2015 #URL#", "Disney Infinity 3 0 Edition • Announcement Trailer • PS4 Xbox One PS3 Xbox360 WiiU PC iOS Android WP #URL#"], "ents": [[{"py/tuple": ["Ryan Gosling", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Ryan McHenry", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["James Harden's", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["2014-2015", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["5", "CARDINAL"]}, {"py/tuple": ["NBA", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["May 5th", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Wild Hunt", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Canadian Kish's", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Aiman", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Mike Conley Returns", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Lead Grizzlies", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Game 2", "EVENT"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Karl Lagerfeld's", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["CHANEL", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["2", "CARDINAL"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Nexus Trailer", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["50", "CARDINAL"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Hawaii", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["3", "CARDINAL"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Anita H Reddy", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Destiny", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["House of Wolves Prison of Elders Reveal Teaser", "ORG"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Indian", "NORP"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Asha Negi", "ORG"]}], [], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Hohokum • Action Trailer •", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["COMMENT JE PEUX GAGNER DE L ARGENT SUR INTERNET", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["3", "CARDINAL"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Trailer", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Stephen Curry", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["396", "CARDINAL"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Bob Lennon", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Wild Hunt", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Tony Allen Steals", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Andrew Bogut Sends Courtney Lee Away", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Wolfenstein The Old Blood •", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Nexus Trailer", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["COMMENT SE FAIRE DE L ARGENT DE POCHE", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["COMMENT TROUVE DE L ARGENT RAPIDEMENT", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Trailer", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["2015", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Tatum", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Matt Bomer Movie HD", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["House", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["D8", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Madrid", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["2015", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Tuesday", "DATE"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Indian", "NORP"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Anita Hassanandani", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Middle Earth Shadow", "LOC"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Mordor", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["the Year Edition Trailer", "EVENT"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Xbox", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["NBA Daily Show", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["May 5", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["COMMENT GAGNER DE L ARGENT SANS INTERNET", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Fiji", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Qingdao", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Ultimate Kim Kardashian Paper Magazine Cake", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Laxmi Rai", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Trailer", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Kit Harington", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Hayley Atwell War Movie HD", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Pakistani", "NORP"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Robert Pattinson's", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Bruno Peyron - Archive INA", "ORG"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["2", "CARDINAL"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Ari Touboul", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["David Hasselhoff - True", "PERSON"]}], [], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Forza Horizon 2", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Xbox One", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Kim Kardashian", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Justin Bieber", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Selfie Ban", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Hollyscoop News", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Brooklyn", "GPE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Alia Bhatt's", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Kahui", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Cooper", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["COMMENT GAGNER DE L ARGENT FACILEMENT", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Holmes", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["US", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Trailer", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Ian McKellen", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Wolfenstein The Old Blood •", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Phone Apps", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Stupidizer, Linqapp, Drupe, Kolor", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Condom - Short Film - Hot", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Alia Bhatt", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Stephen Curry", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["2014-2015", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Brett Morgen", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["The Sex Is Wack", "WORK_OF_ART"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["NBA Conference Semifinals", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["2015", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Lessons in Storytelling: The Final Chapter", "WORK_OF_ART"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Last Day", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Jennifer Lawrence", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Salman Khan", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Sonakshi Sinha", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Al Horford", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Nene", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Ellie Goulding - Love Me Like You Do", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Vevo", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["YourSelfie", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["May 2015", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["EMBRZ - Silent", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Amy Rose", "PERSON"]}], [], [], [{"py/tuple": ["Pakistani", "NORP"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Interview Psy de Lolita Pille - Archive INA", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["2", "CARDINAL"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Snoop Dogg", "ORG"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Pharrell Williams - BUSH", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["COMMENT GAGNER DE L ARGENT SUR INTERNET EN", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Chariot • Launch Trailer", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Madrid", "GPE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["2015", "DATE"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Wednesday", "DATE"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Trailer", "PERSON"]}], [], [{"py/tuple": ["COMMENT GAGNER FACILEMENT DE L ARGENT SUR INTERNET", "ORG"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["Yo", "PERSON"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Honey Singh - Dubsmash", "PERSON"]}], [{"py/tuple": ["3", "CARDINAL"]}, {"py/tuple": ["Android WP", "PERSON"]}]], "POS_tags": [[{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "ADJ"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "X", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NUM", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "VERB", "VERB", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "X", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "X", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "X", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "X", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PRON", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "X", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "X", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "X", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADP", "VERB", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN", "X", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "X", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PART", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "AUX", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "AUX", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SCONJ", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "X", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADP", "PRON", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "X", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "NUM", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "VERB", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "ADV"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADV", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "AUX", "PART", "PRON", "PRON", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "DET", "NOUN", "AUX", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADV", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "ADV", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "VERB"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PRON", "INTJ", "PRON", "AUX", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "AUX", "PRON", "PROPN", "PUNCT"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "SPACE"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["ADJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["NOUN", "X", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "PRON", "ADP", "PROPN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM"]}], [{"py/object": "builtins.generator", "py/iterator": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "NUM", "NOUN", "X", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN"]}]], "clean": ["ryan gosling eat -pron- cereal as tribute to vine star ryan mchenry", "good of phantom james harden season highlight", "top nba plays may", "the witcher wild hunt monsters dev diary xbox one pc", "inked the story behind canadian kish tattoo", "dubsmash by aiman and muneeb", "mike conley return to lead grizzly to game win", "karl lagerfeld interview cruise chanel show", "mai hondelatte direct bfmtv zohra bitan et buisson", "cute girl dubsmash tamil video", "wildstar invasion nexus trailer fr pc", "shades trailer version lego", "the other side make in hawaii part", "the royal baby highlights", "tv actor anita h reddy dubsmashe haryanvi dialogue a must watch", "destiny house of wolves prison of elders reveal teaser xbox one", "cruise chanel show first look", "dubsmash of indian tv actor of asha negi", "dubsmash pakistan celebrity", "dragon age inquisition dragonslayer dlc trailer fr xbox one pc", "hohokum action trailer ps vita", "comment je peux gagner de l argent sur internet", "the human centipede final sequence official trailer horror movie hd", "stephen curry accept mvp trophy", "skyrim ep playthrough fr hd par bob lennon", "the witcher wild hunt monsters dev diary fr xbox one pc", "tony allen steals and flush -pron- home", "andrew bogut sends courtney lee away with the swat", "wolfenstein the old blood gameplay launch trailer fr xbox one pc", "achieve long life and low cost in separator for fuel cell", "wildstar invasion nexus trailer pc", "dragon age inquisition dragonslayer dlc trailer xbox one pc", "comment se faire de l argent de poche", "comment trouve de l argent rapidement", "magic mike xxl official trailer channe tatum matt bomer movie hd", "house of crade bertrand chameroy en prime sur", "madrid tuesday hot shot andujar", "funny telugu dubsmash viswanath naidu", "dubsmash by indian tv actor anita hassanandani", "middle earth shadow of mordor game of the year edition trailer fr xbox one pc", "nba daily show may the starters", "comment gagner de l argent sans internet", "development woman game gather pace in fiji", "extreme sailing competition in qingdao", "the ultimate kim kardashian paper magazine cake", "laxmi rai friends dubsmash kollywood", "ramon sessions drops circus shoot high off the glass", "testament of youth official us release trailer kit harington hayley atwell war movie hd", "another dubsmash video of pakistani actors and actresses", "sctm the hidden face of paradise", "fka twigs have a penis on -pron- dress at met gala -pron- be robert pattinson", "triomphe romain pour bruno peyron archive ina", "justin timberlake dress like a lime in crazy tequila commercial", "magicka completely unscripted co op trailer pc", "super clasheur vs ari touboul", "david hasselhoff true survivor video commentary", "myriam abel all by -pron- archive ina", "interview big apple amanda big apple archive ina", "forza horizon alpine stars car pack trailer fr xbox one", "comment on fait pour gagner de l argent", "kim kardashian and justin bieber give two about selfie ban at met hollyscoop news", "stéphane freiss brooklyn boy et le grand rôle archive ina", "alia bhatt dubsmash will make -pron- laugh out hard", "kahui smash cooper with huge tackle", "comment gagner de l argent facilement en travaillant", "holmes official us release trailer ian mckellen mystery drama hd", "special compilation of pakistani actresses dubsmash video", "wolfenstein the old blood gameplay launch trailer xbox one pc", "phone app stupidizer linqapp drupe kolor", "randi sex with condom short film hot scenes xxx", "alia bhatt just make -pron- dubsmash debut -pron- not what -pron- expect", "people share -pron- secret sex move", "stephen curry show off -pron- ridiculous handle in", "montage of heck vice meet kurt cobain documentary filmmaker brett morgen", "when the sex be wack", "nba conference semifinals commercial lesson in storytelling the final chapter part", "willow shields give exclusive detail about -pron- last day on set with jennifer lawrence", "uditi bali cute and funny dubsmash", "yet another dubsmash by salman khan with sonakshi sinha", "good of phantom hawks and grizzlies even -pron- series", "al horford deny nene to protect the paint", "resultat on a pas fait grand choose", "ellie goulding love -pron- like -pron- do vevo do -pron- yourselfie", "minecraft across the time", "new the good vines of may", "embrz silent ft amy rose", "downhill mtb through an abandoned mine through -pron- eyes aaron chase", "silky cute dubsmash queen movie dialogue", "special compilation of pakistani actor actresse dubsmash video", "interview psy de lolita pille archive ina", "the last frontier pat moore blueprint season ep", "snoop dogg pharrell williams bush track by track", "comment gagner de l argent sur internet en tunisie", "chariot launch trailer", "madrid wednesday hot shot cilic", "return to sender official trailer rosamund pike thriller hd", "smosh school -pron- on youtube", "comment gagner facilement de l argent sur internet", "yo yo honey singh dubsmash debut", "disney infinity edition announcement trailer xbox one wiiu pc ios android wp"]}